Chapter 1: The Beginning (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!!

Luo Jing’s head was rumbling.

Boom!!

His head once again rumbled as his body violently jerked before falling down. Boom!

His head smashed onto something hard, causing him to grimace in pain.

As he slowly opened his eyes, he could only see a dim, blurry background. In front of him, a silhouette was moving back and forth, as if it was busy closing the window and cleaning up the room. Next to the silhouette was a window; lightning flashed outside, brightly illuminating the room as if it were day.

"Oww…"

Luo Jing moaned as he tried to raise his hand to rub the back of his head, but his body wouldn’t move: a mixture of pain, itching, and numbness had left it paralyzed. It was as if his limbs didn’t belong to him; they firmly laid on the ground beside him like four wooden sticks.

"Am I dead?" His mind was still chaotic. He had a flashback: while taking a shower, he had accidentally touched the power outlet with his wet hands, electrocuting himself in the process. With his own eyes, he watched as a burst of blue electric current emerged between his finger and the sockets, and after which came a pungent smell of burnt flesh as he lost consciousness.

His head was in a daze; it seemed like all his memories had turned to mush.

Luo Jing opened his eyes as much as he could, trying to figure out what was going on around him.

"Thud!"

After another violent rumbling, his head hit the headboard of the bed, filling him with yet another outburst of unbearable pain as he passed out soon after.

Nobody knew how long it had been, perhaps one day or perhaps several days, when he finally regained consciousness and could feel his body once more.

He heard the soft sound of a door closing.

"Has mother left already?" A girl’s voice asked.

"Yes, she ate breakfast before us and went out to get some groceries. I’m going to leave to visit your auntie soon as well." The familiar voice of a man answered, followed by silence.

Luo Jing found himself in a small bedroom. In front of him was a reading desk. He was holding a black pen, writing something on a piece of white paper. A bright light shone from the window to his right; light rain showers fell outside, and the roof of the residence building across the street was soaked through.

Suddenly, like a flood breaking out of a dam, a huge and complex wave of thoughts rampaged into his mind.

He unconsciously groaned and gripped his forehead with his hands. Countless new memories swarmed into his brain.

"Garen? My... my name is Garen? Have I traveled to an alternate reality?"

He couldn’t think about anything else; still bearing a headache, he started exploring the memories that had just flowed into his brain.

This world was similar to Europe prior to the Nuclear Age. There were cars, planes, and firearms like guns and cannons, but weapons of mass destruction had not been developed yet.

His new identity was a boy named Garen from a middle-class family. He was 16 years old and his parents were employees of a rubber company. He had a little sister called Ying Er. The lifestyle was like that of the 20th century Europe, but the memories of his family and his own appearance made it clear that this place was definitely not on Earth. Both Garen and his sister were born with dark purple hair and eyes the color of wine. Their hair color was passed down from their father and eye color from their mother. He’d never heard of anyone born with these hair and eye colors on Earth. Furthermore, in Garen’s memories of history, the most powerful countries in the world were not China, the United States, or Russia. Instead, they were the Yalu Confederation, Weisman Empire, and the Republic of the Tulip. Just like Earth, there were a few hundred other countries of varying sizes and governments.

Asides from the difference in names and lifestyle, things were very similar to Earth. People who lived here received education as well, starting from elementary school, then middle school, and finally college. Right now, Garen was attending the third best high school in the province, Shengying Nobles Academy. It was the first year of school. During the school break, Garen was sick in bed with a fever and actually died, just as Luo Jing died in his world and ended up here.

Still collecting his memories, Luo Jing started to change clothes. When he snapped out of his trance, he found himself in a small and tidy room, eating a soft cherry cake on the dining table. The palm-sized cake had a creamy-yellow color, and was decorated by a ring made of whipped cream with cherries on top.

Luo Jing’s mind was still going through Garen’s memory. Although they were attending a nobles’ academy, their parents were barely able to pay the fees by living frugally and working overtime. In order to let both their son and daughter attend this academy, all expenses at home were cut to the bare minimum: their parents didn’t buy new clothes or jewelry, the handsome bonuses and the salary from the rubber company were all used to pay for their tuition.

Unfortunately, the two children weren’t particularly gifted when it came to studying. Thus, no matter how hard they tried, their rankings and scores were always in the lower half of the class rankings. In the academy, the other students all came from well-off families. As a result, the siblings started feeling inferior compared to their peers, and that affected their once optimistic personalities. Garen became an introverted "weirdo", and Ying Er became taciturn.

"You are heading off for school soon, don’t fight with your friends, work hard and try to get into a good college." The father, Mr. Lombard, sat across the table and urged him while eating his plate of salad. "And you Ying Er, don’t read those fiction books all day, school subjects are your priority."

"Alright Daddy," Ying Er replied. She sat at Luo Jing’s right side, wearing a fine white girdle waist sweater. A white corsage on her chest outlined her immature yet fine body line. She was wearing a deep purple bouffant mini skirt and her legs were covered in black leggings. While Ying Er was eating the cake, her two small black shoes were pointed inwards, her head was down, and she looked submissive.

Luo Jing silently ate the cake and drank a sip of milk from time to time. He looked at his sister’s dress: it flaunted a glowing black silver pin on her chest that looked like a wreath surrounding a logo. This was an indication that she was a student of Shengying Nobles Academy.

He looked at his own clothes: a slim-fit white shirt which had black and silver stripes on the cuffs and neckline. The lower body was also a pair of slim-fit black trousers, paired with black dress shoes. His uniform looked striking yet delicate.

The siblings both had very average appearances, the only highlights being their purple hair and their wine-colored eyes. The sister looked ordinary, with some freckles and acne on her face. Garen himself had messy hair, and his eyes looked empty because the sockets sank deep into his face, giving the impression that he had been sick for years.

Luo Jing wasn’t able to absorb most of the information from Garen’s memories until after breakfast. The siblings helped in cleaning up the dishes before going back to their rooms to get ready for school.

"Brother, have you seen my history textbook?" asked Ying Er loudly from her room.

"Nope," answered Luo Jing, or should we call him Garen now, thoughtlessly.

He was also preparing his textbooks. History, geography, etiquette, math and other various subjects; they had more subjects compared to the high schools on Earth. There were even swordsmanship and archery textbooks among them. Garen let out a relieved sigh after shoving all the books inside the black backpack. He walked to the window and pushed it open, letting in a moist and cool breeze.

Outside the window was an open space between two residential buildings; the ground was covered with a black and gray checkerboard pattern. To the west of the field, some people were lining up behind a brawny man with a sign. The crowd was slowly gathering, and it seemed like they were going somewhere. The letters on the sign spelled ‘Collins Wins’.

Just below the window, on the first floor of the building where Garen lived in, a woman walked out while pushing a grayish yellow trolley. It was filled with utensils and cooking materials for making crepes.

"Whoosh!" A white bird flew in front of his window and made a few turns before disappearing again.

Entranced by the bird, he suddenly snapped out of his daze, realizing that he was really in a completely different world now, standing on the fourth floor of a building in a totally different environment from the China he knew.

Most people outside had either blond or silver hair, while some had red hair, and their eye and skin colors varied greatly. The language they were speaking and writing in was an alphabetic language like English. Having obtained the memories from before, Garen was able to understand it.

He was no longer the adult man on planet Earth, but an ordinary boy of only sixteen years of age, with an ordinary family, look, and background. Along with that, there was also his weak and ill body. His parents worked every day, from dusk until dawn. He and his sister came home from school once a week and, between school and home, life was boring and linear. He just had to graduate from high school and take part in the national examination. If he was lucky, he’d get into a decent college, have a good degree, and find a well-paying job in the future. He was one among thousands of students that would take the examination.

Their parents’ greatest expectation for them was to have a decent job.

"If this kid weren’t sick and ill, I might not have successfully traveled into this world," Garen thought with a wry smile. He had a feeling that earlier in the carriage during his coma, it might have been the body of Garen instinctively resisting Luo Jing’s consciousness. If Garen had a healthy body, he might have prevented Luo Jing’s spirit from ever possessing it.

"From his memory, this world should still be in the era just before World War II, without large-scale weapons of war; this is a world similar to mine before the emergence of nuclear weapons." He carefully thought, "This isn’t what I imagined. There’s no magic, no energy, not a XianXia world, not even a small trace of supernatural events."

Thinking of this, he didn’t know what to do. When he found out he had traveled to an alternate reality, he had some small expectations. But after scrounging through Garen’s memory, he realized that this world was merely one that was decades behind in technology.

"Oh well, let's take it step by step, recuperating is of utmost importance right now." Garen raised his arms, which were skinny like bamboo sticks, and a helpless smile showed up on his face.

Bringing their respective backpacks, the siblings walked outside together and closed the door. Garen walked in the front with garbage bags in his hands, and as they stumbled down the stairs, he carefully observed the other households and the situation of this era: the staircase was dark, each floor only had two households, and every one of them had a brass mailbox on the left side of the door, with names engraved on them. They looked quite old.

The residents going in and out were wearing tidy and elegant suits and dresses. Although they had very tired expressions, they moved in a hurry and kept their backs straight; it was natural to say that they just had very fast-paced lives. Only a small number of households were in poor condition, and some were rented by street vendors.

The two walked out of the staircase in silence. Garen disposed the garbage and looked at his sister to his left. Ying Er was a few inches shorter than him, and she was brought in by his stepfather after Garen’s father had passed away. Thus, they were not blood-related, although the two had the same hair and eyes. The relationship between them was not close, not any better than normal friends.

As usual, the two got on the school bus, which was already littered with a few students.

Chapter 2: The Beginning (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen found a seat in the back of the bus next to his sister. He glanced at the students sitting in the seats in front of them and saw that everyone else was also wearing Shengying Academy’s uniforms. The girls were dressed like his sister, wearing a white t-shirt paired with a black miniskirt and black leggings.

On the other hand, the boys were wearing stylish slim-fit white shirts, black trousers and black shoes. They looked neatly uniformed.

The students were chattering in groups, with laughter all around them.

Not long after they stepped on, the bus stopped again, and two more students from the academy came in.

After many stops in the same manner, two handsome boys hopped on while chatting; one of them was tall and slim, while the other had a sturdy build. Both looked confident and classy, and they immediately drew the attention of the girls on the bus.

Garen sat next to his sister and saw her unconsciously staring at the two guys that just boarded the bus. He was comparing himself to them but shook his head helplessly. He looked at them just once more before withdrawing his eyes.

There were too many ordinary guys like him sitting at inconspicuous corners on the bus; compared to those two, they were merely foil characters.

Garen watched as the scenery outside the window flew past. Street lamps stood one by one on both sides of the tidy streets. The surroundings were mostly composed of ordinary-looking concrete houses, but occasionally he could see some white marble buildings. The architectural style was a bit similar to the Europe’s. From time to time, there were cars speeding past the bus.

"Mom and dad told us not to go back home next week, so we need to spend the weekend at school. The company assigned them to a business trip, and since they might not come back this week, they told us to take care of ourselves," said Ying Er in a low voice.

"Got it," he nodded and replied in his usual tone. "Oh right, your rank went up after the last exam. Dad bought you a teddy bear right?"

"So what?" Ying Er turned her head, "If your grades went up mom would get you something as reward too."

Garen smiled and stopped talking to her. Unexpectedly, he noticed that five red transparent numbers slowly emerged in the bottom part of his field of vision.

Garen restrained his smile. Shocked for a moment, he looked around, but no one had noticed his peculiar behavior. Those who were laughing continued, those who were chatting carried on with their conversations. Beside him, Ying Er pulled out a history textbook and started silently memorizing.

"What is this, is it the benefit of traveling to an alternate reality?" Garen had read many webnovels before, and some mentioned that people who traveled to alternate realities would have gifts bestowed upon them. He just thought he didn’t receive any, but after a while, something unnatural showed up. There were red symbols that apparently only he could see.

He focused on the five symbols at the bottom of his vision, and his lips moved silently as he read the information: "Strength 0.31, Agility 0.22, Vitality 0.27, Intelligence 0.32, Potential 25%."

Right after he finished reading them, a short and brief memory suddenly surged into his mind.

Garen closed his eyes and stood still on his seat. A moment later, he slowly opened them back, enlightened. "I changed and gained superpowers as a result of electrocution and transmigration?" He clearly remembered the whole process of how this power came to be after the mutation, countless coincidences and complex unimaginable changes occurred before this ability was created.

"When the Potential attribute reaches 100%, I can increase one of the other four attributes?" Garen was puzzled and looked at the 25% Potential, but still could not believe it. "Isn’t this the same as playing RPG games? I can choose which of my attributes I would like to increase in real life."

Garen was aware that in this world, the technology was behind, and thus melee weapons were still used together with firearms. Therefore, if this ability could really improve his attributes, his future would be unimaginable compared to ordinary people.

"But, this isn’t just an illusion, right…" Garen thought with a mocking smile, "Maybe I’m going crazy thinking about getting a superpower."

The bus suddenly stopped.

"We’re here, everyone get off the bus." The driver was a man with hard whiskers, he was yelling with his body turned around.

The students started getting off the bus one after another. Ying Er pushed Garen lightly to bring him back from his daydream and got off the bus first, carrying her backpack.

A line of black school buses was parked near the edge of a huge green lawn, while students of the Shengying Academy were continuously moving toward a group of buildings at the other side, all dressed in the same uniform, white at the top and black at the bottom.

At the far end of the lawn stood a swath of buildings. The main building had a white dome with yellow patterns, and around it there were towering buildings with dozens of floors with white domes and dark yellow patterns. In the distance, one could vaguely see large buildings with similar architecture styles. Many students were moving between them, and among them there were some teachers wearing black uniforms.

On the edge of the lawn, a skinny boy walked away from one of the buses. He had purple hair, red eyes, and an overall pallid appearance. He looked listless.

Garen roughly glanced at the academy’s facilities. Looking behind him, he saw a ring of tall white fences surrounding the academy. The buses came in through a white arched gate and were leaving the campus after dropping off the students.

"This is pretty much like the schools on Earth." Garen followed the other students toward the buildings across the lawn.

"Garen is from Grade 9, class 2…" He moved based on his memories, quickly following the crowd to the left side of the vast campus. He stopped in front of a trapezoidal building and walked up the stairs.

The second classroom on the second floor had the brass tag, Grade 9 Class 2, hanging above it.

Garen followed two boys into the class and walked toward his seat near the window in the back of the room. He threw his backpack inside the desk’s compartment and began thinking about the five attribute symbols at the bottom of his vision. Since he had only been here for one semester and he was introverted, he had no friends in the class.

The first class was mathematics; the professor was a middle-aged woman with a stern face. The material was only of elementary school level. Garen listened for a few minutes and continued minding his own business. The class after that was language, which taught them the language and writing as well as literature of this country. Garen didn’t bother listening.

The third class was etiquette, but instead of paying attention, Garen was testing the connection between the attributes and his body -- when suddenly, the Potential attribute number in his vision shook, drawing his attention and making him flinch.

Shocked, Garen looked around the class, but no one had noticed it, so he raised his head and looked at the podium.

At the front of the class, the etiquette teacher was holding an open rosewood box, which had various gems and jewelry inside. "One’s own appearance is also a representation of how much respect you have for the people you interact with, and jewelry is one of the key factors in improving one’s image. Last class we talked about gold and silver jewelry, and today we will be going over how gems and diamonds are used in fashion."

The etiquette teacher was a man wearing an elegant beard and glasses. His expressions were meticulous, giving a natural and elegant vibe. "Now you will pass on these gems and observe them one by one. Nobles are not just wealthy in the materialistic way, more important is the nobleness in your heart. Self-discipline, elegance, self-esteem, responsibility, courage, and so on, together with a good image and quality attire. Combine all of these and you can call yourself a noble. If one’s only pride is in his lavishness and wealth, then he is merely a parvenu."

Garen sat in the back of the room watching as the box was passed on for the students to see. Before he could react, the numbers on the bottom of his vision started changing. The last attribute, Potential, started slowly increasing from 25% to 26%, like the second hand on a clock moving up.

He paid attention to his classmates as they passed on the box; most of them were just casually glancing through them since they were obviously used to gems and jewelry like these. Only a few students seemed excited when they held the box, as they were the ones from the not so well-off families.

After waiting for long ten minutes, the rosewood box was finally passed to the chubby kid wearing glasses in front of Garen. He roughly flipped through the contents, and then handed the box to Garen. "Here you go."

"Thanks." Garen carefully received the box. The moment he held it in his hands, he felt his body becoming numb, with a tingling sensation that started on his fingers and flowed through his body like the steady flow of cold air inside a fridge.

Garen quickly put down the box and fiddled inside with his hands until he found a black and red pearl. "That’s it…" He picked up the pearl lightly, and the cold flow became stronger.

At the bottom of his vision in the attribute pane, the Potential percentage jumped up crazily like it took drugs, within ten seconds, from 26%, it rushed to 50%, then 80%, and 100%.

As the number reached 100%, Garen felt the black and red pearl in his hand dimmed, as if it had aged.

He quickly put the pearl back into the box, and passed it to the last student on his right-hand side. Even then, the box had been in his hands for quite some time.

The student to his right was a redhead girl with a ponytail. She looked at him with a frown, took the box and immediately passed it on to the guy in front of her, without even glancing at the jewelry.

Garen knew this girl; her name was Ai Fei. Like him, her family was not well-off, but unlike him Ai Fei had good grades and great self-discipline; it could even be said that her personality was somewhat rigid. They were also a little similar in that they didn’t have any friends.

He didn’t bother with the girl since his focus was on the Potential percentage that only he could see. An unknown flow of air was hovering in his eyes, but it only started after he achieved 100% in Potential. He had a feeling that if he focused on one of his attributes for three seconds, this flow of air would jump onto that attribute, increasing it.

"So it really wasn’t my imagination… I really got this superpower!" Garen was excited; after living for decades, he unexpectedly achieved his childhood dreams of having superpowers. Even with his temperament, it was a little unnerving.

"Then, which attribute should I put this flow into?" Garen’s eyes cruised between the four attributes.

Strength, Agility, Vitality, and Intelligence.

Chapter 3: The beginning (3)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The class was about to end but Garen still hadn’t decided on which attribute to enhance. At this point, he finally believed this supernatural ability was actually real.

"Riiiiiiinnngg"

After the crisp sound of school bells, the etiquette teacher collected his rosewood box and left the classroom. The class went from complete silence to chaos.

Garen remained seated in his desk, startled by the mess. He straightened his back and let out a relieved sigh. Suddenly, he felt his belly deflating and quickly covered it with his hands. A sense of hunger -- never felt before -- came from his stomach.

He bent down and looked around, checking to see that no one was looking at him. He reached into his pockets and took some blue papers out, each of which had either the numbers 1 or 5 printed on them. Counting the bills, Garen slightly knitted his brows.

"Only fifteen dollars to spend... this is far from enough for one week. Also, I remember eating breakfast just now, but when the potential reached 100% I started feeling hungry again. It seems like the potential wasn’t just draining energy from the gem, but also from my body’s digestive system."

At that moment, someone patted him on the shoulder. "Garen, same old spot for lunch?" A young male voice came from behind him.

Garen turned around and saw the white-skinned hand of a freckled boy laying on his shoulder.

"What old spot?"

"The one close to the windows." The boy’s name was Kalidor, one of the students Garen was most acquainted with in his class.

"Last weekend the cafeteria had jasmine tea and dim sum. I wonder what’s on the menu today?" Another teenager joined them and murmured, "If they still have that specialty dark purple fruit jam, I’m ordering it."

"All right, I’m going to get the goat milk for everyone, so give me your money. Five bucks each." Kalidor extended his hands. All the students had the habit of drinking hot goat milk before lunch.

Right after Kalidor reached out, a dozen students gathered around him one after another, placing five dollar bills in his hands.

"I’ll have one!"

"I’ll have one too."

"Same for me…"

These students were nowhere to be seen just now, but when they heard someone was willing to fetch the milk, they all showed up out of the blue.

Kalidor counted the money in a hurry. "There’s money here for twelve people... Garen, don’t you want milk? In case you want something else I can bring it for you instead of the milk."

"It’s okay, you know I don’t like goat milk." Garen quickly refused. He pretended to look indifferent, but the truth was that he had no money, so even if he liked it he had to say he didn’t. The small amount of money he had was to be spent on more essential things. After all, the old Garen had always used that pretense as an excuse for not buying milk, so the new one just followed his lead.

However, Kalidor had no idea of his true thoughts and always just believed that he didn’t like goat milk. "Come on! Try it once, it’s delicious! I can bring you one. What are you afraid of?"

"It’s okay, I really don’t like it." Garen refused again.

"Try it man, it’s great!"

"No thanks, I’m good. You guys go ahead!"

"Fine then…" Kalidor shrugged his shoulders and jogged out of the classroom.

After a little while, the students chattering all had a carton of goat milk in their hands while Garen had to pretend he was focusing on his school work. He lowered his head and started taking notes. Over the last few days, he had started exercising more frequently. The amount of money he had on him was far from enough to satiate his new highly active metabolism. As he smelled the fragrance of the hot milk, his belly started growling again. Fortunately, the loud chattering noises covered it up and no one heard it. He shook his head helplessly, then suddenly noticed the girl on his right, Ai Fei.

Just like him, Ai Fei was pretending to be studying with her head lowered. She strained as she sucked her stomach inward in an obviously unnatural position, trying to prevent her belly from making a sound.

Ai Fei seemed to have noticed someone staring at her and looked over. When their eyes met, both Garen and Ai Fei blushed. They roughly understood that they were in the same situation and thus a sympathetic feeling rose between the two.

After drinking the goat milk, Garen and the other boys left toward the cafeteria, laughing and chatting.

The cafeteria stood in the center of the academy, surrounded by student dormitories. It had the shape of a black cube, with each side containing an entrance. Students were constantly coming in and out through the doors. One could smell the sweet scent of cakes and bread, and hear the noisy students long before walking inside. Garen ate the free lunch together with his acquaintances, finally satisfying the ravenous hunger in his belly.

Following the crowd out of the cafeteria, Garen raised his head and looked up at the clear sky. The bright sun shone on his face and he felt a burning sensation. "This place really lives up to its name as one of the top 100 schools in the nation. Shengying Nobles Academy probably has the best food among all the ones in Huaishan City… The class schedule is different in the afternoon, school would be out at three. I could go to that place and test the effectiveness of my abilities."

Looking again at the five symbols at the bottom of his vision, Garen’s eyes glimmered with anticipation. He started recalling all the information he had about the local geography. "I have to check out the details of my surroundings…" Thinking of this, he looked around, picked a direction that looked vacant, and marched off in big strides, quickly disappearing among the buildings.

********************

The orange and oblique light of dawn shone above Huaishan City, dying the large complex of buildings red. Some high-rise buildings with pointed and domed roofs reflected the sunlight like mirrors. A breeze of warm air gusted through the city.

In the south district, next to the streets west of the well-known Shengying Nobles Academy, there stood a spacious courtyard built with redwood. In front of the yard, there were simple houses while the back had two huge training grounds.

On the corner of the yellow training ground to the left, some youngsters in yellow uniforms were hitting the training dummies under the shade. The sound of impact rang out ceaselessly. A young man in white uniform was walking between them with hands in his back, correcting the boys when they made mistakes. One of the young men stood on the outer rim of the grounds, under the shadow of the surrounding trees. He had purple hair and wine-red eyes. It was Garen, who discreetly left Shengying Nobles Academy after lunch to come here.

This was an ordinary dojo near Shengying Nobles Academy, which specialized in teaching basic martial arts. Garen and two other classmates joined the dojo out of pure impulsiveness; they only wanted to practice martial arts because they noticed that the students practicing here all had a sturdy body and wanted to look as fit as they were.

Garen was sluggishly whacking the wooden dummy in front of him. The dummy was as tall as a person and had a dark yellow body covered with rubber. Even if he hit it with great force, his hands would not feel any pain.

After a while, he took a break. "According to Garen’s memory, it wouldn’t be wrong to say he didn’t have much talent, but he did work very hard at this dojo. He had practiced the White Cloud Dojo’s basic combat techniques countless times. However, his talent and his body were just terrible. In this world, without Qi or special abilities, anything would be meaningless if one’s body was too weak."

Leaning against the stout wooden dummy, Garen panted lightly and organized his thoughts. "In the White Cloud Dojo, the dojo master was rarely seen. The ones teaching the techniques are usually the dojo master’s disciples who have mastered the basics. The one teaching us…" Garen’s eyes landed on the young man in white uniform, "…is Luo Ya, and there is another girl named Sharmilla."

"The basic combat techniques I learned should be good enough, but my body is too weak, making it impossible for me to stand out among the others."

Garen had something planned in his mind. As he was thinking about this plan, he started exercising his body again, following the routines he already knew by heart.

A few minutes later, from the far side of the training ground, a girl in a white uniform with a ponytail hastily walked over and talked with Luo Ya, who was standing among the students. Luo Ya decisively walked toward the exit, giving the impression that someone was waiting for him outside.

The ponytail girl in the white uniform was Sharmilla, who was now covering for Luo Ya. Most of the students were familiar with her, so no one questioned the substitution.

Garen glanced at Sharmilla. Her slender legs were her greatest pride. She was tall and had a slim waist, with white skin and a charming face. In the continuous demonstration of the correct positions and movements of the techniques, her chests bounced slightly, showing amazing tension and suppleness.

A lot of boys who were practicing peeked at her now and then. Some of them seemed to be hitting the training dummies much harder than before. One of the students made a mistake on purpose and was spotted by Sharmilla. She scolded him with a smile and flicked his forehead.

"I love it when assistant Sharmilla is teaching us. This is the best!" The two boys next to Garen mumbled. Garen, of course, did not waste his time replying. "I didn’t save my money to look at pretty girls. I came here to practice combat skills."

"All right, pick a partner and let’s start one-on-one training. We’ll rank everyone later. Same exercises as usual, the five who place the worst will clean up the field." Sharmilla raised her voice and announced.

Garen’s movements gradually died out and he squeezed the dummy’s arm in anger. In the dojo, they had to do one-on-one ranked combat daily. Garen was consistently one of the people cleaning up the grounds since he rarely won a match, and thus could never relax after the training sessions. He was one of the worst among the twenty students in this class.

Hearing that ranked sparring was about to begin, his eyes landed on a girl with short silver hair. He had lost to this girl last time, once more joining the ranks of his fellow cleaners.

On the other hand, the girl did not notice his gaze. She was focused on chatting with a female friend of hers, occasionally laughing out loud.

Sharmilla inspected the students, nodding satisfied at the growing eagerness in their eyes. "The combat techniques of our White Cloud Dojo are simple but effective. Even an ordinary person can instantly use forces up to 1.5 times greater than his original strength if they master this technique, but only five among them have mastered it. We will observe them for a few more days, but if no one else improves we’ll have to pick two among these five and teach them better techniques, promoting them to elite students."

It was clear to her. No matter how much one practiced the basic combat technique, the effectiveness of the strength amplification was at most 1.5 times, and the training results were also very limited. Moreover, it was hard for ordinary people to master the technique. Only those who were truly interested in martial arts and had great perseverance could go one step further while the rest simply did not have enough willpower to practice advanced martial arts. Most dojos used this method to pick out the talented students for training.

Garen started preparing for the upcoming battle by reviewing the basic combat techniques and warming up his body while focusing his vision on the five symbols. "I should be able to use the basic combat technique to train my body while speeding up my growth with the help of attribute enhancements. This way, I have faith that no one would be able to surpass me in training speed. I wonder just how much the attribute enhancements would change my body…"

He carefully went through the five symbols in his vision. Strength 0.31. Agility 0.22. Vitality 0.27. Intelligence 0.32. Potential 100%. Garen’s focus switched back and forth on these five attributes, but no extra information from his memory showed up, so he stopped, disappointed.

"Okay, let’s begin," Sharmilla’s voice echoed over.

Chapter 4: The Beginning (4)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The martial arts dojos in this world were similar to the taekwondo dojos back on Earth. Their primary purpose was to promote physical exercise and workout. There existed a dojo ranking system, but most dojos were basically superfluous and non-lethal, aside from those high-ranked traditional ones. The ones not fighting for the top rankings were only useful for exercising and for showing off.

In this culture, martial art was similar to music or dancing, a part of the regular educational curriculum aimed at making the children more versatile and well-rounded.

Garen followed other students and spread out into pairs. Facing him was the same girl from last time.

She had ordinary looks: a slim waist, flat chest, and her silver hair glimmered crimson under the fading sunlight.

"Rank 15, Daris."

"Rank 16, Garen."

The two stood facing each other, then greeted by using their ranking and names.

"Begin!" Sharmilla yelled.

Garen and Daris stopped worrying about the other combatants and focused entirely on each other’s movements. The basic knowledge passed onto them did not contain any special moves or advanced fighting techniques. It was only a simple exercising routine and the Explosive Force Technique. In Garen’s memory, there were no special fighting moves; the so-called combat training was just two people fighting based on their own combat experience, with the only difference from any other fight being that they could use the Explosive Force Technique, thus allowing their strength to be heightened for some attacks. In fact, this was the dojo’s sole purpose in having a one on one combat training. The main goal was to test their students’ raw strength and potential.

At this point, Garen stopped thinking superfluous thoughts. He pounced onto Daris and threw a punch towards her left shoulder. He had not used the attribute enhancement yet, wanting to see how strong his body truly was.

While his fist was still in the air, Daris dodged to the right and swatted Garen’s chest with her shoulder. Neither of them was very agile and so Garen could easily react to the counter attack. He turned his body and tackled her with his own shoulder.

After a loud bump of shoulders clashing, both backed off a few steps. They then both charged and ended up in a grapple. Like before, they threw punches at each other without any form or routine. In the previous fight, Garen had been exhausted after wrestling for a while, which led to his defeat.

However, this time Garen made use of a brief gap when the two split apart and were both gasping for air to focus his attention on the five attributes at the bottom of his vision, stopping for some seconds on Strength.

"Clink"

A quiet sound ringed inside his head. Garen felt his muscle swelling up. In a blink, he felt as if he had grown larger.

Looking again at the Strength attribute, the number had increased from 0.31 to 0.41.

"This incredible change was the result of just an increase of 0.1 points?"

Garen’s heart skipped a beat, and he looked at Daris who was still panting.

Without a word, he charged forward again, but this time he bent his legs and applied a heavy force against the ground to gather momentum. The result was a distinct increase in his speed.

His strength turned to force, and force turned into acceleration. It was an abrupt change that Daris could not have foreseen. She tried to dodge to the side like the last time, but it was too late: she was tackled by Garen while her balance was off.

Daris sat on the ground after being knocked over with a flip. It seemed she could not get up. She gasped for air with a stunned expression. Her eyes were filled with shock and disbelief as she stared at Garen.

"Huff… You…" She was panting heavily, "You actually still have… this much strength?"

Garen clearly felt the changes that took place in his body, and he was joyous but also confused. With no time to check on Daris, he went back to Sharmilla to record the combat results.

Sharmilla had noticed Garen’s sudden burst of strength. Even though Garen had a weak body, he was one of the five students she had noticed this time. After recording the results, she nodded at Garen with a smile, "Go rest for now."

"Yes, assistant Sharmilla." Garen wiped away the sweat with his sleeve and sat on the ground to take a break. Half of the students were sitting on the ground like him, waiting for the others to finish their fight. Watching the matches taking place under the shade, Garen slowly felt the full effects of the growth in his strength.

He raised his skinny arms, shockingly discovering a trace of contour of muscle, instead of the skin and bones from before. "Just by enhancing Strength by a tenth of a point I’m already much more powerful. My strength has increased at least by a third. Now, at the very least, I think I would rank 15th among the students, but probably not much higher. This is still a great improvement compared to before. What kind of changes would other attributes bring? Agility, Vitality, and Intelligence… If these attributes could enhance my body in the same manner…" Garen’s heart was filled with anticipation. "It seems I have to find the reason behind the increase in potential. If I can keep enhancing the strength attribute, I could probably join the dojo as a disciple. Then I would receive a handsome stipend from it."

*******************

The increase in strength did not bring many changes to Garen’s school life, other than the fact that now he eats a lot more. He stopped caring about school work, focusing entirely on grasping the true essence of the attributes. In order to continue filling the Potential meter, he started paying attention to the jewelry and gems that the girls were wearing. Also, after school, he would go to jewelry stores and pretend he wanted to buy something. After visiting every single jewelry store in the city, Garen had only found items that could increase his potential meter at a thrift jewelry shop: one was a sapphire and another was a tiny ruby on an earring. After touching these gems, his Potential meter raised to 89%. Unfortunately, he did not find any more special gems similar to those after the earring. Garen, by now, had also discovered what appeared to be a rule for the gems that could fill his potential meter: they had to be antique items from a long time ago.

*********************

"Hey Garen, wanna visit Jaderipple Lake with us this weekend?"

A few students gathered on the rooftop of one of the school buildings. They were hanging out and chatting near the railing, overlooking the school.

The morning sunlight was cool and pale, softly shining on their bodies without much warmth.

Garen was there as well, leaning against the railing. Kalidor and two youngsters he had just met were with him. Their names were Jake Reese and Fayne. There were also three other girls, Ai Fei and two of Fayne’s friends. The seven of them had just gotten to know each other this week.

"Jaderipple Lake? Where is that?" Garen asked Kalidor.

"It’s near the paper mill in the suburbs. We’ve only been there once. There were tons of swans at the lake, along with many other types of birds. And... you know…" With a sinister smirk on his face, Kalidor made an eye gesture at the girls who were merrily chatting behind them

"The point is, it’s a desolate wildland…" Jake added from the side. This boy looked quite mature with his short red hair and tanned skin. He looked like a candid fellow, but in truth, he had tricked and hurt a lot of girls’ feelings with his honest appearance.

"Easier to get things done…" Garen added, and the three of them laughed maliciously.

Kalidor winked at Fayne. "It will be every man for himself, so don’t blame me... There will be more girls this time, but Fayne and the two girls who are friends with him are going as well."

Garen shook his head. He had met Fayne’s friends some time ago. Fayne was from a wealthy family and the girls he brought were very pretty. However, last time they were together those girls all hung out solely among themselves, completely segregated from the impoverished students. They didn’t bother talking to them even after Fayne introduced the groups to each other.

"If it’s like the last time, then forget it." Garen replied, "I don’t have much spare money left anyway and don’t want the trouble, you guys can go by yourselves." Garen had grown some muscle in the last few days, so he did not look sickly and skinny anymore. His body had become more muscular and manly.

"It’s fine. I can pay for your share, no problem." Kalidor said as he slammed Garen’s shoulder. "Everyone traveling together is more fun. What’s the point of sticking around by yourself? If we don’t hang out often, we’ll become distant. What’s going on, you don’t like the gang anymore?"

"You’re paying for me again? Last time was…" Garen was speechless.

"Forget about all that, so do we have a deal? We’ll meet at the Academy’s front gate at 9 A.M., you guys good with that?"

"Of course."

"I’m fine with that."

The others had all agreed, and Garen was forced into an accord by Kalidor. Even though he really didn’t want to go, he couldn’t resist in the face of Kalidor’s overwhelming enthusiasm. He was under the impression that if he didn’t go, Kalidor would break up their friendship.

After settling on the time, they asked the girls to come, but Fayne’s friends had things to do and declined the invitation.

Only Ai Fei stood on the rooftop, with her right hand holding down her mini skirt. The place she was standing on was very windy, making the hemline of her skirt flutter in the wind. Ai Fei held her skirt with an uneasy expression, afraid of a wardrobe malfunction. Even though she was wearing leggings, an upskirt still was one of a girl’s most feared embarrassments.

Hearing the invitation to Jaderipple Lake, Ai Fei looked to Garen first. Ever since the goat milk event, the two had been feeling like they had a lot in common.

"Garen, are you going too?" She asked.

"Well… Fayne promised that if I go, he’d let me see his family’s jewelry collection… You know, it’s my hobby now."

Ai Fei nodded and slightly furrowed her brows. In the last few days, she had been paying some attention to Garen. She thought that this young man was different from the others. He was a lot more mature and prudent than the other boys, and his family was also financially similar to hers.

"Wouldn’t that leave your sister alone at home?"

"She’s going to practice at the archery club. Apparently, she’s about to join a competition. Her school performance might be lackluster but she sure is good at archery," Garen explained. He had to agree this time because he knew that Fayne’s family had an antique jewelry that could not be purchased elsewhere. It was very ancient, similar to the teacher’s black and red pearl he had absorbed the energy from earlier.

In order to enhance his abilities, he could not decline this invitation. The last enhancement to strength allowed him to reach rank 14 in the White Cloud Dojo’s class. After researching ways to fill his Potential meter, Garen found that this world was not as simple as he thought...

Chapter 5: The Outing

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Jaderipple Lake. Clear blue waters, lush green mountains, and glistening yellow stones. A few white birds slowly glided above the lake. A cool wind whistled through, making the surface of the azure lake ripple, blurring the reflection of the endless mountain range on the water.

The boys walked along the stone-filled riverbed and soon found a great spot for a picnic. Then, they began taking out tools and food from their backpacks.

Garen looked at the girls seated in the shade. Aside from the ones they already knew were coming, there was also a gorgeous surprise in the form of a girl named Felicity. This dazzling beauty’s white dress fluttered in the wind, and her blond hair was tied together and hung over her left shoulder. Her crystal clear skin was gleaming with a halo, and her eyes were filled with aloof loftiness, like the clearest sapphire in the world.

Withdrawing his gaze from her, Garen looked at himself, Kalidor, Fayne, and Jake. None of them knew how to dress up. Their attires were completely mismatched, comprising solely of various dull colors like beige, gray, white, and black. On top of that, the clothes they were wearing were cheap, making them look like a ragtag army of bandits. He had not felt this way before, but after comparing the boys to the girls on the other side, he could not help but acknowledge the significant difference.

"That girl is Felicity. Fayne’s friends invited her to come. She looks so elegant..." Kalidor said in a low volume while stacking the firewood together.

"Tsk, tsk… I haven’t seen anyone with an aura like that in the academy." Jake lowered his voice and added, "Imagine if you could have a girlfriend like that."

"She's my cousin’s friend, so I don’t know her either. You guys should keep it down," Fayne explained on the side. "I didn’t know my cousin would invite her, I told her to come with her other friend." He shrugged.

Garen smiled and squatted down with them, fixing the messy firewood. Compared to the pure and spotless Felicity, the boys who were working with muddy firewoods were from a completely different world.

"Want to play poker?" Kalidor leaned over and asked. The poker he mentioned was a game loved by children from poor families. The cards were made by folding paper and pinching holes on them. The rules were very similar to the game Garen knew on Earth.

Garen, Jake, and Fayne saw him pulling out some old poker cards and they got excited. "Let’s go, what do we use for stakes?" said one of them.

"Let’s use these roasted fish and kabobs! One per hand."

The few kids sat on the ground in a circle and began playing atop a white rock. It wasn’t long before they became heavily immersed in their game.

Felicity stood in the shade, watching the boys playing poker in the middle of the muddy riverbed. Her sapphire eyes did not have any trace of discrimination, but they still put her on a level above everyone else. She was from a different social class compared to the students in this small city. Originally, she was just passing by, but after the invitation of her friends and classmates, she agreed to come out for some fresh air.

A girl with short red hair came up to her and watched the boys together. "Fayne is my cousin, albeit a very distant one. The students here like to come out at night and set up a campfire to have a barbeque. Are you interested? I could introduce you to them."

"No thanks, that looks dirty…" Felicity frowned. "I’m just here to get some fresh air, it would be great if I could have some quiet time alone."

Garen was playing poker with the guys and noticed their eyes unconsciously wandering off towards the girls. He thought it was funny, so very discreetly, he took an extra card when it was his turn. He glanced at them but they were oblivious. He repeated this a few times until he finally showed his hands. "Sorry boys, I won."

"Wha…?" The others looked confused, their mouths agape.

Garen smiled and carefully stacked the cards together. Seeing his friends’ expressions, he thought of the old Garen in his memory. Before he traveled here, Garen used to get into arguments with his sister all the time. Furthermore, he would get knocked on the ground in just a few seconds every time, without any chance of retaliation.

Ying Er was not as fragile as she looked. She was great at all sports, martial arts and archery. He had been bullied by Ying Er ever since their parents married. He was three years old at the time, and Ying Er was only two.

However, Garen used to fail at everything, be it playing cards or anything else, because he doubted himself and didn’t understand how to be flexible. And these failures continued to destroy his self-confidence, forming a downward spiral. Part of the reason why he decided to practice martial arts was because he couldn’t best his sister in fights.

Going back in his memory, he remembered he had cried once after Ying Er had beaten him in middle school. Garen’s smile convulsed.

"Beaten to tears by his own sister when he was already ten years old… This is a whole new level of shame… And he secretly wept in his room... No wonder the two had a bad relationship…" Garen was suddenly regretful of possessing this body.

*********

"Shoo!"

The black-feathered arrow launched from the bow accurately pinned itself on the edge of the bullseye. Ying Er was wearing a white archery robe. She slowly lowered the bow and sighed. "My form is still not steady enough..."

"You are already doing quite well from this distance," said the girl with blue hair standing next to her. "If you can keep this up, the next Vice President of our archery club will be you."

"Thank you, senior sister!" Ying Er answered her with respect.

Each of Shengying Academy’s student organizations worked differently. Students from higher grades were allowed to partake in the academy’s administrative positions, and they were not only the head of student organizations, but also in charge of managerial decisions within the academy.

The girl in blue hair nodded. "Also, about the fight last time, I’ve taken care of it. You should try not to let that happen again. At least, don’t hurt people that badly, since it’s hard to keep these things under control."

"Thank you so much, president, I’ll try to keep it down." Ying Er apologized again; she knew that the president had great expectations and constantly took care of her. Ying Er was someone who could be persuaded by reason but not cowed by force. She had always felt guilty towards the president. She knew that if it weren’t for all her fights with the other students, she would have already been promoted to vice president of the archery club by now.

"But the fight last time was because…"

The blue-haired girl heard her response, nodded, and left to check on the other members.

Ying Er continued to practice on her own. After a few minutes, a brunette girl came by and whispered something to her.

Ying Er’s face turned red. "It doesn’t matter how useless he is, he’s still my brother! Whoever dares touch him is disrespecting me as well! Let’s go!" She put down her longbow and fiercely ran out of the archery dojo still wearing her white robe. The tomboys that were inside all followed her out, almost as if she were the Don of an all-girls mafia.

The president of the archery club saw this and shook her head helplessly. "How many times has it been… I wonder if she has a brother complex… everytime someone mentions him… Ling, go watch her and don’t let her get into trouble. She’s our best hope for the competition that’s coming up. Don’t let her beat them up too bad or she might get disqualified."

A short girl with red hair next to her nodded and jogged out without saying a word.

Other members of the club were well used to this and thus went back to practicing. A few of them shook their heads and smiled. While obedient and cute in front of her seniors, she was a violent and terrorizing figure to strangers. Ying Er’s temperament was well-known among senior members of the club.

***************

The sky was clear and blue, with only a few plumes of cloud hanging on the edge of the horizon.

Garen sat on a white rock with a handful of kabobs turning in his hands. The delicious smell of spice permeated over the fire. Some oily bubbles flopped on the golden and crispy surface of the roasted meat.

He laid the kabobs on the barbeque racks and looked at the others. They were all busy sprinkling spices over their kabobs. He stood up and strolled towards the lake, then squatted down and scooped a handful of water. He smeared the water on his face to wash off the soot from the fire.

As the cold lake water splashed on his face, his spirit lifted.

Garen looked behind them, but the girls had wandered far off. They were gathered far away on the riverbed, and were putting down some snacks and beverages over a white picnic blanket.

He exhaled deeply. "So many days have passed in the blink of an eye…" He glimpsed at the attribute pane at the bottom of his vision. Agility and Vitality were increased by 0.01 each, but this was the result of his own exercising, since his potential meter was stuck at 89%.

"Only 11% short. I’ll see if Fayne’s jewelry is effective. If not, then I must find another way… Jewelry with potential is too rare. I wonder what kind of background the black pearl the etiquette teacher brought, to be able to fill the potential meter by a whole 100%."

As the cold wind howled, Garen felt the chilliness on his back. He decided to go back near the bonfire.

"Far ahead on the river bank is the paper mill, where my uncle works. Do you guys want to go visit?" Kalidor pointed to the river by the lake.

"What’s so interesting about paper mills…" Fayne was saying something when suddenly, a scream came from afar and lingered in the air. The girls seemed to have encountered something horrific.

The boys looked over to where the girls were supposed to be having their picnic. Two of them were on the ground, slowly backing away from something. One had already run off, too scared to get close to whatever was there. Felicity was one of the girls who fell.

"Something must have happened, let’s go!" Garen was the first to react, but the others followed a second later, throwing their kabobs away as they rushed over.

Among the pebbles of the yellow riverbed, a black and purple snake held its head high, spitting its forked tongue. Two girls lay on the ground, backing away in complete terror, one of them with a bloodstained bite wound on her calf.

Chapter 6: The Establishment of a Subject

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"It’s a Panaja Snake, a highly toxic amphibious snake! We need to get the poison out right away!" Garen instantly reacted and quickly recognized this type of snake. He had not been just blindly living his new life all this time; he had already memorized most of this world’s common knowledge. On top of that, the young Garen who grew up in the countryside had previously dealt with this type of snake before.

As soon as he finished talking, he kicked a cobblestone.

Bang!

The stone landed beside the black snake. The snake immediately slithered into the stream out of fear, leaving behind only a trail of ripples as it quickly disappeared.

"How do I detoxify the venom!?" sobbed Fayne‘s cousin Enna, the only girl who had not been bitten.

"Rinse it with water, find some poplar leaves, then chew them to bits and apply them to the bites!" Garen yelled.

During this critical time, all the students were overwhelmed. This clearly contrasted the calmness Garen had as a mental adult. He directed the boys to acquire poplar leaves and asked the girls to help clean the bite wounds and squeeze out the venomous snake’s blood. Everything was dealt with rather quickly. The girls who were bitten seemed distraught, but they held it in.

Felicity stood up from the ground, groomed her messy hair, and adjusted her skirt. Looking at the well-composed Garen, she was a little surprised.

"I will remember how you helped out my friend today," she calmly said as she helped stabilize her friend with her arms.

"It’s not a big deal." Garen shrugged. With his mental age that was a few decades old, he naturally didn’t mind. "Of course, if you really want to show your appreciation, I appreciate antique jewelry. If you have any, I would love to borrow and admire them."

His gaze was softly placed on Felicity’s white neck, where a dark blue, almost black leather cord hung.

Just as he was getting closer, the Potential Meter appeared in his lower field of vision. The meter jumped by another two units, from 89% to 92%. He was certain that Felicity had a Jewel of Potential. This jewelry could be superior in quality compared to the black pearls.

"Jewelry?" Felicity softly frowned.

Fayne, who was on the other side, came over to explain, "Garen really likes jewelry from ancient times. Originally, he didn’t want to come, but I promised him that I would show him the jewelry my family passed down. If I didn’t make this promise, then this guy here would have definitely not shown up!"

"Do you want to be a jewelry appraiser or something?" Felicity asked. She thought about it for a second, then reached behind her neck with her two hands and unbuckled the dark leather cord.

Only now was everyone able to see the pendant attached to the cord. It was a diamond-shaped blue crystal the size of a fingernail. Surprisingly, inside the crystal was a tiny silver halo.

"This was an antique I bargained for a while ago. This is what you’re interested in, right?" Felicity handed the crystal to Garen.

Garen took the crystal and examined it. It did not appear to be very valuable other than the fact that it looked very antique.

"It’s very pretty…"

The moment his hand touched the crystal, however, he felt a breath of burning heat surging out of the crystal and into his fingers.

The Potential Meter in his peripheral vision was skyrocketing.

92%...98%...103%...132%...177%...181%!

The Potential Meter gradually started to slow before stopping at 181%.

Looking at the crystal in his hand, Garen felt as if something within the crystal had gradually disappeared despite the lack of any physical change. Working hard to suppress the exhilaration, he carefully handed the crystal back. "This is a really nice crystal. If possible, can I hear the backstory of this piece of jewelry?"

Felicity took the crystal, paused in surprise, and asked, "You know what it is?"

"Know what? Does this thing have some sort of story?" Those who finally finished tending the snake wounds were beginning to relax. When she saw that the two people were talking among themselves, the red-haired girl suddenly felt intrigued. She walked over and joined the conversation.

"It has a little bit of a story." Felicity nodded. "The crystal’s name is the Halo of Tragedy. Legend has it that those who wear this pendant will run into all kinds of misfortune and eventually die an unnatural death, but I do not believe in these superstitions. However, I am very interested in these types of things, so I paid a lot of money to buy it. I’ve been wearing it ever since, but there are many forgeries of this Halo of Tragedy, and I am not even certain that the one I have is real."

Garen nodded his head. Behind this crystal was actually such a widely spread background story. The two Jewels of Potential he had absorbed before also had tales of superstition behind them. This added another conjecture to his theory: only jewelry with supernatural backgrounds would have Potential.

"You sure have a lot of courage. What if the rumors are true?"

"All the previous owners have died of unnatural causes, so is it real or fake?" Two girls, revitalized from their wounds, crowded Felicity to ask more about the crystal.

Garen, having consumed the potential, walked to the stream alone and pretended to wash his hands and face.

"I have already tested my strength the last time I did this and there really was a huge change. I wonder what kind of element I will receive today?"

In his vision, the four attribute bars rose.

"Physical attributes are my weakness, but fitness, strength, and agility can easily be improved with training. Intelligence, however… I’m not sure how much it can affect me."

Pausing for a moment, he placed his gaze on the strength, intelligence, and fitness bars.

"I think that spreading out my potential points wouldn’t yield great results; it would just make me into an above average but normal person. To really create an advantage, I must specialize. Since I’ve already added points to strength, adding to it again is one way to go. But… if only I could split the points and add them…"

As soon as he had that thought, the flow of essence that was twirling inside his brain split into three different segments and entered into each of the three elements: Strength, Agility, and Intelligence.

Garen felt his body rattle as a strange numbness crazily descended from his head down to his back.

After a few seconds, his body returned to normal.

He felt like his upper body increased in strength and toughness. His mind also instantly became a bit clearer. Suddenly, he could think through and answer questions from his academic studies that had eluded him before.

He took some time to adjust, then peeked at the meters that displayed the different attributes.

Strength: 0.44, Agility: 0.23, Fitness: 0.31, Intelligence: 0.36, Potential: 81%.

Strength increased by 0.03, Fitness by 0.03, and Intelligence by 0.04.

"They increased the points evenly!" Garen paused. "What’s the use of intelligence though?" he wondered as he examined the condition of his body.

The Shengying Nobles Academy used a standard noble’s curriculum. In other words, they specialized in developing geniuses. As long as the student had one particularly strong area, they could be accepted into the Academy even if their other areas were weak. However, Garen had no plans to attend Shengying Nobles Academy. That was a path paved out for the children of power, who had no worries about food or clothing. Ordinary students tended to improve their overall performances and apply to prominent schools.

To do so, the student had to be proficient in every element.

*******************

Night time.

A little community on the south side of Huashan City, inside a red-roofed condo.

Garen sat in front of a desk in his room, his purple hair and burgundy eyes glowing dimly as he used the faint yellow lamp light to read the book in front of him.

The thin pieces of paper gently stuck onto his fingertips before turning and falling down again, soft and smooth. The book placed before him was a social history book.

Dong… Dong… Dong…

A dull clock bell faintly tolled outside the window.

Garen glanced outside. The building across from him was pitch black without a single ray of light. "Is it already midnight? Good timing, I finally just finished using the effects the potential had on my intelligence…"

A clicking noise came from his sister’s neighboring room. It was the sound of her flicking off her light.

Garen stood up and laid down on his bed. His two hands supported his head.

"My general memory abilities improved by a small amount. The time I need in order to logically assess a problem also decreased. But most importantly, my mental math speed has been greatly enhanced… I even reluctantly learned some fundamental knowledge in regards to my least favorite subject, social history. If we calculate based on the rules of this game system, I am currently only at the entry level for social history. There should still be three more stages: intermediate, advanced, and formal disciple."

As soon as he had these thoughts, the bottom of his peripheral vision flashed and a new symbol appeared flashing above the five attributes. Garen froze.

"Ah, sh*t, even this is allowed?" He jumped out of his bed and stared at the newly formed symbol without a word.

A light red symbol could clearly be seen in the bottom of his peripheral vision.

Mastery level of skill – (Social History: Elementary. Conditions required to meet goal: Intelligence level exceeds 0.34)

Garen repeatedly read this line of writing in awe for a full ten minutes before he was certain that these new symbols were real.

Similar to the other elements, it had a tiny symbol that could easily be missed if one was not paying enough attention. When he was not paying attention, these red symbols faded into a half-translucent status and did not obstruct his vision at all.

Additionally, after these new symbols appeared, Garen recalled information from the social history class. He could easily remember up to 70% of the content as if it was deeply imprinted in his brain.

"I only started studying this course today, yet I have almost achieved almost total recall of all its contents… I guess that this is the advantage of adding points to intelligence. With the differences in subject difficulty, I suppose the intelligence requirements also differ. The necessary intelligence levels also change based on the extent of subject comprehension."

Garen had no desire to sleep after that. He turned and started to gather textbooks for all the subjects.

He read through every single book, one after another.

Half an hour later…

"The condition required to establish a subject is to thoroughly finish reading a textbook. The previous Garen used one year to grasp a single subject, the study of ancient Chinese history… it’s also only at the elementary level."

Sighing deeply, Garen was speechless at his former self.

He watched the symbols in his peripheral vision.

Main subjects: (Math: not yet established), (Ancient History: elementary), (Social History: elementary), (Foreign Language: not yet established), (Physics: not yet established).

Math, ancient history, social history, foreign language, and physics were all mandatory subjects required by the school, with no exceptions. Throughout the entire country, students were required to pass these classes in order to graduate.

Garen did some calculation and comparison of his skills to his test scores.

"In the old days, for every ancient history test, Garen bounced between a score of 60 and 70 out of 100. This means that entry level is within this range. If there are no unexpected events, then my social history should also score between 60 and 70. With these kinds of marks, I would place in the bottom 10 in my class."

"For the prominent universities, according to the average Shengying annual scores, I need to place the in the top 100 to be admitted to a renowned university. To place within the top 100 in a school with a total of 1,000 students per year should not be too hard." He suddenly remembered how Garen’s parents worked overtime every day and only took one day weekends in order to provide tuition for him and his sister. They placed all their hope on the two siblings.

"To guarantee a ranking in the top 100, my average score for my classes needs to be between 70 to 80. At this rate, if I can reach an average level of Intermediate in all my mandatory courses, I can steadily gain entrance to a university. However, even if I work hard and improve, others will do the same. If the questions the students get on exams are relatively easy, then we must compete based on who is more meticulous."

Garen slowly and carefully analyzed all these issues, "If I were able to absorb more potential from the heirloom black crystal at Fayne’s place… If only I absorbed a bit more then, I would’ve been able to increase my attribute points again." He felt somewhat regretful when he remembered what happened at Jaderipple Lake.

Chapter 7: The Bronze Cross

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen stopped overthinking and began sorting things out. He took off his clothes and blew out the oil lamp. He then went onto the bed and covered himself with a blanket. In the darkness, he calmed down and fell asleep.

Dong… Dong… The morning bell kept ringing.

Bright sunlight was shining over the white bed. Garen was sleeping face up and he opened his eyes slowly. Still a bit dizzy, he took a deep breath and looked outside the window. He then slowly removed the blanket and got off the bed.

The peeling light red paint on the walls and floors revealed the pale-yellow colored lumber underneath. A silver framed painting of a wheat field was crookedly hanging on the wall. The window on the right was half-open, and the chilling wind whistled nonstop through it.

Ka-ta Ka-ta...

Amplified by the wooden floors, Garen could acutely hear Ying Er’s footsteps from the living room. He tried to clear his head by rubbing his temples several times. Garen grabbed the loose part of his oversized grey-white long sleeved pajamas, but there was not much he could do about the bagginess.

"I haven’t thought too much about it, but why am I still wearing my mother’s pajamas? It just doesn’t feel right…" Garen said as he walked towards the window and quietly closed it.

Below the right side of the window was a street in the district. Several people wearing thick coats were walking by, and one of them even had a boater hat and scarf on him. There was an empty ground behind the buildings on the left side with more cars parked in it than usual. Some of the cars were black, others were white, and the headlights of these antique cars were similar to the eyes of a goldfish.

"Cars like those look nice, but they have to be cooled down every forty miles…" Garen said as he shook his head. He sniffed several times and he could smell the mixed fragrance of fried egg and warm milk. Garen left the window, opened the door of the bedroom and walked into the living room. On the right side of the room, he saw the yellow-white window curtains billowing in the air due to the strong wind coming from outside. On the left side, Garen could see his sister, Ying Er, carefully flipping fried eggs in the kitchen.

She had changed into a short one piece with a black apron on her waist. Garen could see the white lace on the edge of her skirt and the thick tights underneath; Ying Er also wore a dark purple shawl on her back. Her burgundy pupils intently stared at the fried eggs being cooked in the pan.

"Just woke up? Go brush your teeth. Breakfast will be ready soon. I bought some fresh white bread and warm milk. Making the fried eggs right now," Ying Er said as she looked at Garen.

"They are not coming back?" Garen wiped his oily face with his hands and walked towards the washroom. He turned the tap on in front of a mirror.

Splash!

Water rushed out of the tap. Garen grabbed his red towel and soaked it in the water. He then wrung the towel and pressed it on his face.

"I told you before, right? They are on a business trip," Ying Er answered.

"Do you know where?" Garen asked.

"I think they are going to Delin City... It would take three days for them to get there by the train. Plus the time they will spend on their way back…" Ying Er answered while turning the stove off. She put the fried eggs on a plate and brought them to the table.

"They won’t be back until next week. It’s you and me again this weekend." Ying Er sat down, putting the bread, milk and fried eggs on the table.

"Let’s eat," she said.

After rinsing his mouth, Garen put his wooden toothbrush back into the glass and then turned back and left the washroom. Ying Er sat across from him. The rectangular table was made of redwood, and they both had a silver-colored metal plate in front of them. There was a triangle-shaped piece of bread in each plate, and there were some tiny characters marked on them.

Garen grabbed the silverware and cut off a small piece of the bread. It tasted a bit hard and dry, but there was a hint of sweetness.

"It’s Saturday. You got any plans for today?" Ying Er drank some milk and asked.

"Yeah… I want to go to the new antique store in the southern part of the city. It opened on the old Pennington Street," Garen said while eating the fried egg.

"It’s pretty far from here… We are on Bluetree Street and need to pass through downtown. Then, we need to walk another half an hour. It’s like walking from one side of the town to the other. Why are you interested in the new antique store?" Ying Er was confused.

"If it’s not important, can you go to the fruit market with me? I also want to check out the pet shops on a street beside the market. You can carry the bags for me," Ying Er said as she took a subtle glance at Garen; she seemed to be looking forward to spending time with him.

"I want some white pears, my favorite fruit," she added.

"White pears?" Garen stopped for a second; the old Garen used to love white pears too.

"Sorry, I really need to check out the new antique shop. It’s important," Garen said.

"Fine…" Ying Er nodded and stopped talking. She decided to focus on the food.

"It’s fall now, make sure you wear enough clothes. Don’t catch a cold," Garen reminded as he put the rest of the food into his mouth. He gulped it down with a few sips of milk.

"I’m leaving." Garen stood up and went back to the bedroom to change.

Ying Er listlessly sat by the table as she watched him leave. She kept stabbing the bread pieces in her plate with the fork.

Garen changed from his pajamas to a thick black coat and dark blue pants with a black and white scarf around his neck. He looked like a handsome teenager and was no longer thin and weak. However, his gaze looked deep, and his eyes looked like two pure gems with a sparkle of burgundy in the middle. Now, he looked totally different and more mature with the changes to his eyes.

"When will you be back? How long do you plan to stay in the shop?" Ying Er raised her head up and asked.

"I will be back before dinner. I have to go now," Garen said as he tidied his scarf. He walked to the door and put on his black leather boots.

He opened the door, walked out and saw that his neighbor’s door was open. A middle-aged man with glasses turned back and looked at him for a second, but did not say anything. The man was holding a black bag in his hand and closed his door without greeting Garen. Garen knew this neighbor; the tenant, Boris, was the middle-aged man Garen had just met. He never saw the man’s wife, but he knew that the man lived with a 7 or 8 years old boy. Garen barely talked to them and they never greeted him if they saw him around. Garen had only talked to them once since his family had moved here. He introduced himself and greeted them, but they did not have any further conversation. Garen’s family was irked by how impolite the man and his son were.

Garen carefully closed the metal door, then he rubbed his hands together for warmth. He walked down the stairs and followed the path towards the left, entering a grey road lit by black street lights.

Outside the district, the streets were between yellow buildings and had black railings protecting pedestrians on the sides. An antique car was driving along the road, and Garen could see the white smoke coming out of the exhaust. There was an ox cart full of fruits following behind the car, and the coachman whipped the ox while yelling from time to time.

While glancing at the yellow buildings beside him, Garen walked by the railings; each of these buildings was around 7 floors tall and some had their windows open. Others closed their windows tight and put barbed wire on them. The edges of the buildings were round rather than sharp right angles.

A chilling autumn wind blew through Garen’s hair. He lowered his head and felt his skin numbed by the cold. There were young trees planted next to the railings, however, they were bereft of leaves. As such, Garen could only see the dark, bold branches.

After walking for about twenty minutes, he started to see more people and cars on the street. He walk passed a bronze sign labeled ‘Garden Street’.

Garen turned left at a crossroads, and instead of yellow, the buildings became grey and white with complex designs. These buildings looked luxurious, and there were tall round poles around them. There were also some beautiful sculptures by the buildings, and the black street lamps were decorated with white ornaments on top.

The sidewalk was almost empty. There was a woman wearing a thick white dress walking her dog, and there were also two old men holding canes sitting on a black metal bench talking in hushed voices.

Garen tightened his scarf and looked over the building on his left. Garen’s uncle lived on the fifth floor of that building; this uncle of his was the one who helped him and Ying Er get into the Shengying Nobles Academy.

Garen’s uncle started his business from nothing and worked very hard to build up his reputation. He was one of the richest merchants in Huaishan City, and he treated Garen very well. However, he did not care about girls, so he barely talked to Ying Er.

"I should visit my uncle on my way back…" Garen thought as he walked faster towards the end of the street. He passed a bronze road sign standing beside the sidewalk that read ‘Pennington Street’. There was a small store at the corner by the end of the street. The arched door of the shop was wide open, and there was yellow light coming out of it. A bespectacled old man was sitting by the yellow shelves, carefully looking at the object in his hand with a magnifier.

Garen glanced at the top right corner, towards a triangle sign hanging on the white wall. It read ‘Dolphin Antiques’. Garen walked into the shop and looked around the place. There were more than ten tables in the shop, and there were red fabrics strewn all over the tables and walls, but he was the only customer. Many strange items were put on the tables.

After entering the shop, Garen stepped on the dark yellow floor and was startled by the ‘person’ to his right. He looked over and saw an incomplete body sculpture of a kid with curly hair; it only had the head and the shoulders. There was a cuboid stone pole supporting the sculpture from below.

"What do you need?" asked the old man, who put down his magnifier when he saw Garen enter. The old man’s skin was gray and yellow, while his wrinkled face was full of black freckles.

"Let me see…" Garen panicked for a second, trying to think of a reason for being there…

"Don’t mind me, I am just looking around," he answered after calming down.

Chapter 8: Special Ability Enhancements

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The old man brushed his fingers through his sparse hair. "Look around by yourself. Items on the left side of my shop are personally acquired from the countryside. On the right are heirlooms that have been passed down for generations." He bowed his head and started to examine the tiny object in his hand again.

The old man wore white gloves and held a soft gold pocket-watch. The back of the watch was open and he seemed to be studying the gears and mechanics of the watch itself.

Garen first glanced around the entire shop and then began to browse in detail from left to right.

A long rectangular oil painting hung on the far left wall and depicted a white castle under siege. There were a handful of armored warriors who were pushing towards the castle bearing a red banner. The catapults were constantly flinging giant rocks as oil spilled down the castle walls. Bloody corpses were everywhere.

Below the oil painting was a circular dark gold metal sheet. It was half a meter wide and a smiling human face bulged out in the center.

"What is this?" Garen touched the metal sheet. The material was hard and the surface had a rough texture similar to copper paper.

The old man standing under the bookshelf looked up. "This is the Totem of the Sun God owned by the Crimson tribe from 300 years ago. It’s a very valuable object. Every time the tribe plundered new gold, the wizard of the tribe would paint the metal disc with molten gold. Other than the human face in the middle, everywhere else has been painted over countless times with gold and brass. If you are interested, I can sell it to you for cheap at $35,000." The old man took off his glasses and rubbed the lenses with a soft cloth as he continued, "Not a lot of people know the value of these objects anymore. A few decades ago, when antiques were the trend, I could have sold that for hundreds of thousands."

"Totem of the Sun God…" The corner of Garen’s lips twitched. He knew without looking that this was fake. Not only did the lack of response from his special ability signal this, there was also the fact that if the totem really was worth that much and was really made out of gold, then there was no way it would be displayed here waiting to be sold. If it was actually a huge piece of gold plated metal, any jeweler would be willing to buy it for $100,000. Although the shop owner even gave him a "deal" for $35,000… the total amount of cash he had on hand was only $20.

On his left, he saw a tall redwood table. On top was a burgundy emblem, a transparent wine bottle, and a silver cup.

Garen gently touched each of the three items. When he touched the burgundy emblem, the Potential Meter at the bottom of his vision jumped.

"Hmm?! There’s something up with this!" He quietly turned his body until his back was facing the old man. The skin on his face tensed.

He picked up the burgundy emblem and inspected it carefully.

The emblem was in the shape of a cross. The cross was burgundy with gold laurels wrapped around its edges. Garen found that in the dead center of the cross, there was a tiny patch of black paint the size and shape of a fingernail with the letter P carved on it.

He could feel the powerful concentrated cold qi inside the emblem. Compared to the black pearl and Felicity’s Halo of Tragedy, this one felt many times more powerful. For some reason, however, he could not entirely absorb this energy from the emblem. There was only a thin thread of energy between the emblem and him, with Potential being slowly squeezed out like toothpaste.

"Before, I could easily and instantly absorb all the potential from the objects I found. How come this time it’s going so slowly? At this rate, if I want to fully consume this energy, I would have to stay here for days." A trace of excitement and disbelief flashed across Garen’s eyes.

"That’s $6,000," the bespectacled old man said in a deadpan voice while standing to Garen’s right side.

"$6,000…" Garen frowned.

The old man was wearing all black. Looking at the emblem, he said in a low tone, "I acquired this Bronze Cross Emblem from a veteran family. You sure have good eyes for picking this one out. Out of all the stuff I acquired, this emblem is the most exquisite. It came from the Republic of Mengdiya over 150 years ago. At that time, the Republic of Mengdiya was so powerful that all other countries lived in fear of it. They were able to establish hundreds of colonies throughout the world and half of the land now occupied by the Yalu Confederation was also colonized by them. This emblem was one of the products left from that period of time. I believe it was a reward given to a level two military commander."

"I’ll look around a bit more… I’m not in a rush." Garen wanted to suppress his desire to purchase it. He knew that if he could absorb all the potential out of the emblem, then he would be able to add more than two points to his Abilities. Unfortunately, he had no money…

The weekly allowance he received was only $20. The difference between that amount and $6,000 was astronomical.

The old man noticed how reluctant Garen was about giving it up. "I had a soldier coming in last time who wanted to buy it off me, but he didn’t bring enough cash. If you really want it kid, take this opportunity and get it before he comes back."

Garen’s face twitched. "I‘ll look at some other stuff first."

"Alright, up to you." The old man smiled like a blooming chrysanthemum.

Garen peeked at the old man. "This guy… he obviously noticed that I wanted to buy it and so made up a story to push me over the edge. However, I should be careful. Perhaps there really is someone who has their eye on this. But no rush, if I’m lucky, I can find something else in this shop and absorb potential from it as well."

He became more determined and began to browse through everything from the tables to walls. Very soon, he had touched every single item in the shop.

Sadly, the remaining items were regular objects and only the emblem had potential.

After a while, he again returned to the round table and picked up the cross-shaped burgundy emblem. He examined it for more than half an hour.

"I don’t have enough money on me at the moment. Do you think you can reserve it for me for now? I will return to buy it later." Garen raised his head and looked in the old man’s direction.

The old man had long since returned to the bookshelf. He was wiping the dust off his antiques with a soft white cloth. When he heard Garen’s request, he turned his head with a grin. "Of course I can. However, I cannot reserve it for long. The story I told you may seem like a sales tactic, but someone really does want to buy it. There are only three weeks left until he comes back."

"Three weeks…" Garen frowned, "Alright. I will try my best to get the money. What’s the lowest price you can give me?"

"Since you are a student, I will discount the price and only ask for $5000. That is the lowest and final offer," the old man said as he adjusted his glasses.

"I will not bargain with you now, but we will talk about it later." Garen didn’t say anything more. He gave the emblem a final glance and placed it back on the table. Then, he walked before the old man. "My name is Garen. May I ask what your name is?"

"Call me Old Man Gregor. What do you want to ask? I warn you though, I don’t answer sensitive questions for free."

"I wanted to ask where you purchased this emblem from?" Garen asked with a frown.

The old man recollected his memories, "I can tell you the answer, but…" He extended his arm with a smile.

Garen watched speechlessly as the old man opened his hand. He took out a $10 bill and put it in the skinny chicken-like hand.

"Cheap…" the old man muttered as he took the money. "I got it from an old abandoned castle in a town more than 60 miles away from Huaishan City. The original owner of the castle was a viscount, but his successive generations were feeble. Nowadays, the highest title in the family is knight. Nobody has been able to maintain the castle for years. As a result, everything in the castle has been bought and sold – it’s practically empty now. If the castle was in a better condition and a better location, it would’ve been bought off a long time ago. The castle’s name… I think it was called Silversilk Castle."

"Silversilk Castle… can you draw me a detailed map of how to get there?"

The old man again extended his open palm with a grin on his face.

"What the eff!" Garen cursed uncontrollably. He took another $10 bill out of his pocket and stuffed it into the old man’s palm. "Can you please hurry!"

"Of course!" The old man accepted the bill and quickly took out a thin yellow paper from a drawer. He picked up an ink-soaked quill and drew out a simple map.

Garen scanned the map after receiving it, "Thanks for taking the time. Please wait for me."

Before the old man could respond, Garen rolled up the paper and marched out of the antique shop.

After walking on the sidewalk for a while, he reached out and touched his empty pocket. He wanted to cry, but he had no tears. "Even if I don’t buy the emblem and only travel to the castle, it would still cost me $50 to $60… this means I need to save my allowance from this week and next week."

As he walked, his brain looked for ways he could get his hands on $5,000. He had a faint feeling that the emblem was covered by something, causing him to be unable to truly get in contact with it and absorb all of its potential. If he wanted all the potential, he would have to scrape off whatever was covering it and reveal the actual object. The issue was that he could not afford it and therefore could not damage it by scraping.

Looking at the light red numbers in his lower field of view, the Potential Meter had broken through to 101%. A cold wave of air lingered around his brain. now, he could add points to any attribute at any time.

"There is no rush. I stood there for so long, yet I absorbed such little potential. If I want to absorb substantial potential from the emblem, I would need to stand there for days. There is no way Old Man Gregor would allow that." Garen recalculated the estimated total potential from the emblem and felt a flame burning in his chest when he realized that there should be at least five points.

"I can try to try to get money and come here every day to absorb its potential. Small portions will eventually add up. There is no way I can’t finish consuming its potential!" He silently decided.

Walking to the entrance of Pennington street again, Garen raised his head and looked over at his uncle’s house.

Coincidentally, the arched window was wide open. A chubby middle-aged man was standing beside the window and was looking down. "Garen is that you?" The man had a very common face with very thick black eyebrows and gave off a tough vibe. "I haven’t seen you in so long. Hurry, come up!"

Garen didn’t expect to actually see his uncle. He merely nodded, walked around the stone column, and entered the half-open wooden corridor entrance.

The corridor led to a spacious lounge. The floor was covered with black carpet and a white stone statue of an angel was placed in the center. The wings of the angel were spread wide, as if ready to fly.

Garen entered from the left side stairs, jogged past a few people, and quickly reached a red metal door on the left side of the fifth floor.

Dong, dong, dong.

He reached out to open the door.

Immediately, the door creaked open. Uncle Tyr was standing in front of the door wearing a white dress shirt and black dress pants. "Hurry in! The fireplace is lit."

"Okay." Garen passed the door, changed into slippers, and walked into the room with his uncle.

The room was covered with light yellow wallpaper and there were oil paintings after oil paintings on the walls. Most of the paintings were not of Uncle Tyr, but were of his wife, Windsor.

After a few minutes, Garen stood by the window, listening to his uncle talk about recent local news with a bearded guest.

In the middle of their heated conversation, Uncle Tyr suddenly fixed his gaze onto Garen.

"Garen, if you want to make a difference in the future, you must remember one thing: read lots, explore lots, and think lots. The fundamental principle is to speak less, but act more." Uncle Tyr removed his cigar and gently flicked it into the ashtray. "You are in high school now, you will be going to university in the future, and then you will start your career. Whether it’s about your academic career or your professional career, it’s good to remember this piece of advice."

"Also, hang out with Lombarth and Phelia more often. You are all around the same age and will be cousins for life. These days, they are always playing some chess war game. They don’t do useful stuff anymore. You should talk some sense into them."

Uncle Tyr had been managing his own business for a long time. There were very complex relationships between the legal and illegal means. Even though he appeared to be an ordinary businessman, he actually had a lot of interests in other aspects and even had a gun permit.

Garen looked down and nodded continuously. He knew that even though his uncle looked very kind, in his bones he was someone stubborn and paranoid. He hated others disagreeing with his plans since he had a very strong sense of individualism.

The bearded man laughed as well. "This is your nephew? Nowadays, young people have such valuable resources. Thinking back to our days, we did not grow up in such a nice environment."

"Exactly, the environment is so good they have forgotten how to treasure it," Uncle Tyr laughed helplessly and returned to discussing business news with the bearded guest.

Garen stood to the side and listened to the two adults having their discussion. Internally, he was looking for ways to acquire that $5,000. Usually when he visited his uncle, he would receive allowances ranging from a high of a few hundred dollars to a low of $80 to $90. The distance to $5,000 was still too far.

Garen had no plans to ask for money from his uncle anyways. If he did, this would be his first time asking and he might need his uncle’s help for a second or third time after today. While it might be possible the for Garen to get some money from his uncle the first time, if Garen did this multiple times then his uncle would stop accommodating him regardless how much his uncle liked him.

"I have to find a way myself..." Garen thought of the Dojo. "If I can successfully gain entrance to White Cloud Dojo, then every month I can get a small monetary reward. Usually it’s $2,000. This is one source of income. Additionally, the school offers lots of scholarships for a total of ten grand. There are two more months till the end of the semester, but there is no way I can get the scholarship with my current level of learning unless I can get ability enhancements. Other than for ancient civilization and history, I have yet to achieve the minimum level of the intelligence requirement. I can only memorize and understand everything after achieving this minimal requirement. Otherwise, I have to follow the normal rules and slowly study."

Suddenly, a thought flashed across Garen’s brain, "There are archery and swordsmanship competitions! Out of the two, Ying Er will participate in one. Top three are awarded and even the third place wins $10,000, but I’m not sure how good Garen is at archery and swordsmanship?"

As soon as he thought of this question, he saw that the symbols were slowly changing at the bottom of his vision. Soon, it changed into three elements: Swordsmanship, Archery, and Basic Boxing.

Swordsmanship: Elementary. Archery: Elementary. Basic Boxing: Elementary.

"I wonder if I can add points to these abilities…" Garen speculated.

He tried to concentrate on the swordsmanship element. Inside his brain, waves of air were pouncing around, waiting to spew forth.

"It’s possible!!" He immediately stopped the flow of air, shifted his focus, and repressed the excitement he was feeling.

Chapter 9: Change

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen calmed down and stood there listening to the conversation between the two. It was almost noon and was getting brighter outside.

Uncle Tyr finally stood up and saw the customer to the door.

"Uncle, I have to go now," Garen said while taking his scarf off the clothing stand.

"It’s still very early. You can leave after lunch if you want," Tyr said, turning back to Garen.

"You rarely come to visit and Lombarth will be back shortly. You could have a chat with him," he continued.

"Maybe next time. Ying Er is waiting for me at home." Garen smiled.

"I promised her that I will be back for lunch," he added.

"Fine… Stay safe." Tyr chuckled. He patted Garen’s head several times.

"I will," Garen said.

Garen put on his shoes and was about to leave. Suddenly, some warm paper was shoved into his right palm. It was a stack of hundred dollar bills. Garen turned back and saw his smiling uncle.

"Take it. I haven’t seen you in a long time. It’s just some pocket money. Make sure you work hard in school," Tyr said.

"I will. Thank you, Uncle. Goodbye." Garen smiled and bowed in gratefulness.

"Come and visit me more often whenever you are free," Tyr said.

"I will."

Garen said goodbye and walked down the stairs. He went back to the first floor, where he saw a blond boy wearing a tight white suit standing in the middle of the hall as a torrent of people walked past him. The boy was by a sculpture of a white angel. He saw Garen coming down the stairs and raised his eyebrows.

"Garen, get over here." The boy waved one of his hands while holding a white ball in the other. He dribbled it as he chatted with a black-haired girl who was next to him.

Garen knew the boy. It was his cousin, Lombarth, the son of Tyr. He never liked Lombarth and hated his cousin’s self-centered and arrogant personality. Garen scowled and walked toward Lombarth, stopping when he stood about two meters away.

"What did my dad say to you?" Lombarth leaned toward Garen and asked with a light tone.

"Nothing special. He asked me how I was doing recently. I have to go if you have nothing important to say," Garen answered softly.

"Why are you nervous? I am your elder. Could it be that my words are annoying you?" Lombarth raised his eyebrows again and looked at the girl beside him. He felt like he was challenged by his younger cousin.

"I am leaving if you really have nothing else to say. It is lunchtime and Ying Er is waiting for me at home." Garen did not want to waste his time on Lombarth, so he walked toward the exit. He felt a bit speechless.

"Hey! I am your elder! Stop right there!" Lombarth yelled angrily.

"Lombarth, do you really want to do this?! You don’t want to mess with me!" Garen turned back and frowned as he raised his voice. Although the old Garen was weak, the new Garen would not back down from a situation like this.

"Ha… How dare you speak to me like that? I will teach you what respect is!" Lombarth suddenly tried to slap Garen’s face. He applied martial force to his palm. The strength of the slap was doubled with the use of his combat techniques.

Lombarth, with a roar, motioned toward the left side of Garen’s face.

*Pa*

Garen used his palm to block the attack, their palms colliding with each other in mid air. Their strength level was similar, neither had an advantage during the exchange.

Garen was a bit surprised that his playboy cousin knew any martial arts, but he himself had already reached the first level of professional martial artistry. He applied more force into his palm and angrily pushed it toward Lombarth.

Unable to handle this counterattack, Lombarth took the hit and toppled sideways. He crashed into a middle-aged man beside him and he flushed in embarrassment. Lombarth looked at his right hand, which was already swelling.

It hand burned with a fiery pain and he could no longer raise it.

"Good… Garen… You are pretty good!" Lombarth said and looked at the girl beside him again.

"You just wait, I’ll make you pay for this!" he yelled.

Garen decided not to waste any more time. He knew that although Lombarth probably learned some martial arts growing up, that there was no way Lombarth could fight him. Garen had bitterly trained himself with incredible fervor. Even if Lombarth wanted to send someone else to beat Garen up, Tyr would never allow such a thing to happen.

"Save yourself some time. I can’t imagine how disappointed my uncle will be if he sees you fight like this," Garen said as he exited the hallway through a small wooden door. From behind, he could still hear Lombarth crazily yelling curses at him.

Garen returned to the district by the way he came. There were more people on the main road than before and he spent about half an hour getting back to Bluetree Street.

He entered the district; the fourth building on the right with a red roof was his home. There was an old gentleman walking down the stairs slowly with a cane in his hand. The stairs were narrow, so Garen stood to the side and waited for the gentleman to exit the building.

The gentleman gave him a friendly smile, but did not say anything. He walked straight toward the parking lot on the right. Though the gentleman needed to support himself with the cane, he was walking carefully at his own pace. His crisp black suit gave him a solemn aura as he walked away.

Garen withdrew his gaze and stepped onto the stairs. He went up the dim stairway and heard footsteps from above, and he peaked through a gap in the stairway. He saw Ying Er walking upstairs slowly, it seemed she was carrying something very heavy.

"Ying Er!" he yelled.

"Garen? You’re back? Come help me. I bought a bunch of white pears." Ying Er heard the voice, put the groceries down onto the ground, and peeked through the stairway back at Garen. She was still wearing her black dress, the hem of her skirt barely covering her thighs.

"Coming." Garen started to move, but from his angle, he could see something white through the black tights under Ying Er’s skirt. He started to blush.

"You fool, stop acting like Lombarth!" Ying Er realized where he was staring at and started to blush as well. She immediately closed her legs tightly.

"You should’ve been careful in the first place!" Garen tried to explain and ran toward her. He held the wooden yellow basket above his chest, holding about 20 fist-sized white pears in it.

"Am I not being careful?!" Ying Er yelled with arms akimbo.

"Let’s talk after we get back home!" She realized she was being too loud and looked around to make sure that no one else was there.

Garen shrugged his shoulders and stepped up the stairs again. Ying Er opened the door with her keys and they quickly entered their home. Garen put the basket down from his hands and ran away after changing his shoes.

*BANG*

Ying Er slammed the door closed, and raised her fists while still blushing.

"You are dead, Garen!" she yelled and rushed toward Garen. She was faster than Garen, even after his hard training

Ying Er started to chase Garen in the living room. After about ten seconds, Garen was tripped by Ying Er and fell down hard to the floor

‘She knows intermediate level martial arts… and it’s even trained using some Secret Art.’ Garen thought while staring speechlessly at Ying Er. Even though he did not use any martial arts and wasn’t being serious, he could still tell how strong his sister was just by watching her moves. Ying Er’s martial arts were more about speed and dexterity, while the White Cloud Dojo’s arts were more about bursts of strength. Ying Er had probably already reached the intermediate level.

Different dojos had different focuses when developing their basic martial arts. Some focused more on strength, some focused more on bursts of damage, some on agility, and some had buffs to stamina, dodging skill, or innate resistances. Their basic martial arts had different names, but were just used for common fights, unlike Secret Arts.

Secret training arts referred to special ways of exercising the body, and different dojos usually developed different versions. For example, the basic martial arts from White Cloud Dojo was not its secret arts, it was just a strength burst technique. Compared to basic martial arts, secret training arts would only be passed down to the true disciples. If these disciples kept exercising their bodies with the secret training arts, most of their attributes, such as strength, burst, agility, resistance, and flexibility, would be constantly increasing.

Garen heard that the disciples of White Cloud Dojo showed their strength during various competitions and that their secret training arts were probably developed to increase their strength. Ying Er’s speed was ridiculously fast, she had probably used some sort of special training arts to attain this level of speed.

Garen stopped musing and turned his head to the side. From his previous angle, he could again clearly see what was under his sister’s skirt. Garen could see Ying Er’s long, slim legs through her sheer black tights.

"Of all the people to take after, why do you decide to be so much like Lombarth!" Ying Er was breathing heavily as she kicked Garen in the chest. Garen’s coat was thick, so Ying Er was not worried about him getting too hurt.

Garen blinked his eyes and suddenly fiercely pulled at her feet with his hands.

*PONG*

Ying Er fell on his body and they both groaned in pain.

Garen could smell the girl’s fragrance and her soft breast pushed at the area above his chest. Garen somehow felt a little excited.

"Come on!" Garen stood up while rubbing his stomach.

"What are we having for the lunch?" he asked.

Ying Er was not paying attention to Garen’s movement and accidentally fell on his chest. She was going to blame Garen, but she started to blush again after realizing she was right above his chest. Garen was much stronger than before and she could feel his chest muscles. Unlike the last time he was tripped by his sister, Garen acted like he did not care instead of getting angry. Ying Er felt surprised after hearing Garen ask her about lunch and she hesitated for a second before standing up.

"I made sweet bean cake, onion pancakes, and coconut with sweet melon soup," Ying Er answered as she brushed some dust off her dress.

Chapter 10: No title

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen gradually noticed the change in his sister. His adult consciousness allowed him to sense that Ying Er treated him slightly different; she seemed to take his every word very seriously. She was very careful with her actions when they were playing tag earlier, using only a very slight amount of force, as if she was worried that she might hurt him. That was how he managed to sneak an attack on her and take her down in the end.

"Have some lunch first. Making breakfast and lunch, going out to buy fruits, it's been a tough day for you, Ying Er." He reached out a hand to pinch his sister's cheek. There seemed to be much less acne and freckles on her red face recently; it felt soft and smooth to the touch.

"Ugh, you!" Ying Er slapped away Garen's hand. "Did you take the wrong medicine? Since when did you know how to show concern towards someone else?" She quizzically looked at Garen. Although she usually tried very hard to pretend as if she wasn't close with her brother, in fact, she was constantly concerned about everything related to Garen in secret.

Garen's heart skipped a beat. He realized that he had gone slightly overboard with his change in character; he immediately retracted his hand without saying another word. "Can't I have grown up? Do you have to act all shocked? Come on, let's eat."

After a rushed meal, the brother and sister duo worked together to wash the dishes, then quickly went back to their respective bedrooms, both seeming slightly off. Ying Er kept feeling as if there was a gust of wind under her skirt ever since she was accidentally exposed, and she constantly felt uneasy in front of Garen. They were step-siblings after all; a relationship built through the fusion of two single-parent families was not considered to be blood-relations.

Garen, on the other hand, was rushing back to his room to further ponder about Attribute Enhancements.

Standing by the window, he quietly stared at the pale red Attribute data in the lower part of his field of vision.

"If skills can indeed be enhanced, I will be able to participate in the tournament within a short period of time and win the large prize pool if I enhance my archery or sword skills. My only worry is that it would stick out like a sore thumb if a student that seldom practices suddenly participates and wins the award. Putting aside what others might think, Ying Er knows my situation well. She is aware that I don't usually practice my archery or sword skills." He rested his hand against the glass window pane.

"If that's the case, this idea with archery and sword skills won't work. But what about the White Cloud Dojo? I've always been attentive to the Dojo's training. If I dove into the tournament, people would assume I have steadily accumulated the skills through observation, and it would attract less attention. Moreover, the Dojo isn't the Academy; it's an independent party. It wouldn't attract much attention even if something unusual or exceptional happened there. It's just that the prize money is a little on the low side… I could approach the Dojo and inquire whether there are any inter-dojo tournaments. Those offer much more prize money than internal tournaments! Now that's an idea!"

He lightly grazed his hand over the surface of the glass; it was smooth and cool to touch. "If that's the case, I'll pay a visit to the Dojo this afternoon and ask a trainer about the general situation."

After resting in his room for a bit, Garen quietly walked out. When he walked past his sister's room, he saw Ying Er lying on the bed, cheeks rosy and sleeping soundly, and decided not to bother her.

He gently put on his scarf and coat, then changed his shoes and walked out the door. Walking out of his cul-de-sac and grasping the 300 dollars from his uncle in his pocket, Garen hailed a black carriage and stepped into it.

"To the White Cloud Dojo."

"It's ten dollars yeah?" the driver turned around to confirm.

"Yup, just go." Garen nodded in consent.

Sitting in the carriage and looking out the right window, he could see buildings with pale yellow walls swiftly pass by one after another. A few minutes later, after turning a corner, the streets gradually became deserted. The previous scene was replaced by solemn, gray buildings. Shops with round arch doorways formed a row, all of them selling clocks and sundries.

Garen looked closely at the Skills section in his field of vision.

Fighting skills: Amateur. Archery skills: Amateur. Sword skills: Amateur.

"If I can pass the assessment and train in the Secret Arts of White Cloud Dojo, I can enhance my physical quality. Couple that with my Attribute points to concurrently increase my power, the effect of my training would be exponential compared to that of my peers!" His wine-red eyes narrowed slightly, indicating a trace of anticipation.

"If I keep using Attribute points to enhance a single skill, I wonder what the maximum level of increase would it reach. It's been said that different people have different talents, leading to great disparities in the effect of training in the Secret Arts. This could help conceal the fact that I'm enhancing my skills with Attribute points. This way, even if the level of the training method is slightly inferior, it would still be able to match up to top-level training methods. Now, my only hope is that Attribute points can enhance training methods like they enhance personal qualities.

Recalling whom he could inquire with at the Dojo, Garen could only come up with three people: Sharmilla, Luo Ya, and the girl with short and silver hair that he trained with.

There was one that left a deep impression though: the best in their batch, Erwin. He would always achieve high rankings with overwhelming skills. In addition to that, he had a mild attitude, was very humble and was well-brought-up. If there was someone with a hundred percent chance of being a Formal Disciple of White Cloud Dojo, it would be Erwin.

"I could go to Erwin. This guy would definitely be training in the Dojo even if it's the weekend, no exceptions. Moreover, he would definitely be clear about these things," Garen thought. He has heard of grand inter-dojo tournaments where the crème de la crème of Galantia Province - in which Huaishan City is located - were chosen, and were presented awards and medals by officials. "This tournament is a great way for dojos to avoid vicious competition, exhibit their talent pool and solidify their social status. The annual grand prize is almost never below 100,000 dollars, and the winner will qualify for the national tournament."

While Garen was busy sorting through what he knew, the carriage gradually slowed down to a stop.

"Sir, the White Cloud Dojo," the driver's words interrupted Garen's train of thought.

"Yes, very well." He dug some notes from his pocket and handed it to the driver. Once he received his change, Garen immediately leapt off the carriage.

The streets were narrow, giving a messy and complicated impression.

The ground was paved with gray and black pebbles, which made it uncomfortable to step on. The heights of the buildings on both sides of the street were varied; there were red ones, gray ones, and pale yellow ones. There was a variety of patterns too: squares, triangles, plaid, wavy arcs, etc. It all looked a mess. Ten odd steps from Garen, a khaki-yellow bell tower stood in the middle of the street; at its base, a round and arched doorway allowed pedestrians through.

A smattering of pedestrians continuously went in and out from the doorway.

There was a white wooden board on the left side of the doorway displaying a paper notice. Two people were standing there reading it.

Garen walked over to the notice and checked it out.

"White Cloud Dojo Notice on Recruitment over the Holidays: Under-18 applicants with a student card can enjoy half-off student fees. The specific adult fees schedule is as follows: …"

One of the people reading the notice was a freckled teenage boy who frowned after he read it. "Let's go, Jim. Martial arts training is too exhausting, and it's not as if it would serve any purpose. No matter what arts you train in, a shot from a pistol would still take you down in an instant."

The other boy shook his head and both walked past the board through the doorway, leaving Garen standing there alone.

To the right of the notice was the façade of a building with a grayish-white steeple. Mahogany strips were affixed to its main entrance like a spider web. The mahogany door at the entrance was wide open, displaying the deserted scene beyond: a lone student wearing khaki-yellow robes was sweeping inside.

Garen browsed the contents of the notice, then immediately walked towards the entrance to the right.

The student who was sweeping looked up at him, but kept silent.

Garen went through the main entrance, the middle hall, past the khaki-colored courtyard, and headed directly towards the innermost row of short buildings.

The row of short buildings at the edge of the courtyard formed a straight, dark gray line. Garen walked towards the entrance of the leftmost house. The sound of people hitting sandbags came from inside the room.

He gently opened the door. It was quite dark and empty inside, with only four black sandbags hanging on the wall at the far end. Two guys and a girl were each hitting a sandbag at a fast pace, and there were three students by the side holding towels and the like for them.

An endless stream of thumps could be heard.

Garen's entrance went almost unnoticed. One of the students holding a white towel turned around to look at him, and then proceeded to ignore him. This was the gym where any student could train in, but with relatively high specifications. The sandbags here were extremely heavy, only suitable for Formal Disciples to train with. If normal disciples tried to train with these sandbags, they would probably hurt themselves.

Garen's sight swiftly fell on the leftmost boy.

The boy's upper body was bare, and the bronze muscles on it were distinct. Sweat poured down his back and drenched his gray shorts. He was completely focused on the sandbag in front of him, punching it at a moderate pace, only causing it to tremble slightly at every punch.

Garen walked over and waited patiently by the side.

More than ten minutes later, the boy stopped. He wiped the sweat off his face and combed his short, pale yellow hair - completely drenched in sweat - backward. He yanked a black towel off the rack to the side and started wiping his sweat.

"Senior Brother Erwin, I'm Garen, one of the students in your batch. Can I ask you something?" Garen took the opportunity to step forward and said aloud. The room was filled with punching sounds; he wouldn't be heard if he didn't speak up.

"Garen? Oh… I know you." Erwin put down the towel and gave a kind smile. "Just ask anything you want. We're batchmates, no need to stand on ceremony."

"I'd like to inquire about the student tournaments."

Ten minutes later…

Garen came out of the room with a good general understanding of the tournaments. One had to first participate in the dojo's internal tournament and get a good ranking in order to participate in the tournament jointly organized by two neighboring cities. The winners would then be selected for the provincial tournament, which would eventually lead to the national tournament; the multiple stages formed a ladder-like hierarchy. Additionally, only the internal and inter-city tournaments would be held within a span of three weeks from start to finish; the rest would be held in the next year or in the year after that.

"But it's good enough if I can get my hands on some prize money. The first prize for the city tournament this time around is 10,000 dollars, 5,000 for the second and 2,000 for the third. I'll be able to resolve this money issue as long as I get second place."

Chapter 11: Secret Method 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After leaving the judo, Garen was waiting for a carriage in front of the entrance.

"Mister, would you like a newspaper?" A young boy wearing a gray cap walked over with a stack of newspapers in his arms and held out a newspaper to Garen.

"Newspaper?" Garen thought for a while, grabbed the newspaper, and handed over a dollar from his pocket.

"Thanks." The boy left to continue looking for the next customer.

Garen shook the grayish-white newspaper and spread it open. An enormous black headline suddenly appeared in his sight.

"Tensions between Weisman Empire and Republic of the Tulip increasingly apparent!! The stance of the Confederation will become important."

He frowned and continued to look at the other headlines.

"The Chairman of the Confederation will conduct an ordnance inspection of the armed forces on the 19th at nine in the morning."

"Shocking massacre in the Western Alliance, owner of a manor and 42 other people murdered."

"Fascinating archaeological discoveries of historical remains found in Stonecliff Continent."

Rustling the newspaper, Garen was just about turn to the next page when a pedestrian bumped into him. A page of the newspaper fell out, revealing a black and white photo.

It was a dark wheat field with a slanted scarecrow alone in the middle, surrounded by a sea of black wheat.

There was a caption below the photo.

"Shocking discovery of a purple wheatfield in the Southwest Province."

Garen carefully looked at the photo; very subtly, he actually felt a trace of movement from his supernatural ability.

He scanned through the content below, and the name of a location appeared in his eyes.

"Mason Farm"

The sound of a carriage approached from a distance, and Garen quickly rolled up the newspaper and raised his hand to hail it.

The grayish-black carriage slowly stopped in front of him.

"Go to Bluetree Street."

"Yes, sir."

****************

"After the Border War 15 years ago, the world has reverted back to a peaceful state. As one of the superpowers of the three continents, it is our historical duty to maintain world peace..."

The geography lecturer was standing on the podium, giving a history lecture filled with his own opinions. The adorable bald elderly man was vigorously waving his arms while turning back from time to time to chalk down important key points.

Within the white classroom, Garen was sitting in the back row by the window with his chin resting on his palm, flipping through the geography textbook on his table.

The entire textbook was white except for the cover, where a black flying bird was printed in the middle. It was the flag of the Yalu Confederation. The four characters on top of the image meant geography.

Garen flipped through the front pages in the images section and stopped at the page with the world map.

The white rectangular area represented the ocean; three irregular gray lands were floating in the middle of the ocean.

The three lands formed a ring pattern with a tiny gap in the upper left corner.

The upper strip of land was labeled Stonecliff Continent, the bottom left was Azura Continent and the bottom right was Fivestar Continent. These three continents were surrounded by countless islands of various shapes and sizes.

Garen's finger slowly and steadily glided on the Stonecliff Continent and finally stopped at the middle part of the continent, slightly to the left. There was an irregularly shaped land in that location, labeled as Yalu Confederation.

This region was close to a third of the entire Stonecliff Continent.

"This world sure is strange... Even though planes exist, no one has been able to explore the entire world. The continents are entirely surrounded by water with no end in sight. All of humanity revolves around the three continents, and the surface area is equivalent to all of the continents on Earth combined, if not more."

Garen flipped to the next page, glanced through it and looked out the window.

A group of people was setting pole flags on a field at a distance away. It seemed like they were preparing for some sort of activity.

The late afternoon sunlight with a hint of redness shined onto the field, covering the dark green surface with a layer of golden red.

It had been three days since Garen returned from the dojo. He already applied during the audition at the dojo, and all he needed to do now was to wait for the results.

If he passed, he would directly become a formal disciple of the White Cloud Dojo; he would be able to learn a Secret Method and even receive a monthly allowance.

Ting...

The sweet sound of the school bell rang out, marking the end of the class.

The geography teacher clapped his hands to get the class’ attention.

"Well, today's lessons end here. I hope that everyone reviews after going back. I will be checking next lesson. Lan Ruo, thank you for your hard work."

"It's nothing."

A black haired female student with twin ponytails stood and nodded. She then left her seat and waited for the teacher to leave before she rapidly wiped the writing on the blackboard.

The girl had a pure and cold disposition. She had an oriental look with large black pupils; her bangs slanted diagonally downward across her forehead, and her skin was fair and delicate.

Garen knew her; there were only twenty-five students in the class—there was not a single person who didn’t know her.

Lan Ruo was in the top three in academics in the class and top five in the entire grade. She was pretty and pure like a flawless ceramic doll, and her skin was as tender as milk jelly.

It was just that she had an indifferent personality and barely spoke to her classmates. Other than the basic greetings, she would always silently look at the person trying to start a conversation with her. Faced with her large eyes and expressionless face, they could only give up and leave.

"Have you seen Fayne?" Kalidor approached Garen from the front rows. With a head full of yellow hair, he wore a white shirt and yellow leather vest with a sapphire necklace hanging around his chest. With his thin frame and fashion, he looked extremely flamboyant.

"Fayne? We only just got off class and he's already gone. Why are you looking for him?" Garen puzzledly asked. "That guy's probably messing around with some girl somewhere."

"Since his elder cousin came, let's gather for lunch later. She'll be bringing a female friend with her, so it'll be me, you, Fayne and them. We're all in the same grade, and I heard that they're from an all girls' school." Kalidor raised his eyebrows.

"So what if they're from a girls' school? I need to go to the dojo later, so I can't make it."

"Why are you missing out on such a good chance?"

"I'll go the next time, really." Garen shrugged his shoulders. "This time, I really have something to do."

"You rascal... This is such a good chance!" Kalidor muttered to himself as he left the classroom.

Garen was speechless as he shook his head. After tidying up the book on his table, he stood up and walked out of the classroom with his black cloth bag.

********************

Twenty minutes later...

White Cloud Dojo Martial Coliseum

Within a dim and spacious redwood hall.

A bald elderly man sat cross-legged on the floor with a burning fireplace at his back. The red flames were continuously propelled outwardly, creating a crackling sound.

There was no lighting, only the red glow of the fireplace.

Over ten youths in white clothing sat cross-legged in front of the elderly man on the floor. Each of them had a solemn expression on their face as they looked at the elderly man.

"Congratulations," the bald elderly man slowly said. "You're the latest batch of official disciples this year."

No one said anything, but their breathing became slightly heavier. Among them, the oldest was eighteen years old and the youngest was fifteen. However, without any exception, joyful expressions appeared on all their faces.

The elderly man noticed it and slightly nodded his head.

"When you become a formal disciple, the greatest benefit, other than not having to pay tuition fees, is that you'll be taught a Secret Method of Martial Arts."

"Secret Methods of Martial Arts are an absolutely undisclosed secret within each and every sect and dojo. So before we begin, I hope that you will be able to uphold the agreement that you just signed."

The elderly man took out an ancient yellow scroll from his black gi and gently spread it open on the floor.

"Starting from the first person on the left, come up here and look at this once, then step back."

The leftmost person was a girl who was sitting in a cross-legged position. As she stood, she walked to the front to pick up the scroll. After giving it a glance, she immediately returned to her original position. Then the second, third...

Each of them took less than ten seconds to finish reading.

Sitting in the rear was a purple-haired boy with red eyes: it was Garen who had rushed here directly from school to receive the Secret Method of Martial Arts. He was wearing a white gi with both of his hands on his knees, staring at the students who had seen the scroll.

It was soon his turn. Garen stood up and walked to the front. He knelt in front of the elderly man, picked up the scroll and carefully looked at it.

A human figure was drawn on the light yellow scroll: the figure was posing in a weird posture-- similar to the horse stance -- emanating a rich and special hidden meaning.

Garen looked at it once and easily remembered it. At the same time, he detected a light fragrance from the scroll. It was very faint and similar to the smell of honey.

As he returned to his position and sat down, he suddenly felt sleepy.

"Now, take the posture shown on the scroll. Take note of that particular hidden meaning," the bald elderly man's voice clearly sounded out.

Everyone stood up, spread out and began to imitate the posture shown on the scroll.

Garen followed suit as well: his arms were thrust to the front while tiptoeing on one leg and on his heels with the other.

After taking the stance, the skill section at the bottom of his field of vision suddenly changed. A new skill actually gradually appeared: White Cloud Fundamental Secret Method: Elementary.

Garen felt a warm sensation slowly converging in his chest and abdomen, then spreading to his four limbs. His entire body rapidly entered into a comfortable state.

Within the attribute column in his field of vision, his strength attribute slowly started to change. It jumped from 0.44 to 0.45.

The elderly man's voice sounded out again.

"Do you feel a pleasant feeling spreading throughout your body? It means that you have already successfully learned our White Cloud Secret Arts. In the future, use this pose to meditate. This Secret Method will increase your strength based on your physical condition and talent. This Secret Method has three stages: the beginning Heat Stage, intermediate Frost Stage, and finally Heatfrost Interchange . Every time you move to the next stage, it will increase your strength to a certain amount. If a normal person were to reach the highest level, their strength will increase to twice their original strength. Of course, it would take a while to reach that point.

"In addition, the growth of the Secret Method is progressive. There are also some restrictions when training with this method: do not train when you're too tired, do not train when you're too hungry, do not train where there are lots of distractions..."

Garen was sitting in the back, listening to the key points explained by the elderly man. As he continued to hold the posture, he was experiencing a pleasant feeling throughout his body due to the increase in blood flow.

He continued to listen to the key points as he monitored the attributes and skills section at the bottom of his field of vision.

After thinking for a while, his line of sight finally focused on his newly gained White Cloud Secret Method.

After a few seconds, a burst of energy suddenly rushed into the skill.

The display status of the White Cloud Secret Method gradually changed, from elementary to intermediate.

Chapter 12: Secret Method 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Humm!!

In the instant the change was completed, Garen felt a tingling sensation throughout his entire body. Suddenly, his blood flow increased, and the pleasant feeling from just now abruptly changed to a cool and refreshing feeling as his heart rate accelerated like a rapid drum beat.

At the attribute column at the bottom of his sight, his strength attribute was once again changing. From the initial 0.45, it gradually changed to 0.46, then to 0.47, 0.48, 0.49 to 0.5!! The number stopped at 0.5 and, at that moment, Garen felt that all the muscles in his body were screaming in pain; from various parts of his body, a powerful force rushed out.

His arms, legs and chest were all slightly enlarging.

Puff...

Garen could not help but exhale, the air that he breathed out was slightly hot.

At this moment, the elderly man's voice sounded out again, "After training, use the Secret Method of our dojo together with the basic fighting techniques. A special technique to exert force combined with the Secret Method training will allow you to achieve the most explosive output. You will experience the benefits yourself in the future. Each stage will experience a different level of explosiveness."

"At most, a normal person's instantaneous peak force is around 200 pounds. By training using a Special Method and the use of an Explosive Force Technique, your strength will be able to reach this limit and might even exceed it.

"And so!"

The elderly man stood as his eyes swept through the students.

"There are no shortcuts in martial arts! There's only diligence! Sweat! Effort!! As long as you put in enough effort, you can compensate for your lack of talent!"

"Yes!" Everyone could not help but shout out loud.

The elderly man nodded in satisfaction, took out a piece of paper from his pocket, then walked to the wall and pasted it on. Then, he walked out of the hall and closed the door behind him.

Garen's entire body was bulging, and his blood was flowing at a high speed. However, he did not feel cold in the slightest. He breathed out once more and slowly recovered from the posture; he rested while standing still. Everyone around him was caught up in the excitement and did not notice his strange demeanor.

The wooden hall was filled with clamor; students who were familiar with each other were asking each other about their experience regarding the Secret Method.

"Hey! Garen, how are you feeling?" Feeling a tap on his shoulder, Garen quickly turned around and found Erwin standing behind him.

"There's a pleasant feeling throughout my entire body; it feels similar to how it feels after going for a run!" Garen quickly replied, "Senior Brother Erwin, how about you?"

"You can just call me Erwin." There's a trace of excitement in Erwin's expression. "I feel the same way you do. Also, I heard that after training using the Secret Method, our Explosive Force Technique will be even stronger. Moreover, the stronger our body is, the more powerful our peak force will be! My original strength was around 120 pounds, but I think I've reached 200 pounds with this Secret Method! This is a normal man's limit!

"It's just that starting from 160 pounds, it gets even harder the more we train. In order to exceed 200 pounds, every slightest improvement requires a lot of hard work and effort."

"Senior Brother, since you have a strong foundation from the start, your situation is better than ours." Garen helplessly shrugged his shoulders. "I am content as long as I can reach your standard."

"That's simple." Erwin patted Garen's shoulder with a smile. "With a weak foundation, you'll find that you will improve quickly from the start and only slow down much later. Since there’s a limit to the human body, it only gets harder towards the end. In our White Cloud Dojo, the highest record is 250 pounds."

"250 pounds?" Garen quietly noted down this number. "Where can we test our strength?"

"The headquarters specially made sandbags with different weights so that we can test our strength. We can roughly estimate our strength based on how far we can hit the sandbags," Erwin explained.

"Why don't we go and try it out?" Garen was eager to try.

"That's right, Senior Brother Erwin, let's go and try it."

While the two of them were talking, two of the students approached and introduced themselves. The boy was Khairul and the girl was Rodelisa; they were in the same batch as Garen.

"Sure, let's go and test our current strength!" Erwin was interested as well. He brought the three of them out of the wooden hall and traversed through the red wooden corridors. They soon passed by a rectangular sports field made of white stone and entered a black courtyard built on its edge.

Within the courtyard, five black sandbags of different sizes were hanging on a black metallic frame. On its right, there were many old boxing gloves on a wooden shelf. There were already some students around the sandbags testing their strength.

Garen looked at all of the sandbags; from left to right, they were labeled: 120, 140, 160, 180, and 200. The five sandbags each corresponded to a different weight. A white line was drawn behind the sandbags; it was there for validation. Only when the sandbags crossed the line after getting hit would the force of the blow be considered as meeting the corresponding weight.

At that moment, a group of people had already given it a try, and no one managed to hit the sandbags far enough to reach the white line. They could not do it even with the lightest 120 pounds sandbag.

Soon, a slim and flat-chested girl with short silver hair walked out of the crowd. It was the girl that competed with Garen for the 15th placing: Daris. Daris stood in front of the 120 pound sandbag. She breathed in deeply, took a step back and pulled her right fist back. Like a coiled up spring, her pose was impeccable, and she had a solemn expression on her face.

Following her movements, the surroundings quieted down. Everyone was attentively looking at her to see how well she would do.

"Judging from her flawless posture, she must have trained before," Erwin whispered to Garen. "I heard that her family runs a dojo as well. It's just that after her father passed away and her mother fell sick, there was no one to take over, and it was difficult for the the dojo to continue. She joined the White Cloud Dojo to make a name for herself, and once she gains enough fame, she'll be able to revitalize her family's dojo."

"Isn't she only sixteen or seventeen years old? It must be hard for her to take the responsibility of her entire household on her shoulders." Garen slowly nodded.

Hah!!!

Suddenly, Daris charged forward while wearing the old gloves, her right fist striking out in a straight line and brutally hitting the black sandbag.

Bang! Ow!

Daris was struck by the sandbag as it swung back, causing her to fall onto the floor. Her eyes reddened and welled up with tears.

The surrounding students all burst out in laughter.

"From her posture, you wouldn't think that she would only reach a third of the distance..."

"Shouldn't the requirement be lower for a girl?"

The sandbag made a whooshing sound as it swung and continued to wobble around.

Another boy went up and tried; he looked muscular and was a head taller than both Garen and Erwin.

With a dull thud, the boy struck the sandbag and it covered most of the distance and was only a small distance away from the white line. "It was so close to reaching 120 pounds." He shook his head and walked off.

"I'll go!"

The boy next to Garen, Khairul, managed to reach half of the distance. The girl, Rodelisa, managed to reach a third of the distance.

"Aren't you going to try?"

"I'll continue watching first." Garen nodded. He did not know his current strength either, but he was slightly expectant as well after greatly improving.

"Then, I'll go first." Erwin walked towards the sandbags as he rolled up his sleeves.

Bang!!

Erwin easily crossed the white line for 120 pounds. With an easygoing expression, he warmed up his fist in a relaxed manner.

The spectactating students immediately quieted down; all of their attention were attracted. This was the first new student that easily passed.

Daris was also standing in a corner looking at Erwin; in her eyes, envy was written all over.

"Senior Brother, good luck!"

"You can do it!"

Garen and the other two loudly shouted.

Erwin smiled and walked to the front of the 140 pounds sandbag. He took a standard fighting stance and breathed in deeply.

Bang!!

The black sandbag immediately swung up, flying over most of the distance before easily crossing over the white line.

Then, it was the 160 pounds sandbag; with a dull thud, there was still a little distance before the sandbag could reach the line.

Erwin shook his head with a smile. "I can't do it, this is my limit. I’ve already tried many times before. I had a breakthrough today only because of the Secret Method; I couldn't even reach 140 pounds before."

"I'll give it a try as well." Garen walked forward and stood at the 120 pounds position. Wearing the gloves and not using any techniques, he immediately took a pose and breathed in deeply.

"I'll use three quarters of my strength." He slowly relaxed the muscles in his arm, estimating three quarters of his strength.

He tightened his fist.

Bang!!

The black sandbag immediately flew out; there was still a little distance before it could cross the white line though.

Even though his fist was wrapped inside the gloves, Garen could still feel a numb sensation in his hand.

"Not bad!!" Erwin loudly cheered. As a lifelong martial artist, he could tell that Garen did not put in all of his effort into that punch. If Garen had tried his best, he would easily break through to 120 pounds. Previously, Erwin thought that this junior brother would not be able to do it, at least not within such a short amount of time. "As expected, youngsters still in their puberty are scary..." Erwin was speechless as he shook his head.

Among the other students, the previous few that almost passed looked at Garen's physique and did not want to admit defeat; they got ready to start trying once more. All of them made up their mind to break through to 120 pounds that day.

The rest of the students were still quite lacking. Some of them started to gather around the students with better results to ask them about force exertion techniques, while the rest slowly dispersed.

Daris bit her lower lip as she stared at Garen. "He wasn't as strong as me previously... Yet, he has grown so much within a month! How is this possible!?" She recalled training day in and day out just to inherit the dojo, but she barely reached the standard of an ordinary girl due to having a weak physique from birth. Along the way, she shed a lot of tears and suffered a lot. In that moment, she suddenly felt wronged from the unfairness of this world.

Garen relaxedly stretched his hands and neck as he estimated his current level. "If I use all of my strength, I should be able to easily break through to 120 pounds. However, 140 pounds should be quite difficult. My actual strength should be much lower than Senior Brother Erwin."

From within the entire White Cloud Dojo, Erwin's level was superior among the new disciples. However, he had reached the limit of his physique, so he would need to put in a lot of effort to make any more improvements.

The strength of ordinary formal disciples was around 160 pounds, while the stronger ones were disciples that had been training for a long time. The highest 200 pounds could only be reached by the dojo master; that was the limit of adults. At least, that was the limit of adults in the confederation.

The fact that Erwin was able to get close to the limit of an adult by the age of 18 was obviously the result of long-term training. And since Garen was able to reach 120 pounds by 16 years old, it was clear that he was within the upper tier among his peers.

Furthermore, he had yet to use the second stage of the Secret Method after comprehending it. When combined with an Explosive Force Technique, his strength would greatly increase, and he might even be able to reach 140 pounds.

Chapter 13: The Beginning of the Beginning 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Coming out of the ring satisfied, Garen removed his gloves and walked to Erwin's side.

"Looks like I'll be able to catch up to you very soon, Senior Brother Erwin."

"You think you’re the only one improving?" Erwin threw him a look of feigned contempt. "Alright, let’s put this topic aside. You have to go home for dinner later, right? It’s quite far from here to the city center, so head home then or else you won’t be able to find transportation later."

"Okay, I'll be leaving first then." Garen was aware of the situation too. He greeted two other people on his way out the door, walked past the courtyard and exited the main entrance of the Martial Colosseum with a few other students.

White Cloud Dojo was just a dojo in Huaishan City. It had two branches and a main Martial Colosseum. Both branches were within the city, and only the main Martial Colosseum was located in the outskirts, which was quite a distance from Bluetree Street where Garen lived.

After finally managing to hail a carriage, both Garen and another female student going the same way squeezed into it. The carriage started heading down the gray cobblestone road towards the city center.

Sitting on the right side of the carriage, Garen reclined on the leather seat, closed his eyes and rested with his head tilted slightly upwards. The crisp sound of hooves on cobblestone could be heard incessantly.

The girl beside him took out a book and started reading it page by page; the sound of pages turning came at regular intervals.

In a daze, Garen slowly fell into a half-asleep state.

Some time passed. There seemed to be a slight commotion going on nearby. He gradually woke up and looked out the carriage window.

The black-haired girl beside him also turned to her side to look out the left window. A group of colorfully dressed children were playing chase and ran past the side of the carriage. These children, seemingly from Zhejiang, each had an assortment of red, yellow, and green gift boxes in their hands.

"Ahh, it's Children's Day today." Garen realized.

"It was yesterday, but some families choose to celebrate it a day later. That way, it's less crowded and probably safer for the kids." The black-haired girl turned around to face the front of the carriage again. She took a glance at Garen and asked, "Where are you getting off?"

"I'm getting off at Pennington."

"It's already Blacktree Street here. We'll be at Pennington soon."

It was then that Garen noticed the buildings passing by outside had become gray ones; the walls of each engraved with reliefs. Both sides of the road were each lined with a row of candlenut trees.

"Thanks for the reminder. The corner of Pennington is just up ahead. Sir, if you could just let me down here?"

"Of course."

The black carriage slowed down to a stop at the corner of Pennington. Garen stepped off the carriage and paid the fare. Afterwards, he straightened his clothes and started walking towards Dolphin Antiques at the corner of the street.

A ray of scarlet sunlight shone in and lit the whole antique store a warm shade of red.

The old man was once again sitting in front of the bookshelf directly facing the entrance, and had dozed off at the desk.

Garen walked through the door without disturbing him, and directly headed towards the left side of the store with a sense of familiarity, to where the Bronze Cross Emblem was placed.

He picked up the emblem and examined it. There was a thin layer of glimmer on it, but that didn't matter. Holding the emblem, Garen's attention shifted to the Attribute Pane in the lower part of his field of vision.

Although 100% of the Potential Attribute had been used up, several days of continuous "accumulation" had made Garen’s Potential rise to 47% once again.

"You again, kid?" Old Man Gregor spoke from behind him, "You're here to see it everyday. If you like it so much, why not just buy it so you can look at it all you want?"

"Am I not already trying to save up? Do you think it's possible for me as an ordinary student to casually come up with such a large sum of money?" Garen refuted without turning around to face him.

"It's up to you. Your presence makes my shop seem livelier anyway. But rules are rules, it's 10 bucks an hour."

"Yeah, yeah… You're really obsessed about money." Garen was rendered speechless.

He dawdled for more than an hour holding the emblem, while the sky outside gradually darkened. Garen reluctantly put the emblem down after seeing his potential increase slightly at an infuriatingly slow pace.

"Remember to take good care of it. I'll be back!"

"Yeah! Scram kid, you're even more long-winded than me!" The old man impatiently waved his hand and continued, "It's time for me to close up anyway."

"No wonder you don't get any business here." After multiple interactions, Garen was already familiar with the old man's temper. Initially, there was still a veil of civility between the two, but after growing more familiar, both just let it all go and spoke their minds.

***********

More than two weeks had passed.

Garen resumed his normal routine in the academy, travelling between the antique store and the dojo day in and day out. His Potential steadily increased past 100%, allowing him to allocate new Attribute Points again.

It's just that he hadn't decided on what to add the points to. Originally, he meant to raise his grades in a few subjects, but unfortunately, not all skills could be enhanced with Attribute Points.

Only a few special skills allowed such enhancements, and not others; for example, National Studies and Foreign Languages. The high-grade learning materials for these subjects weren't even distributed, and Garen had no relevant memory of them, so naturally, he couldn't understand any of it.

It dawned on him that his Attribute point enhancements could only work on skills and subjects already within his field of knowledge.

Simply put, if he was taught a level of the White Cloud Secret Method but had no clue about its further levels, he would need follow-up training before he could enhance it. So, under such circumstances, he wouldn't be able to compel an Attribute point enhancement since his memory bank didn't have the blueprint for further enhancements.

Attribute Points and his Unique Skills, as Garen concluded, were more like means with which to substantially develop, mine and utilize his potential, expressed in the form of skills and levels. They were not like skill points in a videogame that allowed him to learn new things instantly.

Therefore, to enhance a skill, one would have to have a comprehensive understanding of the content of the next skill level. Leave something out, and the skill couldn't be upgraded.

Putting aside his own development, his relationship with his sister Ying Er seemed to have changed. Ever since that odd session of playful slapstick the other day, Ying Er would be in a hurry and wouldn’t say much every time they interacted. What happened? Garen wasn't sure what was going on with Ying Er. He just felt that things had become more awkward than before. After meals, she would clear the dishes quickly, then dash back to hide in her room, not speaking to Garen anywhere near as much as she used to.

In the blink of an eye, midterms were approaching fast. Confederate schools had three semesters in a year, so each semester was quite short. Ying Er's archery tournament was about to begin too.

Garen did some light reviewing. Only the exams in third year of high school were important anyway, so he didn't really bother about the other semesters. It's not as if university was the only option. Moreover, Mathematics and Physics here were effortlessly simple. It took him a mere ten days to boost his mastery of both subjects to the advanced level. He even managed to attain elementary level for both National Studies and Foreign Languages through rote memorization.

After enhancing his intelligence, his memory and comprehension had improved as well. Pairing that with his adult consciousness and mind, this made his results far better than that of the previous Garen. If not for the fact that his focus wasn't on studies, he would probably be on par with the top students.

****************

The afternoon sun shone on Pennington Street at an angle which cast long silhouettes on the street. Both sides of the street were deserted, and only a few pedestrians passed by, all with thick windbreaker jackets on.

Two black cars were parked by the side of the road. The polished surface of the car bodies reflected a pale yellow glow. In one of the cars, the driver could be seen sleeping soundly at the wheel.

On the right side of the street, a purple-haired boy with burgundy eyes was rubbing his hands together and striding along in a hurry. His hair was slightly long, extending from his temples to his chin. His purple hair wrapped around his face, occasionally being blown backwards by the wind. He was wearing a light gray sweater and trousers, which accentuated his porcelain white skin.

The boy looked up at the advertisement banner on a distant building.

The red banner read: From 21st to 25th of September, Elizabeth Jewelries Autumn Bargain, Discounts ranging from 50 - 90 %.

"It's already September? Time sure flies…" Garen quickened his pace. He was on his way to the antiques store. It was already a few days past the time limit that the old man had mentioned. Because he had only just been freshly selected as a disciple at the dojo, he could only participate in the internal tryouts in the next quarter; there was no way he could make any money from tournaments for now.

He didn't have the money, but the other buyer that Old Man Gregor mentioned hadn't appeared either. Garen felt at ease and justified to continue making one to two hours of contact with the emblem every day to absorb more Potential.

"Enhancing skills with Attribute Points still isn't as worthwhile as using it on my own Attributes," Garen carefully analyzed, "Skills can be improved through mastery. Unless it's a difficult skill to improve, using Attribute Points on my own body would be better. Improvements like these are long-term enhancements. If I used a few Attribute Points on Physics or Mathematics just to make it easier for myself to attain an advanced level, it would have been a waste. The most that would have achieved was saving me some time. It would be more worthwhile if I used it on the difficult-to-improve White Cloud Secret Method…"

Garen glanced at the Attribute Pane in his lower field of vision.

Strength, enhanced by two points, was now at 0.52. Potential was at 124%.

"I obtained the improvements in strength by training in the White Cloud Secret Method, and partly through daily strength exercises. Moreover, since gaining Attribute Points seems to have the effect of fortifying and maintaining the body, my strength won't decrease from lack of training."

He glanced at the Skills Pane.

White Cloud Secret Method: Intermediate. Fundamental Combat Skills: Elementary. Explosive Fist Arts: Uninitiated.

"Explosive Fist Arts, the fighting technique that only Formal Disciples can learn upon initiation, as well as the intermediate level White Cloud Secret Method - I could use Attribute Points to enhance these." Garen hesitated. "Explosive Fist Arts can raise the strength of the whole body to its highest limit, and the strength of the fists can be increased by threefold; it is the upgraded version of Fundamental Combat Skills. Generally, it takes two years to master the basics, at which point the skin would harden and hitting a sandbag with gloveless bare hands wouldn't cause any injury, whereas the White Cloud Secret Method is the basis of all fundamentals, capable of producing exceptional results if accumulated throughout a long period of time. It has been said that it takes more than 10 years to reach the advanced level, and one would have to possess extraordinary talent…" /

Garen was particularly interested in the martial arts of this world now. It was very similar to the national martial arts on Earth in his previous life, but was much more commonplace than the latter. Even though both were difficult to train in and apply, this wasn't a problem for him because he had his special ability.

He had wanted to learn martial arts to strengthen himself in his past life, but he lacked the conditions to. Now that all the conditions were met, naturally, his interest has piqued; it was almost as if he had become obsessed with them..

"Fortunately, I have the emblem, which allows me to accrue Attribute Points. Following this progression for enhancements, I'll enhance the White Cloud Secret Method first, then boost my Explosive Fist Arts to the most advanced level. By then, I'll be able to reach the upper tier of the entire dojo! Even the Dojo Master of the White Cloud Dojo himself had merely attain the third tier in his Explosive Fist Arts and advanced his White Cloud Secret Method by another level, although it wasn't a full mastery."

"As long as I keep using the emblem to aid my enhancements, I can boost my martial art skills to a level similar to that of the Dojo Master with just five Attribute Points!"

Snapping out of his excitement, Garen had reached the corner of Pennington. Unusually, the entrance of Dolphin Antiques seemed a bit messy today.

He quickened his pace and walked into the store. He was greeted with a shock.

It was chaos inside: antiques and broken debris were strewn all over the floor, it was all a mess.

A man and a woman, both clad in windbreakers, stood at the store entrance while interrogating the old man.

Chapter 14: The Beginning of the Beginning 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The man appeared to be 40 years of age. He had a cute little mustache above his lips and an overall mature-looking face. He wore a black top hat and his black trench coat draped down all the way to his ankles. The one thing that caught Garen’s attention was the black pipe he had in his hand. He was smoking patiently with a frown on his face; white fog shot out of his nostrils from time to time.

The woman standing beside the man was very pretty. She was around the age of 20 to 30 with her light blonde hair in a ponytail. Her entire appearance was elegant and clean, and her white trench coat was spotless without the slightest hint of dirt. With her delicate and beautiful porcelain-like face, she seemed like a professional who was decisive and simple.

The arrival of Garen did not catch the attention of the three people in the room. He walked softly until he was beside the old man and eavesdropped.

"…Then, the time of the crime should be last night. The exact time has to be deduced based on the evidence at the scene of the crime," the man rubbed his chin and said in a low voice.

"That’s right," the old man answered in a low voice as well. "That is the situation as I know it. I have told you everything I know. Oh, this is a regular customer of mine, Garen."

The man checked out Garen from head to toe, then nodded. "Can I ask you a few questions?"

"Sure, no problem," Garen responded hastily.

The man asked Garen about the condition of the shop last night, then began to wander around the store with the lady in white.

Old Man Gregor was kneeling on the ground, picking up the scattered old books. He was quietly cursing the thief.

　"Old man, you were robbed?" Garen kneeled down as well and helped to pick up the books.

As soon as "robbed" was mentioned, the wrinkles on Old Man Gregor’s face twisted into a lump. "I was not feeling well today, so I decided to only open the shop in the afternoon. You know me, I definitely wasn’t opening the shop just for you. Who would’ve expected that as soon as I walked in, I saw…"

The old man and the young man got along strangely well. When they chatted, they forgot about the age difference and formed a cross-generational friendship. Garen felt warm on the inside. He knew that the old man actually felt fine and had been for days. The old man always opened the shop for him in the afternoon before his visit and closed the shop right after he had left. He did not care about money at all. He knew that Garen was simply coming to see the emblem, and therefore opened the shop exclusively for him.

Old Man Gregor was too lonely. He wanted to find something to do to kill time and, perhaps, bickering with Garen was one of the most interesting times in his day.

"Which things are missing?" Garen was suddenly worried, as he remembered the Bronze Cross Emblem.

"Some stuff went missing, including the Bronze Cross Emblem you like so much." The old man had a long face as he confirmed Garen’s worries.

"F*ck!" Garen’s expression changed. "Are you sure it’s lost?" Suddenly, he remembered something and immediately suggested, "No, I think you may have missed a spot when you searched. The emblem was so small. There are so many things here. Maybe it fell in a corner somewhere." He quickly cheered up.

"There is no need to search again. The emblem is definitely lost." The old man shook his head. "I already searched everywhere before you came…"

Garen was silent. The emblem was essential for him to improve his potential. He had searched the entirety of Huaishan City, and the Bronze Cross Emblem was the only thing that had the potential for him to absorb. Now that his sole source of improvement was lost, the perfect life and the bright future Garen had planned suddenly darkened.

The two of them kneeled onto the ground, not sure what to say now.

"Who are those two?"

"They are federal detectives who are investigating the serial thief case: Dale Quicksilver and Miss Si Lan. They are here to help solve the case," the old man informed Garen in a whisper.

In this world, crimes were normally solved by detectives. Famous detectives and policemen had the right to investigate crime scenes immediately after crimes were committed. Since most cases were solved by detectives, famous detectives had a high societal ranking.

Garen nodded and observed the interaction between the two as he picked up more books.

The two of them wandered around for a long time when Dale Quicksilver finally broke the silence.

"This is definitely the doing of the Golden Hoop! The style of the crime is exactly the same as Navici!" He gently touched the edge of a table and sniffed it under his nose.

"This guy ran away quickly!" Miss Si Lan frowned.

"Si Lan, remember what I said the time we solved the Light of Wendini case?" Dale Quicksilver asked suddenly.

"Sir, you mean?"

"Yes"--he then turned his body around--"If the Golden Hoop appears, the two of you must remain calm and not provoke him. This criminal is atrocious, do not anger him! Any carelessness will result in casualties! He is a retired officer from the special forces."

"Not an issue!"

"Of course!"

The old man and Garen quickly stood up and answered.

"We did not come all the way from Navici for fun. This time… we will not let you get away again!" Dale Quicksilver turned around and mumbled. His gaze became strangely profound, "Si Lan! Inform the White Eagle at once. Tell them there is no need for further investigation, say that we already caught the tail of the criminal!"

"Yes, sir!"

Dale Quicksilver shook his trench coat and walked toward the front door in big steps. Si Lan followed after him closely.

"Sir, should we wait for the White Eagle before we make any move? Out of all the cases we have dealt with, the Golden Hoop is the most dangerous. This is also our first encounter…"

"No, it will be too late if we wait for them to take action…" Dale Quicksilver raised his head and stared at the flaming red sunset sky. "Relax, nothing is going to happen… No matter how dangerous, he is just an ordinary person. All human beings have a weakness!"

"Don’t you think this is too risky… after all, the Golden Hoop was an officer in the special forces. He had received formal training and can easily defeat five to six adults empty handed," Si Lan’s face was still frowning.

"Don’t worry. We are not going to personally attack him," Dale Quicksilver smiled kindly and pinched Si Lan’s cheek. Si Lan blushed and lowered her head. "Alright, let’s go back."

"Yes, sir."

With one person in front and other in the back, they marched away.

Inside the shop, Garen sat down in a chair and watched their backs until they were gone.

"Old man, who’s this Golden Hoop? Is he famous?"

"He is a serial thief and killer. Have you not been paying attention to the recent news? There have been multiple instances of stealing and murdering all over the country. I’m lucky that I didn’t have to personally face that Golden Hoop…" Old Man Gregor, who was cursing just moments ago, was rejoicing, "I heard that the Golden Hoop was once surrounded by police. He wounded two policemen with a gun then casually ran away by hiding himself in a crowd. The only wound he received was during a brawl with a policeman when a bullet brushed against his arm."

Listening to the old man, Garen faintly felt that this was not the first time the Golden Hoop and Dale Quicksilver had had a feud.

"A few days ago, in a manor down at the countryside, Dale Quicksilver’s friend had a brawl with the Golden Hoop and was close to arresting him," the old man added.

Garen squinted his eyes and saw that at the end of the street, Dale Quicksilver and Si Lan were negotiating with a strong looking man in black. The man had a tense gaze, bulky muscles, and movements that exposed him as someone who knew Martial Arts.

"Is Dale Quicksilver’s friend that person?" He pointed toward the sturdy man.

The old man peeked in the direction. "Yep, that’s the friend. He was in the shop moments ago."

Garen nodded. From the man’s body language, he could tell the man’s combat level.

"Based on his body type and his aura, he is most likely an ordinary adult who has above average strength. He probably trained in military style combat, and it is possible that he knows special explosive techniques too."

Because of the instinct acquired from training, Garen could naturally compare the differences between the man and himself. "If we had a battle, I do not have nearly as much practical experience; however, strength-wise, I am definitely stronger than him! The strength of an ordinary adult, converted into numbers, is 0.5, and I have long surpassed this number. If I focus all my energy on special explosive techniques, I will win in strength by a landslide. Therefore, if the Golden Hoop is similar to them…"

Garen again focused on the skill panel in his vision.

"Only I am different than others. I can attribute points to different attributes. My actual strength does not match my physique." He had observed everyone else in the Combat Center, and everyone was the same. The heavier and bulkier physique someone had, the more muscles they had and the stronger they were. He was the only exception. He had an ordinary physique, but if he decided to explode all of his energy, he could easily surpass the limits.

*************************

"Bang!"

After a dull impactful sound, Garen punched hard at a 180-pound sandbag, which swayed over the passing line.

He was shirtless. His white, sturdy muscles were quivering on his body. He was not wearing any gloves; instead, he was hitting the sandbag with his bare fists. It was evening; the boxing room was empty except for him.

"After only two weeks, I can easily punch 180 pounds. White Cloud Secret Arts mixed with Explosive Fist Techniques sure is amazing."

Garen grabbed a towel and wiped the sweat off his face.

"No wonder White Cloud Secrets Arts is a closely guarded secret art. It is the most fundamental art you could learn from the White Cloud Dojo. By now, the students who started training at the same time as me are far behind me. The level needed to attain Intermediate Secret Arts in addition to its growth speed are also higher than others too. On top of that, the first time I used the Secret Arts, the results were so great that I was able to upgrade it. Hmm… I guess that in the future I will never be able to achieve such great results again. I can’t believe I was able to combine the use of the medicinal aroma and the Secret Arts to achieve a score above 0.5."

When he was just starting to learn the Secret Arts, the old man from that day took out a secret art scroll that faintly had a medicinal aroma. It was the type of aroma that mixed well with the incense in the fireplace, stimulating deeper comprehensions during Secret Arts Training.

He again posed in the stance required for the White Cloud Secret Arts, and a surge of cold air slowly extended from his chest to his limbs. Muscles from his entire body were pulsing to the rhythm of his heart.

The body adjusted the most and improved the greatest during the first time a secret method was used. That day, Garen only adjusted slightly, but he was already able to handle the 120-pound weight. Now that he had recovered, his strength increased again. He was now able to utilize all the enhancements he received.

To exceed 180 pounds was not a difficult task.

　　

Standing in the stance dictated by the Technique, Garen’s attention was again focused on the skill panel.

"The Explosive Fist Technique is the real combat method in the Dojo. It is not a technique that only looks impressive. If I can successfully master the Explosive Fist Technique, then I can truly start my ranking tests. If I can get a ranking, then I can start teaching at a Dojo and receive better salaries… Then I can start collecting jewelry that contains potential."

Garen was again calculating inside his head. Feeling determined, he shifted his vision onto the Explosive Fist Technique.

"This is the one!"

Following his exclamation, the surge of cold air was sucked out of his head and squirmed onto the location of the record of the Explosive Fist Technique in his vision. The word "Uninitiated", finally, jumped slightly and abruptly changed into Elementary.

Instantly, Garen felt his body tighten as if a waxy liquid was being produced by his internal body. The liquid sluggishly seeped through his skin and covered it.

"Boom!"

Inside his brain, a loud noise rumbled.

Chapter 15: The Incident

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

All of a sudden, Garen felt like half of his body was frozen in frigid ice while the other half was scorching hot. He felt an overwhelming dizziness, as if someone was continuously pummeling on his head with a hammer.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

He could hear his heartbeat. Beat by beat; it pounded like a war drum. With every heartbeat, the streams of ice and fire began to merge together.

The freezing and scorching streams of blood intertwined, but remained distinct. They formed a delicate spiral inside Garen's body and began to flow rapidly.

Within the training hall, the serene moonlight scattered through the high windows. It created a delicate white cloak on Garen's body.

His face flushed like a cooked shrimp as he stood blankly in front of the sandbag. Steam began to rise from his hair, his body, and his pants as his sweat evaporated.

He didn't know how much time had passed.

Ka!

He slowly twitched his body. A loud, crisp sound resounded from one of his joints and echoed across the room. Subsequently, all his joints began to repeat the same sound as if popcorn was being popped.

His mind finally regained consciousness. The first thing he did was to walk in front of the 200 pounds sandbag. He lifted his right arm and took in a deep breath.

Peng!

The sandbag flew in the air and passed the qualification line. The remaining force of the swinging sandbag forced the metal frame to squeak. Garen stabilized the sandbag after it flew back.

[My strength increased again…]" He opened his right palm to examine his skin. His palm was covered by a crystallized texture which felt like a glove. Unlike before, he did not feel any pain hitting the sandbag.

The status under his vision also changed.

His Strength grew from 0.52 to 0.53, while his Vitality also increased from 0.31 to 0.33.

[When I combined this with Explosive Fist Arts, my skin's durability increased quite substantially.] He rubbed both of his hands as he scanned the training room. He saw a wooden rack at the corner filled with weapons. Sword, shield, broadsword, heavy sword, dagger, axe, and hammer. The rack had everything.

Garen approached the stand and grabbed a silver dagger. He gently lifted the dagger. Under the pristine moonlight, the dagger reflected a silvery shadow. The tip of the knife was blinding with its sharp edge.

He lightly slashed the back of his hand with the dagger.

Zzzp... It felt like he had slashed hard leather, and only left a slight white mark.

[Indeed... The Explosive Fists Arts can increase the body's durability! No wonder the procedure included tempering the body against wooden stumps.]

He was genuinely surprised. He began to increase the force exerted on the dagger, starting from one pound of strength. Two pounds... Three pounds... Five pounds... Ten pounds... 15 pounds... 20 pounds!!

All of a sudden, the skin under the dagger revealed a small cut, barely penetrating to the muscle underneath. The dagger was lodged inside, completely unable to move. Garen felt pain and quickly pulled back the dagger.

[Around 20 pounds of force is required to barely penetrate my muscle. The Explosive Fists Arts are indeed powerful. No wonder it takes years to train and master even with the help of natural talent, and no wonder White Cloud Dojo is renowned for this skill.]

Garen had tested his durability with his relaxed muscle, but if he flexed, 20 pounds would not be his limit. He gave this a slight thought, then tested it. He started with a force of 20 pounds and increased it to 50 pounds before the dagger finally pierced into his muscle.

[This is almost equivalent to the Body Hardening Technique. It's incredible!]

He placed the dagger back onto the wooden rack. As he loosened his muscles, blood began to emerge from his arm, but it immediately clotted.

He looked downwards at the 24% remaining Potential. Garen tidied up and dressed, then took the key beside the sandbag and left the training hall.

Any official student had the right to use the potential testing equipment in the secondary hall. Therefore, every official student had a key to the hall.

As Garen left the secondary hall, he could not spot a single soul on the street. The cold breeze carried a newspaper from the distance as he began to jog through the night. Garen had become accustomed to this habitual exercise.

It was almost 10 o’clock. The street was not in a crowded area with a large population. Garen took the desolate route for an easier jog. In ten minutes, he only spotted a few people.

The dim yellow light shoneined on the peaceful street. Garen’s footsteps echoed in the wind with the occasional wooden clap from a shop closing in the distance.

Beep!

A loud beeping noise came from the dark street across the corner. Garen moved from the middle of the road to the left side as he saw a black antique vehicle approach him from his right side. The bright yellow headlights blinded him for a brief moment when the car made a turn. He tried to block the radiance with his hand.

Just as the car passed him, a number in his vision suddenly changed.

[My Potential is going up!?!]

He immediately turned and ran to the car. The Potential Meter increased from 23% to 45% as soon as he turned around.

The only thing in his mind was to stop the car.

"Please stop!"

Garen dashed in front of the car and yelled with his arms wide open.

The cars in this world were slow to begin with. It didn’t show any sign of stopping after being blocked as it headed directly at Garen.

"F**k!"

Garen sidestepped to avoid the car as he began to chase the vehicle.

"Finish him."

Faintly, he heard a woman’s voice in the car.

Bang! The car door suddenly opened and directly hit him on the flank. A pitch black dagger silently darted at Garen’s stomach.

Garen’s heart abruptly jumped as he subconsciously grabbed the arm behind the dagger. His left hand naturally punched the door window.

Bang!

The arm that held the dagger snapped like dried branches. The red muscle and white ligament tore as blood spilled all over the car.

Simultaneously, the car door window easily shattered. Between the tiny glass shards, Garen’s left hand directly punched the passenger’s head. The person’s face caved in when the forceful impact landed. The shape of his face changed as his nose, eyes, and mouth jumbled together due to the violent force. Stained with blood, white bone shards collided audibly against the windshield.

Garen was shocked.

So was the person still driving.

The car continued to move forward. Garen wrenched the front passenger door wide open as he dragged the car to the side. A graceful looking body fell out from the open door. It was the physique of a young woman with an attractive figure.

The girl’s body dropped in front Garen with her face completed disfigured. It was like ketchup mixed with tofu. Her right arm, which held the dagger, hung limply on the side of her body. A black trench coat accented her exquisite figure. From the side, it was easy to see her charming cleavage. From her appearance, she was a young lady.

Under the pungent smell of the blood, he sensed the light fragrance of perfume.

He looked at the body in front of him before blankly staring at the car in the distance. He felt he could see the features of the man driving, along with his cold, bloody stare.

[I just killed somebody…] He stared at his brown pants, now stained with blood, Garen felt a sudden fear from the bottom of his heart.

"I just killed somebody…" he mumbled under his breath as he looked at the woman’s body.

Abruptly, he scanned his surroundings on the empty street. After he made sure that no one saw him, Garen immediately took off running.

The frightened and rhythmless footsteps resonated in the distance.

After he rushed home, he dashed straight into his room without a word.

"Brother, I’ll leave your allowance for next week on the dinner table..." Ying Er walked out of her room. Dumbfounded, she stared at Garen who stepped in front of her. Her face turned pale and she stopped in the middle of her sentence.

Bang!

The bedroom door shut.

"Garen’s back? He didn’t shower after his jog?" their mother Betty asked, opening the bedroom door.

"Yeah Garen, did you exercise again?" Garen’s step-father’s voice transmitted from the bedroom.

"Mhm, he seems to be rushed today for some reason. I didn’t even see him before he got back to his room," his mother complained before she closed the door again.

Huff… Huff…

Huff…

Garen leaned against the door as he caught his breath. His face was an ashen white as his pupils dilated and contracted. The image of the split second when he killed the girl replayed vividly in his head. The shattered bone shards, the crimson red blood, the crooked broken arm, and the pair of wide bloody eyes.

"Nobody was there." He tried to remember his surroundings. There was no one on the street due to the isolated location. The streetlight was dim and the headlights were not shining on him.

He reevaluated the situation before he mumbled, "Nobody saw it, except for the guy driving."

Garen learned how to control his excessive strength gain through continued training, but in that dire situation when his life was on the line, he thought that it wasn’t enough to just defend and his uncontrolled power was brutal.

The result was that the opponent could not be more dead.

Dong! Dong! Dong!

"Brother, are you okay?" Ying Er’s voice resonated through the door.

"Don’t worry; I’ll be out in a minute after I change." Garen tried to respond in his usual tone.

"Mhm, then I’ll boil the water for you first?"

"Okay, thanks."

Her footsteps faded into the distance.

He tried to calm down his rapidly beating heart. He changed into his bathrobe before he grabbed his uniform and balled it into a lump, careful not to expose the parts with blood before walking out of the door.

Boo!

"What are you doing !!?" There was a figure in front of the door. It was Ying Er in her school uniform.

Reflexively, Garen wanted to close the door, but Ying Er put her foot in the doorway. Without much time to think, he dashed to his bed, threw his bloody clothes underneath the mattress, and sat at the edge of the bed.

Chapter 16: Accident 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bam.

The door of the room closed. Ying Er walked in with a look of suspicion, her red eyes scanning the situation inside the room.

"What kind of mischief are you up to again?"

"What mischief? My trousers weren't pulled up, and I didn't expect you to be standing at the door, so I just blocked it for a while." Garen combed his hands through his hair to massage his numb scalp.

"That's not true! What's that under your bed?" Ying Er's sharp eyes immediately spotted the suspicious trace. She walked a few steps forward and stood facing Garen. "Move aside, I want to find out what disgusting things you've been up to!"

"What are you trying to do? It's late, stop playing," Garen said with a deliberate frown.

"Move aside!" Ying Er was one of those who ignored everything once her temper got the better of her. When she saw that Garen wouldn't budge, it fueled her suspicion further.

"Stop it!"

"I said, move aside!" Ying Er's voice deepened as her expression became ice-cold. "Looks like you didn't learn a lesson the last time…"

Garen’s complexion slightly changed. "The last time" was the previous Garen; he tried to hide his collection of dirty magazines, but Ying Er found them and beat him up till he cried. Even though it wasn't actually him who experienced that shameful incident, it was enough to make him choke.

But no matter what, the clothes underneath his bed absolutely could not be discovered!

When she saw that he continued to keep silent, Ying Er's expression turned uglier.

"Looks like this time around, I'll have to give you a lesson you won't forget!" She started cracking her knuckles.

"It's not what you think, trust me!" Garen looked up into Ying Er's eyes. He had just killed someone by using too much force, and the last thing he wanted to do now was to fight his sister. He was worried that he might accidentally do it again…

Ying Er stared into his eyes and realized there wasn't a sliver of embarrassment or anger in them for being exposed, but instead a hint of sincerity.

Both stared at each other for a while.

Ying Er slowly breathed a sigh of relief.

"You're sure?"

"I'm sure!" Garen replied in haste. "Apart from this one thing, I'll agree to whatever you want."

"Fine. I'll ask you a few questions. If you can answer me truthfully, I won't bother you about this," Ying Er paused.

"No problem!"

"Do you like dad?"

"Of course I do. That's easy."

"Do you like mum?"

"Of course."

"Do you like uncle?"

"I do."

"Do you like Ai Fei?"

"Of c... Who's Ai Fei?"

Garen took a deep breath. "Good thing my reaction was quick…"

The palpitations that he suppressed earlier resurfaced. Seeing his sister's expression finally turn bright again, he felt as if he just escaped the clutches of death. He would have never thought that she knew Ai Fei, the prettiest girl among the female students around him.

"Alright… I'll spare you this time. But if you bring those disgusting things in here again, don't blame me…" A satisfied smile broke across Ying Er's face. "Okay, I'll go out now. Rest early."

"I know, I know. Alright, you get some rest too…" Garen breathed a sigh of relief. "See you tomorrow."

"Yup, see you tomorrow… you wish!" Ying Er cried out. She pounced over and slid under the bed in a flash.

Garen hurriedly crouched down and followed suit, reaching for his bundle of clothes.

The bloodied clothes were shoved deeper under the bed by Ying Er's vigorous movements; he could barely reach them.

"What’s in the clothes? Tell me!" Ying Er squeezed further under the bed, trying to grab the bundle of clothing.

"It's nothing!"

"If I catch you, you're dead meat!" Garen clung onto both of Ying Er's legs while she crawled forward in an attempt to break free.

Garen put his weight on her from behind, but he didn't dare to exert too much force, so all he could do was keep a light hold on her. Incidentally, he exerted too little force; Ying Er managed to free herself, and she lunged forward.

Bang!

"Ouch! That hurt…"

Ying Er hit her forehead on the underside of the bed, and her body curled back.

Behind her, Garen suddenly felt that his head was stuffy—he was inside his sister's skirt.

Round buttocks covered by black pantyhose were inches from his face; he could even see a hint of white underneath. His nose almost touched the skin of her buttocks.

The smell of girly fragrance mixed with a hint of sweat wafted into his nasal cavity, instinctively causing him to inhale.

At that moment, both were completely frozen.

In front, Ying Er didn't dare to move a muscle. A blush spread over her face, neck, and the entirety of her body.

She could distinctly feel Garen's face on her bottom—he had probably seen everything under her skirt.

Garen's mind was in a state of chaos. The most attractive part of a girl's body was all of a sudden right in front of him, and he didn't know how to respond.

Knock knock knock.

Someone knocked on the door.

"Are you two done playing in there? Time for you to wash up and go to bed! You have class tomorrow!" their father, Eisen, shouted from the doorway.

Both their hearts skipped a beat. It was nerve-racking.

If their father saw them in this state…

"Yup, almost done!" Garen snapped out of it and frantically shouted in reply.

They waited until the footsteps of their father leaving gradually faded.

Garen leaped out from under the bed in an instant.

He was then followed by Ying Er, with her hands covering her buttocks. Her face was red as she hung her head low; she didn’t dare look at Garen.

"I'm off to bed," she mumbled softly, then quickly opened the door and left.

Garen took a deep breath and sat on his bed. At this moment, he felt a strange calm wash over him.

That bout of ambiguous tension had oddly suppressed his anxiety and panic from the previous event of having killed someone.

There was still a faint aroma of Ying Er in the room. Garen sat on his bed until the lights in Ying Er's room went out. He then went out to find a clothes-drying pole and used it to hook the bloodied clothes out from under the bed, then crept into the bathroom to wash them.

****************

A week later.

"Hey, old man, what's the latest? Any new stock that's particularly good? How about letting me have a look?"

Garen sat bored beside the table, fiddling with a golden button. Apparently, it was from the clothes of the famous Agate Queen who lived three hundred years ago.

"New stock? What new stock? That burglary cleared me out!" The old man was fumbling at the bookshelf. "That's right! I have a book here that you might appreciate. Think of it as the reward for comforting this old geezer in my moment of crisis."

"What book?"

"You'll see."

The old man continued rummaging through the bookshelf. Then, he took a stool and stepped on it, pulling out a large black hardcover book from the topmost shelf.

"Here, take it." The old man struggled down from the stool and handed the book to Garen.

Garen took the bulky black brick from the old man and wiped a thick layer of dust off the cover, revealing some unknown black text.

He turned to the first page.

In that instant, Garen's pupils shrunk slightly.

A huge gust of cool current poured into his palm and flowed to his head through his arm.

"Potential! It's Potential! So… so much energy!"

He didn't know how to react. There wasn't any indication when he first held the book, but when he opened it, he started absorbing Potential.

His heart beat unnaturally fast. Garen glanced over the rapidly increasing Potential figures at the bottom of his vision and looked directly at the content on the page of the book.

The yellowing pages were crammed with an unknown text. Garen flipped through the book page by page. Some black-and-white sketches were occasionally interspersed in between the text.

The pictures were mostly weird, irregular geometric lines, which looked as much like a design for a mechanical contraption as it did a map for a complex terrain. They were densely marked with text and tiny symbols.

Garen didn't have a clue what the content meant, but that didn't stop him from absorbing Potential from the book. Turning it page by page, time slowly crept away.

Half an hour later…

Garen slowly closed the book and let out a long sigh.

"Finished going through it?" The old man squinted to look at the cover carefully; a trace of disappointment flashed over his eyes.

"Yeah, done. This is definitely a precious ancient antique!" Garen definitively said.

"You don't say." The old man seemed to relax a bit more, as if relieved of a burden. "Alright, I'm closing early today. You go ahead, I still have something to take care of."

Garen took a look at the sky outside. The sun had completely disappeared below the horizon, and only a residual trace of red stained the clouds.

"Fine, I'll be leaving first then. See you tomorrow."

"Well, beat it kid!" the old man jokingly added.

"Oh yeah, how's the progress with Detective Quicksilver?" Garen turned to ask.

"There was an explosion in Kyora Town just outside the city, and Detective Quicksilver was injured. He's in the hospital now." Old Man Gregor shook his head and sighed. "Even the famous Detective Quicksilver has faced a setback; looks like there's no hope of getting my belongings back now."

"That's not necessarily the case. I looked up Detective Quicksilver, he's no ordinary guy. The mystery of the stolen million-dollar oil painting in New Zealand, the nine serial killings in West Riyadh, and cracking the case of the torch legend, etc. The guy keeps facing new opponents, and keeps heading to new places to solve riddles; you can tell he enjoys solving cases. From how I see it, this golden bracelet won't be an exception," Garen comfortingly said.

"Thanks for your kind words. Get going now, I need to close up." The old man waved his hand to rush Garen out.

"Alright." Garen walked out of the store carrying his bag.

He looked at the Potential points at the bottom of his vision.

Potential: 179%. It was around 58% initially, and that was due to the increase after meeting that car on the night he killed someone.

"That book…" Amidst his delight, his eyes showed a trace of doubt. "Something feels off."

******

After Garen left, Old Man Gregor closed the front door and went back to sitting in front of the bookshelf. He opened the black hardcover and gently caressed the pages as a complicated expression emerged on his face.

It wasn't after a long while before he finished looking through the entire book.

"I should have known this would happen, but surprisingly I can't help but want to cling on to something…"

The old man shook his head and slowly closed the pages.

He kept turning the pages until he finally closed the cover. The black text on the cover had turned dark red, as if fresh blood had flowed through each stroke and coagulated.

Chapter 17: The Gathering

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Ever since the day he killed someone, Garen had been waiting for the other person’s next move. He remained near the proximity of his home and mindlessly wandered around the school. After he had become completely familiar with the surrounding area, he increased his vigilance. He didn’t know when that pair of crimson eyes would appear once again.

After all, no master would let the murder of their men be without consequence.

Ding.

The crisp chime signaling the end of class shook Garen out of his daydreaming.

He sat at his desk, stretching his neck, and looked around.

Most of his classmates sat in place and stretched, some of them walked around the room, and some began to yell at people to purchase items.

The entire class had become raucous immediately after class.

"Are you going to the competition? Garen?" With a brown blazer, Kalidor sat in front of Garen’s seat. He pushed a slim boy to the side. "Sorry, let me squeeze in a little bit."

The youth mumbled a bit but didn’t say much.

Garen looked at him, speechless.

"It’s the archery and sword art competition right? I don’t have any plans to compete right now, but my sister will be part of the archery contest. I will be there to cheer her on. Where did Fayne and Jack go?"

"I don’t know. Those two were acting pretty suspicious right after class. Who knows where they went?" Kalidor shrugged. Because of his peculiar taste in fashion and carelessness in appearance, not a lot of people enjoyed his company. In a similar vein, due to Garen’s low-income family background and cold personality, only someone as bold as Kalidor got along with Garen.

Therefore, the two had a closer relationship compared to Fayne and Jack. Including Ai Fei, they were a five-man gang. The closeness in their relationships, however, differed.

"I will only be there for the archery competition." Garen didn’t give it too much thought. He felt quite distant from the contest at school because of how dull it usually was. Maybe it was because he had already fought someone to the death, but to him, the competitions were as boring as it could get.

Kalidor pouted as he displayed an expression that said ‘I knew you were going to say that’.

"Since you have time right now, I need you to help me with something." He looked around and dragged the studying Ai Fei look to the side.

"What are you doing?? I’m studying."

"You’ll know once we get there."

The three gathered together and Kalidor began explaining the situation.

Because a friend of his was back in town, he wanted to bring the two of them to their reunion.

Garen and Ai Fei were his close friends at school, so he wanted them to be there. Since Fayne and Jack’s girlfriends needed to be at Xu Xiao’s competition, they could not attend due to the conflict in their schedules.

"All my best friends are attending the gathering. My big brother, whom I respect the most, is hosting it. You guys have to come this time! Just treat it as a favor for me."

"Why do you need us to be there at the gathering?" Ai Fei was puzzled.

"My family found me a girl that I am supposed to get engaged to. I want you guys to give me some opinions at this gathering…" Kalidor said in a shy tone.

"Engaged…" Ai Fei and Garen wereas shocked at the news.

"How old are you, to be getting engaged now…" Garen had a peculiar expression.

"16 years old, is there a rule that says I can’t be engaged at 16?" Kalidor asked defiantly.

Garen paused for a moment.

He wanted to ask Old Man Gregor to see the book again. But the old man had become increasingly stubborn for some reason, so his answer was always no. The Dojo was about to pay out its student allowance as well as host an internal competition to finalize the standings. He also needed to keep his guard up against the man with the bloody eyes. After all, he did kill someone of theirs.

[The good thing is that there’s no news related to the murder that day yet. After the police took care of the crime scene, the detective couldn’t find anything useful. The technology is too behind in this world. If it happened on earth, they could easily use surveillance to identify me as a prime suspect.]

Garen was glad that chaos filled this barely industrial world.

[Even on earth, there are still plenty of people who committed murder but still remained free. Without the assistance of technology, who knows how many truths are still hidden in the darkness. No wonder a detective like Dale Quicksilver can have such a renowned reputation here.]

He was not afraid that they would find his family. It was dark that day, so it was hard to recognize his face. Nobody knew that he went to the dojo through that desolated street either. Without a name as their lead, it would be impossible to identify someone in Huais Shan City out of the tens of thousands of people that lived there. It would be as difficult as searching for a needle in the vast sea. There was no way they could trace any of this back to his family.

After giving it a thought, he felt it was necessary to relax for a bit. A gathering of his friends would be an excellent choice. If he continued to suppress himself, he would go insane before the enemy even showed up.

"The competition starts in a couple of days. Let me be clear, I only have time for the archery competition."

"It’s only for a few days, don’t worry, we won’t miss your sister’s competition." Kalidor gave Garen an "I understand" look.

"I don’t have any problems, let me know when we leave." Ai Fei concurred without hesitation.

"Okay, oh Ai Fei, can I borrow your physics homework?"

"Why don’t you ask Garen?"

"His handwriting is horrendous."

"Go screw yourself! Your writing is uglier than mine, yet you don’t see me complaining!"

Not only Kalidor, Garen himself also regularly copied homework off of Ai Fei. He didn’t know every subject, especially in Foreign Languages. They were learning the renowned ancient Mengdiyan language. The language was incredibly difficult to pronounce with its tongue-twisting syllables. The abrupt tone combined with the peculiar sound made it impossible to memorize.

After attempting multiple times yet still only managing to achieve a score of 30 on his tests, he ultimately gave up on the language altogether. She was the only girl in the gang of five, and was also gorgeous to boot. Ai Fei was the catalyst and core to their desire to study. She could solve any problem they had.

*****************************

Three days later.

In nightfall, Garen and Ai Fei followed Kalidor to a hotel in the downtown of Huai sShan City.

"We are here," Kalidor said as he led the way. Behind him, Garen was in a black shirt, and Ai Fei was dressed up in a light pink dress.

Above the hotel, a sign named: Mila’s Night Star hung in the night sky. Below the name hung ten incandescent light bulbs. Light bulbs were not too common in this world due to the rarity of thin wiring and cost. Only the wealthy families could afford them.

A continuous wave of cars stopped in front of the luxurious rectangular door as they dropped customers off.

"My brother is a great guy; I’ll introduce you guys once he is here." Kalidor looked excited. "He created a business by himself in the Eastern Sea province!"

"Look how happy you are. It sounds like you’re going to meet your believed." Garen responded as he followed. Ai Fei giggled beside him.

"Can you say something nice for once in your life?"

A waiter greeted them as they walked through the door. After politely asking for their names, he led them to a grand hall on the second floor.

As they approached the hall, Kalidor waved at the teenagers in the hall. He looked quite popular amongst them.

"Why don’t you go and say hi? We’ll make ourselves comfortable here." Ai Fei saw that Kalidor was struggling to keep up with all the conversations and understandingly offered.

"Okay, I’ll be back in a moment. There are drinks on the table, make yourself comfortable…" Before he finished his sentence, Kalidor was dragged away by a short-haired man.

Garen shrugged. He started to think as he watched the group of people inside the hall. As soon as Kalidor entered the room, he became the center of attention. His background was not as simple as he had claimed before.

"Let’s walk around. It looks great in here."

"Mhmm."

A graceful man was standing at the corner. His flawless skin and athletic figure almost resembled a woman’s. The fit white suit made him look appear extremely delicate and elegant. He casually chatted with the people surrounding him.

"Kalidor, we haven’t seen each other for a while. Why are you not saying hi? Who was the person that consistently yelled ‘brother, brother’ behind me?" The man saw the three of them approach and gave Kalidor a light punch.

His friends around him also giggled along.

"Brother Weimar, I am here. I came as soon as I saw your telegram. I didn’t dare stop for even a second," Kalidor said with a sour face.

"Okay, stop acting. I know you too well for your tricks to work! Let me introduce you." Weimar said to the group of friends around him, "Noble Stallone’s only child, Kalidor. The rest are old friends, but let us introduce ourselves to the two new friends here today."

He pointed at the blond boy and the girl with yellow pupils.

"William; his father, General William, is extremely close with Uncle Stallone. She is Jessie; the Kaifei International Hotel Chain is owned by her family."

When he introduced Jessie, he winked at Kalidor. Kalidor immediately knew that she was the girl that his family found.

"Since you guys are Brother Weimar’s friend, you guys are my friends as well. If you guys ever need anything in Huais Shan, don’t hesitate to find me." With a forthright statement, Kalidor pumped his chest.

William nodded without saying a word.

"Then I’ll have to count on you here." Jessie smiled at him as she returned a wink.

"No problem."

"Why don’t you introduce your friends to us?" Jessie looked at Garen and Ai Fei in the not-far-off distance.

"They are all my friends from school. The person with purple hair is called…"

"That’s okay, let’s grab something to eat. I’ll have to meet some other friends. You guys keep chatting."

Weimar interrupted him. Then, with a smile, he walked into the crowd with a blue-colored martini.

Chapter 18: The Gathering 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Kalidor was stunned. He wanted to continue introducing his friends, but Jessie brought up a new topic to stop him right away. It was quite obvious that none of them cared about Garen and Ai Fei’s names. They could tell that they were not in the same league as the others just by looking at the way they dressed.

Weimar walked up to the stage in the center of the hall and announced the beginning of the feast. He told everybody to enjoy the banquet. All the youngsters raised their glasses of wine or juice and laughed. After some emotional speeches, Weimar got down from the stage and returned to Kalidor’s side. The band took his place.

"By the way, Wei Sijia just left Kinstria. Her flight passed Huaishan City, so she decided to take a rest here. I invited her today; she’ll drive over later. I guess she must be on the way now. Let’s finish eating and then go get her." Weimar drank some of the Blood Wine in the glass.

"So soon?" Kalidor frowned. "I have friends here…"

"What does it matter? I’ll go explain to your friends and let them go home by themselves. It has been too long since our last gathering. It is such a rare opportunity this time."

"How about we take them with us? They are all my friends, and we can introduce them to the others," Kalidor hesitantly said.

Weimar showed an indifferent smile on his face.

"Kalidor, I hope that tonight it will be just a night of old friends. I don’t think it is a good idea to bring others involved." He saw Kalidor hesitating, so he continued, "I thought you liked Wei Sijia the most? Now that she finally got a chance to come, you don’t even want to welcome her in person? We only have four cars and we don’t have seats for them if you don’t come."

"Come on, don’t screw it up. If you feel that it’s too difficult to talk to your friends, I will do it."

Kalidor was quiet. He suddenly regretted that he had invited Garen and Ai Fei to the party. He didn’t know that his Brother Weimar, whom he had always been respecting, would become so unreasonable… Suddenly, the great image about Brother Weimar in his heart started to become dim. But no matter what, they were still friends who grew up together.

"I urh… Let’s see what happens next," he answered in a low and hesitant voice.

Weimar frowned as the smile on his face gradually disappeared. He tapped on Kalidor’s shoulder and said, "Just think about it."

Garen and Ai Fei had been hanging around the food table and eating since they got in the hall.

They knew nobody except Kalidor in the party. Aside from them, there were also other new arrivals. They were about seventeen and eighteen years old, and always got a warm welcome from their friends in the party.

They were the only two who didn’t know anyone else. They just watched as people talked and laughed in their own small groups, causing them to feel out of place.

"Let’s just eat since we can’t feel at ease. Kalidor’s surrounded right now anyway. We can’t let him leave all of his friends to just accompany us, can we?" Garen talked to Ai Fei in a low voice, then picked a plate and walked away to get more food.

Ai Fei truly felt uncomfortable just standing there. She listlessly walked to the food table and learned to pick up a plate like the others did. Cautiously, she used a spoon to drink the soup in her bowl.

Except Ai Fei and Garen, everybody was either rich or powerful. All those people in this shiny and luxurious banquet hall were so dazzling.

Compared to them, the two-hundred-dollar dress and the one hundred dollar boots on her were very conspicuous and out of place. She had seen most of the food on the table before at the supermarket. They were very expensive, and any dish cost much more than all the clothes on her.

Hah…

A laugh sounded beside her.

"Dear sister, that soup is not for drinking. It is for rinsing the mouth." A young girl couldn’t help laughing.

A blush appeared on Ai Fei’s face as she almost choked. She put down the plate and took a napkin to wipe her mouth.

"I… I recognized it wrong…" Even her neck turned red; she kept her head low and didn’t dare to look up at the girl.

"That is such an obvious pot of soup… You do know what a rinsing soup is, don’t you?" That girl laughed again. Another young girl walked over and whispered to her, and then they both laughed while covering their mouths.

Ai Fei just stood there with her head low, her face and neck red, feeling as if she was burning up. She didn’t know whether she should leave or stay, wishing she could just bury herself into the ground.

"What does it matter? Is the rinsing soup so poisonous we can’t even drink it?" Garen walked over and spoke with a frown.

He was also wearing hundred-dollar clothes, but he didn’t feel restrained at all. In his eyes, those young guys and girls were all some little chickens he could easily defeat. After murdering someone, he now had a different attitude towards ordinary people. Especially when he thought of the fact that the price of a life in this world was so low, he settled down a bit. To him, the only thing that mattered was strength.

"It’s just some rinsing soup. I like it too. What’s so funny?" Garen filled a bowl and drank the entire thing in one big gulp. The rinsing soup tasted a bit sweet with a minty flavor, and was not that bad for a drink.

"It’s fine, it’s fine…" When the girl saw that Garen was so at ease about it, she felt that it would be embarrassing for her to continue making a big deal. She looked at Garen and Ai Fei with a strange expression before saying, "Please go on…" The two young girls slowly walked away. They couldn’t help laughing again as they walked further away.

Garen frowned. Once he saw the girls were gone, he looked at Ai Fei.

"Alright, ignore what other people think. Do whatever you want to."

Ai Fei nodded in silence.

"Should we go to Kalidor and tell him we feel like leaving? It’s a decent place, but the people in it are not," Garen casually spoke as he shrugged his shoulders.

He looked at Ai Fei, and the latter, still red faced, meekly nodded. She was so embarrassed that she didn’t even look up. Speechless, Garen turned around and walked to Kalidor.

Kalidor was talking to a girl with a pair of bright eyes. They were just idly chatting. Most of the time, the girl would be the one to bring up a topic, and Kalidor would just perfunctorily answer her. When he saw Garen walking over, he knew that he was finally about to be saved.

"I may need a word with my friend over there. I think he needs to talk to me. Excuse me." He finally had an excuse to get away, so he said so and walked to Garen.

"Hugh…"

Kalidor took a long breath out as he approached Garen.

"See? That beautiful girl with long dark golden hair is the one I am engaged to. What do you think?"

"Not bad. Isn’t she good?" Garen confusedly said.

"She is too good… I feel useless when compared to her…" Kalidor looked frustrated.

"Alright, I am just here to say that Ai Fei and I are going to head out. You should just spend more time with your friends."

"I was thinking about introducing you to…" Kalidor didn’t finish. He turned silent for a moment, and then said, "Well then… I will see you off."

"No need, we are good. I’ll walk Ai Fei back first. Anyway, I go for a run every night, and I’m used to it. But in reality, you shouldn’t have invited Ai Fei and me tonight, right?" Garen said as his voice turned less and less audible.

Kalidor’s expression gradually turned dull.

"I am fine, but you know Ai Fei’s family; they’re even worse off than mine. She was recruited as a special excellence student and being here definitely made her nervous. Just now, she even drank the rinsing soup. She’s a girl you know…."

"It’s my fault," Kalidor spoke in a low voice. "I thought it was just a few people talking freely. I thought it would be simple, but I didn’t expect it to be so big…"

"You shouldn’t blame yourself, you’re just too kind. Alright, we are off. Enjoy your time." Garen patted his shoulder and ended the conversation. Kalidor opened his mouth as if about to say something, but couldn’t manage in the end. He could only watch as Garen returned to Ai Fei’s side before leaving with her through the back door in the small hall. Asides from Kalidor, no one else paid them any attention.

Garen and Ai Fei left the hotel; they walked along the roads of suburbs, beside them were cars running past.

After that humiliation, Ai Fei looked like another person. Along the way, she didn’t utter a single word.

"It is fine. Don’t think too much about others’ views. After today, they will never show up in our sights again, and we will eventually forget each other." Garen was comforting her. "And don’t blame Kalidor. He is just a fool. He didn’t think about such a situation."

"I don’t blame him." Ai Fei tidied her ponytail. "It was my fault for being ignorant. Why should I blame others?"

"Don’t think too much about it." Garen tapped on her shoulder. "You are still who you are, same as who you were. Don’t let such a tiny thing affect your happiness." The truth was, he had accidentally discovered Ai Fei’s secret when he was hanging around in the city earlier.

The stubborn girl had a mother who was seriously sick at home, and her younger sister and brother were depending on her too. Her father left home because of his gambling debt. She had to gradually pay it on her own. Luckily, she won the scholarship every year as a special gifted student in the Shengying Nobles Academy. She could use that money on her family, and she also worked after school to make more. All the money she earned was only barely enough to pay the tuition fees of her brother and sister and the medical fees of her mother.

The girl had been working so hard. For other students, it might be boring to study in school, but for her, it was a god-given time of relaxation.

"Alright, don’t be depressed…" Garen was just about to talk when he caught a familiar outline of a figure in his peripheral vision, making him quickly avert his eyes. "Come on. I need to go home after I send you back."

"Don’t worry, I can go home by myself. You don’t have to come with me." Ai Fei shook her head. Subconsciously, she looked at Garen with suspicion in her eyes. "You can go, I’m fine."

Garen knew that she didn’t want people to know the real situation of her family. He had things to do now anyway, so he nodded. "Ok then. You take care of yourself and just go straight home. Don’t hang around outside too long. It may not be safe."

Ai Fei quietly nodded. She took a left turn at the corner of the road.

Garen stood behind her watching her off. When he saw her disappear in that corner, he tidied his collar and walked to a dark alley on the street. After a while, he disappeared into the shadows.

Chapter 19: Exclusion 1

Translator:EndlessFantasy Translation

Editor:EndlessFantasy Translation

After being followed by Garen through the alley for a while, the black shadow in front suddenly turned left and ducked out of the alley.

Garen avoided a puddle and continued his pursuit with light, careful footsteps. No matter what, he had to figure out the background of the person he killed the other day, whether they would be able to trace his identity or not. At this point, it wasn't just about Attribute points but, more importantly, about the safety of his family and himself.

He turned into a dirty alley even narrower than the last one. The sound of a man arguing with a woman could be heard from the apartments above. The whole alley was filled with the stench of rotting food and waste.

The person in front was kneeling beside a garbage bin with his hand inside it, digging for something. There were two homeless people sleeping soundly on either side of him.

Garen quietly stood at the corner of the alley and peered into it, borrowing the faint light radiating down from the block above.

After a while, the person rummaged through the bin and dug out a black leather purse. He stuck his hand inside the purse, felt around a little and pulled out a small bronze key. After pocketing the key, he quickly looked around and continued to move forward.

Garen retracted his head and hid behind the corner wall when the person turned. He slowly stuck his head out again after waiting for the sound of the footsteps to fade away.

Without warning, the moment he stuck his head out, Garen felt a stabbing pain in his waist.

He reflexively swung his right elbow backward.

Bang!

Someone let out a muffled groan. The elbow strike had left them staggering. The person tried to turn around and escape, but only managed a few steps before stumbling onto the ground. They struggled a few times to get up but failed.

Garen’s heart was thumping, but it was already his second real fight. Coupled with the changes in his mentality previously, this time was completely different from the first. He wasn’t as panicked compared to before.

He suppressed his nerves and took a few deep breaths. He examined his waist where he was stabbed: there was a tear in his clothes, apparently caused by a small dagger-like weapon, but his skin was uninjured.

"If it wasn’t for me learning Explosive Fist Arts for self-defense which solidified my body to an extent comparable to the Body Hardening Technique, that stab would have killed me." Garen looked at the tear. It was right at where his kidney was. A shiver ran down his spine.

Garen walked up to the man on the ground. The man held a black dagger in his right hand. His clothes were dirty, as if they hadn't been washed in a long time. He looked like an ordinary homeless person.

"You won't be able to live for long now. Master James will avenge me!" The man let out a low sinister laugh and glared at Garen with his beady green eyes. A trace of blood spilled out from the corner of his mouth, his head bent askew, and he was dead. There was a hint of black in the blood that spilled from his mouth: poison.

The man had committed suicide before Garen could manage to even ask about the situation. Garen crouched to check his pulse and breathing: he was indeed dead.

Garen felt like he had been dragged into a war between two forces. The man had mistaken him for a member of the opposing force, and committed suicide without a second thought just to prevent himself from leaking any information.

The harshness and cruelty of this warrior, so ready to die, made Garen shudder.

"He probably wasn't sent to specifically tail me. The person in front must have come to retrieve something, and this guy here was probably sent to kill me after he realized that I was following that person. He could also be a spy from the other organization… Seems highly unlikely that I've been exposed." Garen breathed a sigh of relief after analyzing the general situation. It was clear that his accidental killing had been mistaken for a deliberate act committed by the opposing side.

"No wonder when I stopped the car the man so decisively ordered for me to be killed. I was just in the wrong place at the wrong time…"

The more Garen thought about the situation, the more he realized that these were the facts.

He looked around him, there was no movement. The snoring of the homeless men and the arguing voices from the block above could still constantly be heard, with some feral cats in heat making mating call sounds from time to time.

Garen bent over to examine the assassin and found a gold coin with black and gold stripes in the inner pocket of his coat. Without taking a second look at it, he shoved the gold coin in his pocket and left the same way he came.

He crept out of the alley when the crowd thinned. He acted as if nothing had happened and went around the city center in circles. It wasn't until the bell tower in the city chimed the end of the hour that he jogged home in a hurry.

Creak… Bang.

Garen shut the front door, changed into slippers and went into the living room.

The oil lamp in the living room was lit. His father, Eisen Lombard, was reading the newspaper on the sofa with his legs crossed into a figure four. He was wearing black pajamas, and there was a slight twitch in his brows.

Eisen was a plump middle-aged man with messy indigo hair and a full white beard; he looked like a passionate football coach.

When he saw that Garen was back, he lifted his plump face and gave him a little nod, but didn't say a word.

"Where's mom?" Garen tried to act naturally as he removed his jacket and hung it on the coat rack by the door.

"Since it's a holiday, she's gone to the block across the street for coffee at Madame Cadney's," Eisen answered casually. "You only came back after the bell chimed. Don't stay out for too long next time, it gets dangerous outside when it's late. There have been a few murders in the city recently. They've all happened in places where there were very few people about. Do take care to avoid such places."

"Yeah, I know. I heard some of my schoolmates mentioning it." Garen nodded.

"Especially you, always running around in places with very few people."

"Okay."

"Be careful when you’re walking around. Your sister has just gone to bed. She has preparatory practice for the tournament tomorrow." Eisen put down the paper, finished his coffee and said, "Since you're back, I'm going off to bed too. Don't wait up for mom, she'll probably be out late."

"Alright." Garen rested on the sofa for a bit, drank a glass of water, and watched his father close the bedroom door behind him. He waited for a while longer until he heard the lights go off inside the room. He then got up, washed up, switched off the living room lights, and went into his own room.

He sat by his desk and switched on the desk lamp. Then, he carefully took out the dark gold coin from his pocket and examined it under the light.

The gold coin was the size of a walnut and was as thick as a normal coin. Engraved on the face of it was a double mast galleon in full sail against the wind. Above the galleon was a snake with its mouth open, ready to bite.

On the bottom of the coin was a number: 1521.

On its flip side was a knight's suit of armor. A sword ran through the armor from within, angled upwards, and a helmet hung from the tip. A garland encircled the whole armor.

Garen rubbed on the coin repeatedly. He could make out a dark golden color beneath the black paint from a few spots on the flip side of the gold coin.

As he pressed a finger to the dark gold spots, and the Potential on the bottom of his vision jolted.

From 179% to 180.

And then it stopped moving.

"That's it?"

Garen silently put down the gold coin.

Ever since he’d accrued a few Attribute points at the old man's place, he hadn't used any of them, but instead saved them for the time being.

He originally intended to add them to the White Cloud Secret Method, but later considered that it would probably be better to add them to the Explosive Fist Arts. After all, that was the technique that would give the best results in a short amount of time. On top of that, he hadn't been successful in getting anything out of the book ever since he borrowed it from the old man, which made him even more reluctant to use the rare Attribute points on anything.

"I thought I could find something substantial on him. For a member of an organization that’s stolen so many antiques, all he had on him was a gold coin. Should I deem him a side character in the grand scheme of things?"

He shook his head, then hid the gold coin in the desk drawer.

"Since this is a misunderstanding, it should end here. I can't keep getting dragged into it." Recalling how he was stabbed without warning earlier, he broke into a cold sweat.

"If I hadn’t trained in Explosive Fist Arts which hardened my skin, that stab could have killed me. Fortunately, he was weak. If it were someone stronger, and with some poison on the knife…"

When he thought of this, a shiver ran down his spine.

"I'll just stay focused on going to school and practicing martial arts. This business is too dangerous. It's better if I just leave it to professional detectives like Dale Quicksilver."

He made up his mind not to meddle in this matter anymore. The Bronze Cross Emblem was valuable, but there was a new source of Potential from the Old Man. Thus, even though he could no longer get any more regular absorption from it, Garen's desire to get the emblem back gradually faded.

"I'll use the last bit of Potential on the White Cloud Secret Method. The sooner I add to it, the faster my strength and physicality can begin to increase."

He pondered for a second, and finally cast his line of sight onto the White Cloud Secret Method in the Skills pane.

Slowly, the stream of qi from his brain flowed out and entered one of the items under the White Cloud Secret Method.

The words gave a shake and gradually blurred, upgrading from 'intermediate' to 'advanced'.

Snap!

A crisp sound rang through his brain. The 'advanced' instantly blurred and reverted to 'intermediate'. A current flooded back into Garen's brain.

"What's going on?" He frowned and carefully reviewed the Skills pane.

A new symbol had emerged after 'White Cloud Secret Method'.

Even though he didn't know how to pronounce it, Garen strangely understood its meaning: "Information Incomplete".

"It seems that the teachings of the Secret Method were incomplete. The key to the advanced Secret Method should be in the hands of the dojo masters and key disciples," Garen deduced the truth of the matter.

He thought about it, then focused his sight on Explosive Fist Arts. Similarly, after the Attribute points were added to it, the words blurred then reverted to 'elementary'. There was a new symbol after it, the meaning of which Garen again immediately understood.

"Does the intermediate level of Explosive Fist Arts require external drug stimulation as a simultaneous therapy? Otherwise, it would harm the body and mind…" He was well aware that, to have been initiated in Explosive Fist Arts without any assistance, was extremely fortuitous.

It would be the same for the White Cloud Secret Method. The dojo would naturally want to maintain certain core elements within their control. It's not likely that they would give it all away in one go, otherwise they wouldn't be so established.

"So it seems that, to enhance my martial art powers, I have to elevate my status within the dojo." Ever since he transmigrated here, almost all of his time had been spent on his fascination with martial arts. Something that he could only dream of on Earth, he could actually be exposed to here. This had always made Garen excited. And now that he understood the importance of martial arts and the security it provided, his pursuit of it had become more fanatical.

Although he was encountering some problems, he wasn't too concerned. As long as he could participate in the dojo's internal qualifying tournament, he could attain a good ranking and gain the attention of the high-level core figures.

"Since I can't add to Skills, I'll just add to my basic Potentials." He shifted his sight and lingered on the basic Potential pane.

Strength: 0.53. Agility: 0.23. Physicality: 0.33. Intelligence: 0.36.

"I've added to Vitality, Strength and Intelligence before. I should just add to Agility this time, and check out what effect that has." Garen held a "might as well add to it" attitude toward Attribute points.

Compared to his ordinary peers, he would have a better starting point no matter which items he added his Attribute points to.

After all, he had an ordinary body enhanced by Attribute points.

On top of that, the stabilizing effect of Potentials meant that once he reached a certain level of a Potential, even if he didn't really train much, the body could still maintain the Potential at its peak and wouldn't regress. If he didn't practice martial arts to build up his physicality under such favorable circumstances, even he felt that it would be a sinful waste.

Chapter 20: Exclusion 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"The physical test results are out. The results detail resilience, resistance and physical tenacity. Strength decides explosive power, physical strength, and body shape. When intelligence goes up, it becomes much easier to learn. Now, all that’s left is agility."

He focused on the Agility icon.

Soon, it jumped to 0.33 from 0.23.

Within the instant during which the number changed, Garen felt his body turn lighter. His sight turned dim, and his brain was blank as if many things had been moved out of his body.

He felt like he had taken off a heavy iron suit. His body became incredibly light, and he felt like he could jump onto the roof with just a single stomp on the floor.

"From what I have concluded, the different attributes of ordinary people should only be around 0.3. Originally, my speed was lower than the others, and that’s why I ran very slowly. These numbers are hard to measure though. It would have been better if all these numbers could be converted with a normal human’s abilities as 1 instead."

As soon as this thought crossed his mind, the numbers in his sight began to gradually change.

After more than 10 seconds, the numbers had completely changed.

Strength: 1.77; Agility: 1.10; Vitality: 1.03; Intelligence: 1.20; Potential: 80%.

"So the display will change according to the desires I have in my mind. I guess my strength should be over one and a half times the strength of ordinary people. No wonder I could break a thick glass plane and pass the 200-pound sand bag challenge so easily ."

He turned off the light and opened the window for some fresh air, after which he took off his clothes and lay on his bed. With his entire body filled with the feeling of lightness, he eventually stopped thinking and, very soon, he fell asleep.

He didn’t know how much time had passed since he fell asleep. When he woke up and opened his eyes, he suddenly heard the door of his room being opened; a short figure slid in and stood beside the door, quietly looking at him. It was Ying Er.

She was wearing the school uniform, which had a short skirt. On her slim waist was a silver zipper. The skirt was only enough to cover her thighs, and her black pantyhose was obvious.

"Brother, in fact… In fact… I…"

Garen drowsily got up.

"Ying Er? What are you doing here so late?" He looked at his sister on the bedside. Under the moonlight, he felt that his sister seemed to be more beautiful and purer. When she unconsciously grabbed her short skirt with her head low, all he could see was the pink on her face.

"Brother… You… don’t get close to other girls… Can you do that?" Ying Er’s voice was as small as an ant.

"Are you talking about Ai FeI? We’re just friends." Garen thought about the night when he walked Ai Fei back. With the suspicion in Ai Fei’s eyes while she looked at him, he knew what she meant.

It looked like Ai Fei suspected that Garen liked her, and that that was why he always protected her. Because of that, she didn’t allow him to send her home. It wasn’t simply not letting others know her home address; it was also turning down his pursuit.

"I’ve just been turned down. Now, my sister is expressing her love to me? Ying Er… Only you are so naive to think that your brother is the best. You think all girls will like me, like I will be snatched away from you at any second. Well, not every girl thinks so." Garen felt bitter in his heart.

"So is it that woman who keeps on pestering you? Annoying…!" Ying Er curled her hand into a fist. "As long as you promise me you will never talk to that Ai Fei anymore, I will… I will stop beating you up."

Garen twitched his mouth and didn’t say anything. He felt the words "stop beating you up" were so weird when they came out of his sister’s mouth.

Ying Er didn’t get any response. She lowered her head a little bit more, thinking that Garen was refusing.

"As long as you promise… Then I will… I can… I will let you…"

She stepped ahead, took his hand, and slowly pulled it beneath her skirt.

Garen was frozen in place. From his right hand, he felt a warm and moist feeling that engulfed his entire body. His blood began to boil and, with his body's rising temperature, a thirst overwhelmed him. His private part was as hard as an iron stick, causing him to feel a bit of pain.

Finally, he couldn’t hold it!

"Ying Er!" He finally couldn’t help it anymore. He suddenly sat up and grabbed his sister’s waist with his other hand.

"Bang!"

"Ouch…"

Garen opened his eyes.

"Which ceiling is this…" He looked confused. He reached out his left hand and found his fingernails were bloody. "No… It should be a familiar ceiling, the new me is just still not used to it yet…"

"So it was a dream… I was wondering how Ying Er’s personality changed so much. She actually came to me late after midnight." He looked at the ceiling, a red background with black lattices. He felt so lazy that he didn’t want to move, and he was also a bit disappointed.

While the cold wind blew into the room through the windows, his bed felt warm and cozy. Inside and outside were two seemingly different worlds.

"I guess I have been infected by this world… In this world, relatives further than three generations could be married. Let alone Ying Er, my sister who is not actually my real sister. It is quite normal that I imagine something about her."

He slowly took away the quilt and looked at the nightstand. On the edge of the table was a scratch; it must have been his nails that made it.

He got up from the bed, grabbed his clothes, and put them on. He added a cotton underclothes under his shirt; it appeared a formal suit of long pants and black coat.

"Mom, there is a hole in my clothes. What should I do?" There came his sister’s voice from the living room.

"Take it to Mark the tailor. Your brother’s clothes were ripped yesterday. Get them done together." The voice of his mother, Vania, sounded.

"’Nia, hurry. We have to go. The company car is about to arrive," his father urged. "Where is my tie? My red one!"

"In the closet."

"It isn’t there."

"Then use the black one!"

"Fine, so be it. Move faster!"

"Ying Er, please come and help me with the zipper on my back. It’s jammed!"

"Okay, mother."

Garen opened the bedroom door and stood beside it.

In the living room, his father, Eisen, was busy with his tie, and his mother was putting on a long dress with his sister’s help.

"Are you up, Garen? Our breakfast is bread, milk and an egg for each of us. If it’s not warm enough, put it into the oven for a few seconds. We’re leaving now, we’re going to be late." His mother zipped the dress and tidied it up. She rushed out through the door with her bag in hand.

"Hurry and eat, then go to school. I’m off!" Eisen left too.

Bang.

The door was closed.

His sister took a breath out and turned around to look at Garen.

"Hurry up and go wash yourself. We’ve got a bus to catch after breakfast. It is almost seven!"

"Okay." Garen walked to the washroom. He twisted the faucet and splashed some cold water on his face.

The water made his skin tense up. He didn’t feel sleepy at all anymore.

"Today is the day of my competition. Promise me that you will come and see me," Ying Er shouted from outside the washroom as she dressed up. "If you dare go watch the girls’ swimming game like you did last time, I’ll make you beg for mercy!" She raised her fist and shook it.

"Alright, alright…" Garen helplessly shook his head. He had been living for dozens of years, so how would he be controlled by the emotions of a young boy? The dream must have been a reflection of a memory from his past.

Hmm, it must be.

Facing the mirror, he tried to convince himself.

In that mirror, there was a young man who had dark purple hair and red eyes. His skin was pale and exquisite. There was nothing like a pimple on him. He was also emitting a natural sense of confidence and vigor.

"Come on, stop it. Let me use it!"

Ying Er brushed up close to him from his right. She moved her head so that both she and Garen could use the mirror at the same time. She cautiously tidied her hair before looking at Garen’s face. All of a sudden, a blush appeared on her face.

"That face in the old days was a lot safer…" she murmured.

"What did you say?" Garen didn’t hear what she said.

"Nothing, hurry up."

It was still the same life: catching a bus, attending a class, and eating. There would be a competition in the afternoon, so the classes were cut short.

Garen followed the students in the school to the outdoor shooting field.

***

Students from different classes gathered together and formed groups one after another. Some of them even raised their hands holding wooden sticks with banners saying "XXX Go For It". Some of them actually started yelling like a cheer squad.

The shooting field had two parts: the arrow targets and the shooting fence. The participants needed to shoot from the fence while aiming at the target on the other side. Their scores depended on the rings they would shoot.

Garen found a place on the left to watch the competition. There were some students and teachers around.

The sunlight seemed pale, and the temperature wasn’t too high.

Garen waited for a while. After three groups of people, it was finally Ying Er’s turn.

She was wearing a clean white shooting robe with a black pant-skirt. It looked like an ancient Chinese dress with black and white colors. She was wearing a pair of yellow gloves and, with one hand, she held a brown wooden bow which was over a meter long.

She slowly walked to the other two players; both of them were standing still on three shooting spots. They put on a brown leather chest plate, which covered half of their chest.

"Here comes Ying Er from Class 6 Grade 1, Ilya from Class 7 Grade 1, and David Jones from Class 8 Grade 1. Ying Er from Class 6 is an outstanding player in the Department of Archery. Yi Li Ya has won a medal in a competition in the city. David Jones has just began competing, so it must be quite a challenge for him this time…"

While holding a speaker, a teacher was loudly commentating.

"Elizabeth from Class 7 Grade 3 has shot five tens. A peak record like that is nearly impossible for others to break. Now, let’s see whether Ying Er or the next up Su Man can break the record."

Standing from afar, Garen looked at his sister, and Ying Er also looked back at him. He hurriedly smiled and waved his hand.

Ying Er felt calm. As the preparation sounded, she slowly raised and drew her bow.

Chapter 21: Core (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

From afar, Garen could see three contestants, including his sister. They gently released their bowstrings. Three lines of shadow flew out and nailed their targets.

His eyesight wasn't that good, but he managed to see that the arrows of the other contestants were slightly off the mark and Ying Er's arrow was much closer to the bull's-eye.

Cheers and boos roared from the crowd. Class 6, Ying Er's class, cheered the loudest.

The competition continued into the second round, followed by the third…

Garen didn't understand the rules at all. He just kept hearing the crowd cheer every time Ying Er fired an arrow. The classmates from Class 6 and all the female students were yelling Ying Er's name. It seemed that she was quite popular in school and not as subdued as when she was around their parents.

The archery event took more than an hour to complete; Garen kept yawning while he watched. When the time finally came for him to take the dojo test, he bid his sister goodbye and squeezed through the crowd behind him towards the exit.

Coming out of the crowd, the other parts of the Academy that were used for daily teaching seemed deserted. Occasionally, students and teachers would rush past while moving equipment, apparently to prepare for some sporting event.

Garen looked up at the sky. The sun was pale and its rays didn't provide any warmth. When an autumn breeze blew at him, a chill went through his body.

Heading out from the slightly deserted school gate, he turned towards the street where the dojo branch was located.

White Cloud Dojo had set up this branch dojo right by the street where Shengying Academy was situated. Many of the martial disciples were from the Academy. Combat was regarded as a part of the comprehensive development of quality education, so the Academy had no objections.

He took out the key and slipped into White Cloud Dojo through the main entrance. There was a mix of young and old people in white clothing sitting in the front hall. One of them was an instructor that Garen had seen teach before, the pretty Sharmilla.

Garen didn't know any of the others.

The seats in the front hall were usually reserved for the management personnel of the branch. Even though disciples were not specifically prohibited from sitting there, there were only those few seats when entering the front hall, so it would be unseemly for juniors to take up that space.

Garen gave Sharmilla a polite nod, then headed towards the courtyard through the left corridor. He didn't enter the courtyard, but continued walking left under the eaves. He came to a stop in front a small room with a white door and gently knocked on the door.

"Come in, it's not locked," a young man's voice answered from inside.

Garen opened the door and walked in.

The interior resembled an office archive room. A gentleman sat behind a desk. He whirled a pen in his hand, as if deliberating on a problem.

"Yes? How can I help you? The registration deadline has passed. You'll have to wait until the next quarter if you want to register." The man didn't look up from the documents in front of him.

"I'm not here to register. I'm Garen, one of the branch students chosen to be a Formal Disciple some time back." Garen walked over to the desk, took a chair and sat down. "I'm here to apply to be a Formal Dojo Disciple."

"Oh that. That's simple. Fill out this form right here."

The man handed over a form with a table of details to be filled in: name, age, family, etc.

Garen took a pen and smoothly began to fill in his personal information. A faint burst of cheering could be heard coming from outside while Garen was filling in the form. It sounded like some disciples had started a duel while the crowd looked on.

Garen turned around for a look. Peering out from the open door, he could perceive a few onlookers applauding and cheering.

"Those little bastards outside are betting on a fight. The losers will have to treat the others to dinner tonight. Don’t let them distract you, just fill out your form," the man said with a smile.

Garen quickly filled out the form and handed it to the man. He saw the man review the details once, then pick up a seal and stamp the form.

"It's done. Take this down to the Martial Colosseum and hand it in together with the $1,000 application fee to the Financial Department, then wait for further arrangements."

"Okay, got it. It's just as well that I haven't received my stipend yet. I could directly credit from that." Garen stood up and left the office. He headed back under the eaves, form in hand, while looking at the crowd gathered around the courtyard.

The sounds of punches and kicks kept coming from the middle of the crowd. Garen peered in through a gap. One of the combatants fighting was a boy from his dojo class, whereas Garen did not recognize the other one.

There was nothing interesting about the way they fought. They were only slightly better than Garen; they should be normal students from the branch.

He kept to the path and turned into the front hall. The people who sat there earlier were all gone, with only a young student sweeping inside.

Without another thought, Garen walked out of the dojo and headed back toward the Academy. The tournament was still in progress, but the focus had switched to a girls' swimming competition. The girls in swimsuits attracted catcalls from the crowd.

Without a second look, Garen took the form and headed out from the Academy. He hailed a carriage and directly headed towards the Martial Colosseum.

*******************

Ten or so minutes later…

"There are three people applying for the Formal Disciple certification today. I'll remind you in advance that if your application doesn't go through, the money you paid won't be refunded."

In the white courtyard, a middle-aged man with a handlebar moustache clad in black clothing was speaking loudly to the three youths in front of him.

"Understood!" shouted the three aloud.

From left to right stood a black-haired girl, Garen, and a brawny man. All three of them wore white Taoist robes.

"The test is very simple. Hold me off for half a minute and you pass," the mustached man calmly said. He had his hands crossed over his chest, inadvertently exposing his strong chest muscles and some black hair.

"Half a minute?" The three of them were stunned. They knew that if the man was confident enough to say that, he must have something up his sleeve.

"Don't worry, it's actually just to test your overall quality," the mustachioed man said casually. "Who's first?"

"I'll do it."

The black-haired girl was the first to step forward.

Both didn't exchange any courtesies. They stood their ground, their eyes met, and they abruptly started.

The mustachioed man took a forceful step forward and the ground shook slightly. He adopted a bow stance and deftly punched straight forward, not showing any of the delay that White Cloud Dojo trainers usually exhibited.

The girl didn't manage to dodge in time and the punch glanced off her shoulder. When she was ready to counter attack, another punch followed, so she could only hastily evade.

In huffs and puffs, one attacked and one evaded. This continued until they went in a full circle. Finally, the black-haired girl gave a loud cry and fell to the ground.

The mustachioed man reverted to a resting position and stood still, not the slightest bit out of breath.

"About 17 seconds." He shook his head.

"Thank you for your direction, Senior Brother." The girl clenched her teeth, got up, and gave a bow. She then stood aside, ready to see the other two take the test. It was obvious that she wanted to see others' performance after her own failure.

Having acquired the Secret Method and Explosive Fist Arts not too long ago, it was very clear to Garen that it should have been impossible for him to instantly apply them. Someone who was able to learn the Explosive Fist Arts in a few weeks wasn't a genius, he was a monstrosity!

For this test, he was prepared to use only the minimum amount of power to pass.

Garen took a look at the brawny man whose brow was furrowed, as if realizing the difficulty of the situation. Those able to participate in the test were extremely confident students from the branch dojos; all of them had learned the Explosive Fist Arts and White Cloud Secret Method.

It was unclear what level the man’s White Cloud Secret Method was at, but his training in Explosive Fist Arts seemed effective. His muscles and skin had a particular characteristic to them, which looked similar to what an elementary level of achievement would produce.

Earlier, the girl completely lacked this characteristic and purely relied on a mishmash of techniques complemented by her reflexes.

"My turn." Garen didn't want to waste any more time so he stepped forward.

The mustachioed man glanced at him and seemed slightly impressed.

"You're a new disciple who has just been taught fist arts. Not only did you not lose confidence after witnessing the previous challenger, but you still maintain a fighting spirit. Not bad, not bad."

"Confidence can't be judged by appearances," Garen replied calmly after taking a deep breath.

"Very well! Shall I begin?"

"Please."

Garen stood in place. The mustachioed man's waist sunk low as he took a step forward and threw a quick straight punch again. Somehow, Garen instinctively knew that this punch was easy to dodge.

He didn't give it another thought as he turned his body sideways to the right. The punch missed. Garen had planned to grab his opponent's shoulder to do a takedown, but he didn't expect the man's fist to recoil and spring forward like a snake to punch straight towards his shoulder.

There was a 'shwiff' and Garen didn't manage to evade this time. The punch grazed his shoulder and he felt a slight burning pain.

Before he could catch his breath, another punch flew straight at him. This time it hit his right shoulder.

Garen was determined to face the attack head on, but was worried about revealing his level of Explosive Fist Arts, so all he could do was endure and dodge awkwardly to the side. However, he had never learned any practical dodging skills and was used to facing attacks head on. Although he was able to clumsily escape the full brunt of the punch with his dodge, he was still grazed by the side of the fist.

Fortunately, his skin was tough enough. His elementary level of training in Explosive Fist Arts had hardened the skin cuticles all over his body. The graze caused a lasting numbing pain, but he was otherwise alright.

"Eh?" the mustachioed man sounded perplexed. His punches incorporated a certain level of the Explosive Fist Arts so that recipients would not only feel pain, but would also be numbed to the nerves. Consecutively, he had hit the boy in front of him twice, yet the boy seemed fine and was still able to continue dodging.

Seven to eight seconds had passed.

[This boy has potential. His physicality seems good. He has a strong constitution for someone his age.] The man had an idea and wanted to test Garen. He retracted his fist and instantly threw it out again with increased speed.

As he threw the punch, a faint snap came from the sleeve as it tightened at his wrist.

This punch was aimed to hit Garen squarely in the right shoulder and it was twice as fast as previous strikes so Garen wouldn’t be able to dodge it even if he saw it coming.

Wham! Garen fell back three steps, standing on the spot with his face slightly flushed. When he tried to raise his right arm, he realized it was completely paralyzed.

"Ten seconds." The mustachioed man went back into a resting position and stood straight, a trace of disappointment in his eyes. He had a bulky build and his footwork seemed sluggish, but when he actually fought, the explosive speed of his fists was extraordinarily quick.

"Next. Let's get this over with."

The brawny man clenched his teeth and stepped forward.

Chapter 22: Core (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen walked to the side helplessly; he knew that his performance definitely did not qualify. There was a huge difference between half a minute and ten seconds. Previously, he was confident that he would become a high-class disciple after he learned the Explosive Fist Arts, but he didn’t expect that an examiner would be this strong. He thought to himself,

[Even if I fully unleash my power and fought without holding anything back, I still wouldn’t be able to defeat him.]

The opponent’s attacking speed was too fast, his strength was high, and the attack carried some kind of paralyzing effect. If someone was struck twice in the same location like Garen, then the result would already be determined at that point.

Bam! Bam!

Like Garen expected, the brawny man who went up next did not make it past the thirty second mark either. The man clutched his shoulder and got off of the stage.

The man with the mustache was at ease; he didn’t even sweat. He relaxed his fists and lightly said to the three people, "Ok, the test is over. Your scores are far from qualifying. You guys still need to work hard. You are now dismissed."

At this point, Garen realized that the examiner didn’t even use his full strength; fighting the three applicants was like a walk in the park for him. Garen tried to estimate the man with the mustache’s level and strength.

[He’s probably reached the maximum adult physical strength limit just like me, but he is way faster. His Explosive Fist Arts can’t be at the elementary level, it must be at the intermediate level or above. From his status, it seems like his White Cloud Secret Arts is also at the intermediate level or above. He is also very, very skillful in terms of fighting techniques.]

After comparing himself with the mustache man, Garen felt a little bit better.

The black-haired girl on the side stepped up when she saw the test was over.

"Teacher, can you tell us what level of fighter you are right now?"

"What level?" The man with the mustache smiled as he smoothed his wrinkled clothes. "Do you know how fighters are ranked?" he asked.

The black-haired girl nodded and said, "I only know the Grandmaster of Combat rankings that the Confederation uses."

"That doesn’t count. That’s only the ranking for fake exhibition matches," the examiner said. He became a bit excited and continued, "I will tell you guys the ranking system that we have in our circle."

He pointed out three fingers.

"The first level are ordinary people who know a little fighting technique, or people who are interested in learning. This level also includes special forces from the military who are able to easily take care of one or two hooligans. We call this level Amateur.

"These amateurs are probably our dojo’s primary source of income, right?" The brawny applicant continued where the man with the mustache left off.

"That’s right. Because these hobbyists are excited to train, they are willing to spend money, just like how you guys got started. Also, the masters in our industry would sometimes be invited to teach at an influential or powerful amateur’s home, which is how the network in the industry originated. When a master is looking for a disciple, potential and physical requirements are only part of the equation; family background is also very important.

"That makes sense," Garen nodded. "It’s impossible for a master to teach people for free and also offer free food and accommodations. After all, masters are people too and still need money to live."

"I know some of it." The black-haired girl continued, "Our White Cloud Dojo operates like this and our Dojo Master is a wealthy merchant who runs a huge corporation.

"You are all formal disciples and you guys might teach other people martial arts in the future. Therefore, I’ll give you guys some hints." The man with mustache nodded as he said, "There are two types of disciples you should look for."

He pointed out his index finger.

"One is the disciple who has a robust background with either money or influence. These type of disciples are there for the purpose of coverage and increased influence in the industry. They don’t have to be strong, but they have to be beneficial for the master’s brand."

Then he pointed out the second finger.

"Next, there are the real inheriting disciples. The key traits to look for are potential and the fundamentals. They should be taught with all care since they would need to step up in the future when the master gets old and weak and can’t fight anymore. They need to be strong to maintain the reputation and the status of the dojo brand in the industry, so the brand doesn’t become a stepping stone for other people.

"The selection process for heritage disciples is very rigorous; it's very different from teaching other disciples. Many heritage disciples came from bad family backgrounds, so the master needed to be there to cultivate them. This kind of master-disciple relationship would be the most solid; it would be very close to a parent-child relationship. Eventually, the strongest heritage disciple would inherit everything that the master had. The other disciples would become the backbone of the brand.

"Therefore, you guys have to pay attention to these criteria when you’re looking for a disciple. If you want to cultivate disciples properly, you have to have money and resources."

After he said that, the man with mustache fell silent for a moment and seemed like he was recalling something.

"Right. We were talking about the ranking for the fighters, how did we end up here?" He quickly snapped out of it. He smiled and said, "Let’s focus on the rankings. Amateurs can be considered at the bottom. One level higher would be the professionals; the professional fighters who were trained from a young age. This becomes more complicated and ranges from people who are able to fight off three to five hooligans to people who are not afraid when faced with a dozen people to a few dozen people. As long as firearms are not involved, fighters in this rank can handle it. No one knows how strong someone is in this rank unless they fight them first hand. Most people can only estimate someone’s strength by using their fame and influence. Oh, the Confederation’s five ranks from A to E also applies here. For example, I’m considered an E rank. The letter ranks represent the degree of ability."

"The smaller ranks within the amateur level are ranked from 1 to 9. Letter ranks are only used when someone is at a higher rank than amateur.

"Above the professionals, there are the Dojo Masters. People rarely achieve this rank in the industry. You are not a Dojo Master if you simply open up a Dojo; it’s more complicated than that. Dojo Master represents a completely different level.

"Are people in this rank the same people who are able to break a gigantic green boulder with one punch?" The brawny man’s eyes shined.

"Hehe… that is the story of Dojo Master Rizal who has the nickname of Belligerent Fist. You are roughly correct. At this level, they have reached the peak of human potential and are at an unimaginable level. Dojo Master Rizal can’t block a bullet with his body, yet his defense is considered one of the best in the industry." The man with the mustache laughed, "You could never reach that level, but it’s because of these fascinating stories that we are motivated to train and practice our skills, is it not?"

"My goal is to become someone like Dojo Master Rizal and stand at the very peak!"

"So could someone on the Dojo Master level beat one hundred people alone?" The black-haired girl asked another question.

"If the hundred people are just thugs, then Dojo Master could beat them easily one after another. Dojo Masters could probably also beat them if they all come at the same time. Top ranked masters don’t have any obvious shortcoming in terms of speed or endurance. The people with obvious shortcomings have already died in real fights." The man with mustache shook his head as he sighed.

"Alright, you guys can go now. Come back after you guys practice more." He waved his hand and said, "Just soak the part of your body that got punched with hot water and the numbness will go away."

"Ok!" The three of them replied individually. Although they didn’t pass the test, they were a bit excited after learning a lot of industry secrets that outsiders did not know.

It was Garen’s first time hearing this information about the Martial Arts world, but he felt it was very similar to the Martial Arts world on Earth. He pretended to be excited by this knowledge as he thought about his current situation and started to walk away.

[Looks like I have to become one of the two types of disciple this man talked about in order to get the core teachings. I have no hope of becoming the first type, but the second type is possible; the difficulty level is just a bit high.] Garen thought to himself.

"Hey, young man named Garen, wait a second!"

He heard the examiner shout.

Garen was surprised, but he turned around instantly.

"What do you need?" he asked the man with the mustache, who was walking towards him, perplexedly.

"You passed, why are you walking away?" The man with the mustache was also confused.

"My scored passed?"

Garen was shocked.

"Yeah, you are only sixteen, your requirements are different compared to theirs. Couldn’t you tell that they are adults?" The man with mustache smiled and said, "You are the only disciple who passed the test these past few years. Which branch are you from? Who is your instructor?"

When Garen quickly realized what was going on, he was delighted.

"I’m from the Shengying Academy branch, my instructors are Sharmilla and Luo Ya."

"Your body is quite strong." The man with mustache squeezed Garen’s shoulders. "After some training, you are already about rank 4 or 5. You are fine even after taking two punches from me, especially the second punch. Yet you have fully recovered already. From the data that I read, you were still thin last month, but you grew a lot."

Garen on the other hand just smiled, he didn’t know how to explain everything.

"Ok! Kid, you have a good foundation. Let’s go, come with me and meet your senior brothers and sisters. I didn’t expect that I would accept another disciple in my fifties." The man rubbed his mustache and said with a smile.

"Accepting disciple?" Garen was surprised. "Are you the Dojo Master Fei Baiyun?!!" He thought the man was only a regular examiner.

"Why? I don’t look like him?" the man with mustache said with a semi-smile on his face.

"No, no… You just look too young. You look like you are in your forties and I heard that the Dojo Master is in his fifties," Garen quickly spilled out the truth of what he was thinking.

"You little punk…" Dojo Master Fei Baiyun rubbed Garen’s hair and felt speechless. "I have nothing to do at this age, so I decided to come to the Dojo and test disciples with the hope to find some disciples with high potential. Surprisingly, I actually found a few in the last dozen years; they are your senior brothers and sisters.

"Also, you were trying to hide your full strength earlier. There is no need to hide your tiny amount of strength. You are not at that level yet. When you meet your senior brothers and sisters, don’t do that or it would only make them laugh, especially your senior sister. For the purpose of practice, she has beaten a dozen full grown white bears to death."

The mustached man laughed.

"White bear…!!" Garen was defeated by this information. He had only read about this creature in books. A white bear was about a man’s height when it stood up and its rough skin was very thick. This skin could not even be penetrated by a bullet from afar and could only be pierced at close range. It had about a ton, or 2,000 pounds, of strength. The senior sister that he hadn’t met yet was able to beat a dozen white bears to death? It was unimaginable!

"Of course it’s not like what you think. They didn’t attack her at the same time. She only fought one bear at a time. The white bear isn’t very fast, so if you could dodge its attack, you could win easily by counterattacking. However, none of your dodges can fail or else you could be killed. Only under this life-threatening pressure is your senior sister able to improve quickly," the man with the mustache said with deep feelings.

"Let’s go. I will introduce you to them. I know about your family background as well. You don’t have to host a fancy ceremony or anything. I will invite some of my friends in the industry to come as witnesses for a simple acceptance ceremony. The Dojo will pay for all your training related expenses so your family doesn’t have to worry about the cost. After your parents witness the ceremony, you will officially become my formal disciple.

"Ok, master!" Garen nodded seriously. Although he knew that he could reach this formal disciple level, he didn’t expect it to happen so fast.

Life in the true Martial Arts World of this era was about to slowly unfold for him.

Chapter 23: The Core (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"This will be the first time that I can actually enter the real martial arts circle!"

Garen was excited. After all, he loved martial arts when he was on Earth, but didn’t have the opportunity to train and learn when he was young. Now, with this opportunity as the beginning, his lifelong most cherished dream was about to be realized.

"The only thing a bit strange is that some people have names similar to Chinese names, like the name Fei Baiyun. It sounds like a Chinese name. He even seems like a grandmaster of combat who went to western countries to teach martial arts."

Garen followed Fei Baiyun as they walked under the eaves of the roof. Garen couldn’t hold the thoughts in his mind any longer, so he asked, "Master, you’re not of the Confederation, right?"

Fei Baiyun nodded as he smiled. "You can tell? Yeah, my name is pretty different from the names here at Yalu Confederation. I wasn’t born in the Yalu Confederation, I’m from a huge empire at the east."

"East? Like from Republic of the Tulip?" Garen asked.

"No, it’s a place very far away, very far that not even planes can get there. Only huge ships can…" The smile on Fei Baiyun’s face slowly disappeared, only to be replaced with a tinge of sorrow. "We were only able to reach this place because we were very lucky. I can’t even return now. Enough of this, we’re almost there. Be careful not to get hazed by your senior brothers and sisters," he said.

"Oh…ok…" Garen answered. However, he was still thinking of the modern China back on Earth. The two of them walked into the lounge and started heading up the side stairs to the second floor. Garen saw the two disciples who had participated in the test with him in the lounge talking with a blond man. The black-haired girl turned around and looked at Garen, traces of envy apparent on her eyes.

The other strapping man shrugged his shoulders and said, "Don’t feel envious. If you have time to envy someone, you are better off training more and then fighting for your entrance qualifications next time."

"We are all getting older… There’s no chance." The girl shook her head and said, "This is the last time that I’ll be here. My parents are sending me abroad to Cisilyn to study Business Management. The only time I can come to the Dojo would be during long breaks. This little kid must have passed the test. What’s his name again?"

"I just saw it moments ago. I think he wrote Garen on the data sheet." The strapping man also turned around to look at Garen.

"Alright, alright. People like us can never devote 100% of our time and energy into training. We are still able to live how we want to live at present, but when we get older, we’ll have to accept the arrangements from our families. Therefore, not qualifying could be considered as something good. We won’t regret this after all." A helpless expression popped on the blond man’s face as he said, "I’m really envious of senior sister Rosetta…"

The three of them fell into silence for a moment as they heard the name Rosetta.

Garen vaguely heard their conversation and looked at them. He just saw the black-haired girl raising her fist at him, cheering him on.

He nodded back as he smiled and gestured an "OK" sign back. He then quickly followed Fei Baiyun to the second floor.

The second floor was a wide, open hall. A layer of dark brown carpet was laid on the ground, and a huge grey circle was drawn at the center of hall.

On the four corners were a couple of red wooden cylinders that supported the roof.

What was strange was that there wasn't a column at the center of the room to support the roof. The ceiling of the hall looked like two slanted flat boards leaning against each other such that it looked firm and aesthetically pleasing.

There was a huge black and white oil painting at the end of the hall. Garen saw it clearly as he was walking up the stairs. The painting was of a huge white ship sailing across the waves and tides in the ocean.

Under the oil painting were a few tables and chairs made of redwood. Two people in black uniforms were chatting there; one of them was standing while the other was sitting on a chair.

The one standing was a girl that looked in her twenties. Her dark brown hair was tied into a ponytail, which was draped over her shoulder. She was wearing a pair of tight black shorts and a camisole under a vest, her fair-skinned, slender arms and thighs fully exposed. What was intriguing was her big chest under the camisole. Its size made it seem as though the zipper of her vest would break anytime.

The girl leaned against the wall. From afar, Garen could see her facial features that made her look very valiant. Her lips most especially, the way she spoke was concise and persuasive. She was definitely someone who was straightforward and powerful.

The one who was standing was a white-haired man. He was also in his twenties, but he looked ordinary and had a fatigued countenance. He was the kind of person whom you couldn’t easily recognize on the street. However, his arms were quite lengthy to the extent that when he was seated, his hands could effortlessly touch the ground. It gave people an feeling of incongruence.

Both of them stood straight and walked toward the stairs as they saw Fei Baiyun taking someone up here.

"Master, you found someone after the test today?" The brown-haired girl was surprised, her curiosity evident as she observed Garen carefully up and down.

"I finally found someone with high potential. His foundation and work ethics are both above average. I will stop taking disciples after this last one." Fei Baiyun laughed as he sat down on a chair. "His name is Garen. He will be your junior brother from now on."

"Last one? Hehe! Finally someone who is younger than me!" The white-haired man said with a villainous smile on his face, "I’ve been waiting for this day for so long. All the senior brothers and sisters had been bullying me whenever they got bored, and I wasn’t even allowed to fight back! Now it’s finally my turn."

"Look at you! Do you think you are getting bullied just because you are the youngest?" The brown-haired girl knocked him on the head half-angrily.

"Alright, alright. Introduce yourselves. All four of you will be helping and relying on each other from now on. I won’t be taking any more disciples in the future after all." Fei Baiyun smiled and said with his eyes half-squinted.

The brown-haired girl nodded and said, "I will go first."

She looked at Garen who was standing obediently at the side and said: "My name is Rosetta, the first disciple of the master. I will be your senior sister from now on."

The white-haired man put away his ridiculous smile and said, "I’m your second brother Joshua…"

"Second brother? Screw you!"

A tough, gigantic, towering man quickly rushed up the stairs. His voice was as deep as thunder, and he had a white tiger tattooed on his upper body.

"Hey, little Josh, since when did you become the second brother here? Why haven’t I heard of it?"

"Eh… Isn’t this our strong, handsome, invincible and charming second brother Farak?" Joshua shivered as he hid behind his senior sister.

"I said third brother. You must have misheard it! Misheard… Hehe." A timid expression appeared on Joshua’s face, as if he was a mouse who had just met a cat.

The towering Farak ignored Joshua. He walked up to Fei Baiyun and clenched his fists to salute. "Master, I heard that you just took in a junior brother; I came here just to meet and welcome him."

"Come, let’s all sit down."

Fei Baiyun was most proud of his second disciple Farak. Farak was only in his twenties, and yet he was already at level 3 in terms of the White Cloud Secret Arts. His Explosive Fist Arts were also at level 2. With the herculean strength that he was born with, his combat ability was off the charts. Farak, at this point, wasn’t weaker than Fei Baiyun when he was at this age. Although Farak still couldn't beat his disciple Rosetta, Farak’s strong physique and his direct fist-to-fist combat style was the most compatible with everything that White Cloud Dojo was teaching, and it was the style that Fei Baiyun really favored.

"Your junior brother just became my disciple, so he hasn’t learnt anything yet. You guys should bully him less." Fei Baiyun stretched his neck as he said with a smile, "After a year or two, he will be in a much better shape."

"Nothing wrong with that. Junior brother, just come and ask me if you don’t understand anything! I have a lot of experience in evasive maneuvers." Rosetta smiled with her arms crossed in front of her chest.

"I specialize in heavy punches. You can come and ask me if you don’t understand anything in terms of explosive strength." Farak patted Garen’s shoulder.

"And me, your third brother. If you need any help, just come and find me at Huaishan. But if you are at any other place, then I can’t do anything about it… Hehe."

"Now, we are all brothers and sisters, so there will be more opportunities to get to know each other in the future. How about we go and celebrate now?"

The conversations were very intimate. Although Garen was the weakest of them, none of his senior brothers or sister looked down on him. All of them were the disciples of the master and were so intimate that they looked like a family.

Bam! Bam! Garen got patted by the powerful palms. He was fortunate enough to have achieved the elementary level on the Explosive Fist Arts. Otherwise, his body might not be able to take the full brunt of these pats on the shoulders.

"Let’s go to Worcester Restaurant; they have some great seafood. The dishes there all taste amazing." Rosetta suggested.

"I will pass this time. You young people are able to have more fun together without me." Fei Baiyun smiled as he shook his head. "I have some other plans already. I have to meet up with an old friend."

"Okay then. We will just hang out with ourselves tonight. We’ll treat Master some other time!" Rosetta waved her hand as she said with the temperament of a senior sister, "Let’s go test Junior Brother’s foundation!!"

"I like it!" The third brother Joshua said as he peeked at Garen with "malicious intent".

"Don’t bully the junior brother!" the towering Farak smacked his palm on Joshua’s head and rubbed his hair. "He just became master’s disciple! He is not there yet!"

Garen stood on the side and watched his senior brothers and sister messing around until Fei Baiyun stopped them; he was smiling the whole time.

"Okay, who is first? Make sure you don’t use your full strength."

"I will go first." Joshua was excited. Although he was in his twenties, he was still acting like a kid.

He stretched his black uniform and walked to the center of the hall. He then lowered his right palm and gestured Garen to come.

Although Garen wasn’t too sure what it meant, he knew that this was some kind of test to reveal his full strength, or it could be to see where he ranked among the four of them. The most important reason of all, however, was probably to show him how strong his senior brothers and sister were, so as to properly establish their positions as his Seniors.

In a dojo, Seniority was established by fighting, not talking.

Garen walked up to the center of the hall and faced third brother Joshua.

He put on a simple boxing defense pose. He didn’t know anything about proper combat, so he could only use this most basic boxing stance which could help him exert his full power.

Joshua smiled, letting Garen see all of his white teeth. "Be careful, I’m attacking!"

As soon as Joshua finished the sentence, he leapt forward and aimed his right palm at Garen’s right elbow. This attack was so fast that it created a ‘Whoosh!" sound.

This strike was average in terms of speed and power in an outsider’s view; it looked like a simple greeting that friends would give each other.

But it was different in Garen’s eyes.

Although this palm strike from Joshua wasn’t fast, it gave him a flexible and agile feeling. Garen’s instinct told him that if he tried to dodge this strike, this strike would quickly change trajectories and follow his body tightly.

From the wind that this palm strike generated, Garen felt that the strength in this strike wasn’t weak at all.

Many thoughts went through Garen’s mind, but he didn’t overthink the situation. He took this strike head-on, but he also suppressed a part of his strength just like what he did during the test with Fei Baiyun. He only exerted about 140 pounds of force.

At the same time, he swung his arm from the side and slapped at Joshua’s approaching palm.

Pia!

"Eh? Junior Brother’s reaction is very quick!" Senior Sister Rosetta was surprised as she suddenly stood up from her chair. "Although Joshua’s speed isn’t that fast, most people in our White Cloud Dojo couldn’t really spot his attacks clearly. I didn’t expect Junior Brother to react this fast and block the attack before it reached him. His vision and body reaction are far superior than average disciples."

"Of course," Master Fei Baiyun laughed proudly. "This is where his talent lies, and he is sly enough to hide some of his strength. White Cloud Secret Arts is the technique that we practice at White Cloud Dojo. Although it could result in a substantial strength increase, speed and reaction times would be negatively affected. Therefore, the key reason why I took your junior brother in is because of his talent and potential in speed and reaction time. This way, his natural abilities will cover up the shortcomings of White Cloud Secret Arts."

"Master, you are right. Disciples from our White Cloud Dojo have always lost in speed compared with other Dojos." Rosetta calmed down and agreed with Fei Baiyun.

In combat, after Garen blocked the first palm strike, he kept on consciously trying to block and parry the palm strikes coming from all angles. These strikes struck his body and made continuous hard slapping sounds.

Every time a palm landed on Garen’s body, he would feel a numbing sensation of weakness dispersing into his body.

Chapter 24: The Core (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

His agility, eye speed, and physical reaction were all fast enough to match the fist’s speed. However, he usually could only block the first punch before the change in attack method left him defenseless.

After being whacked more than ten times, Garen staggered a few steps backward . To be beaten up repeatedly without a chance to counter attack made him very depressed. When he finally stabilized his body, he hastily pushed forward with his palm.

There was no technique involved with what he was doing. It was a simple and plain strike in the form of a palm. It received the powerful palm from Joshua head-on.

Bang!

The two palms clashed together with great force.

Garen turned his foot and fell back more than 10 steps. His face turned white and, for a moment, he could not catch his breath.

All he felt was a surge of heat that spun around continuously in his chest. This heat was trapped inside and could not leave his body. The middle of his right palm was boiling hot and as red as a lobster.

Looking up, he saw Third Senior Brother Joshua walking over with a worried look.

"Are you okay Junior Brother? Just now I got lost in the moment and forgot you were underage. I used a little bit too much power…"

"It’s okay…" Garen had felt Third Senior Brother restrain his strength when he realized something was wrong. As a result, Garen was not wounded at all. Garen lifted his right arm, "My blood is just a little congested."

Just now, he estimated that Third Senior Brother’s palm strength definitely exceeded 180 pounds. Looking at Joshua, Garen was sure that that was not even Joshua’s limit. Joshua was also definitely a freak who could surpass 200 pounds.

"Joshua’s strength is around 300 pounds, the weakest one out of all of us. My strength is about 350 pounds. Your Second Senior Brother is the strongest. He was tested two days ago and his strength is above 450 pounds," Elder Senior Sister Rosetta walked over. She grabbed Garen’s arm and massaged it slowly.

"Martial arts does not comply with the idea that the stronger you are, the more likely you are to win." Second Senior Brother Frank rubbed his chin. "Rosetta, you have already surpassed Stage E of training. I am still stuck at Amateur Stage Nine."

"You are lacking in agility. Having only strength is not necessarily a good thing. It slows you down because you are so heavy." Rosetta pinched Frank’s arm with a smile on her face. "Look at all the fat on your body. When we hang out tonight, we will have to order extra meat just for you."

"That’s because I’m consuming a lot of energy now," Frank shrugged helplessly. "Next, let me test the extent of our Junior Brother’s skills. At the same time, we can roughly evaluate the highest stage our Junior Brother can achieve."

"Sounds good. After all, you are one of the judges in our city that determines the Amateur Martial Arts placements," Rosetta agreed while nodding.

Frank, nicknamed Eiffel Tower because he was two meters tall, stood in front of Garen and forcefully pushed Joshua away. Joshua speechlessly ran to the side and sat down to watch the battle.

"Junior Brother, you better beat him up good!" Joshua waved his fist and softly encouraged.

"Senior Brother, you got our roles mixed up…" Garen smiled bitterly.

Everyone in the group softly laughed.

"Please." Frank stood barefoot on the ground. He casually swung his arm and released a wave of wind that made a mess of Garen’s hair, despite a distance of four meters between them.

Garen knew that these Senior Siblings were fully grown adults. Not only had their strength reached the usual limit, but the synergy between the Explosive Fist Arts and other techniques raised their peak strength far beyond the standard maximum value. After all, the standard value was set based on an average adult male.

Therefore, everyone here was much stronger than him. At times like this, not displaying any personality defects or bad habits was more than enough. Winning was simply impossible for Garen.

Comprehending this, he inhaled deeply. He expanded his chest and held his breath.

Side step! Straight punch!

Bang!

The fist hit Frank’s body heavily. It felt like the punch landed on a rubber car tire that was sturdy but elastic. The powerful rebound caused Garen to retreat four to five steps.

Feeling this shocking resistance, Garen was aghast.

"Your guess is correct. The technique I practice is the Mammoth Secret Technique," Frank replied with a smile. "The Explosive Fist Technique is a basic technique in our dojo. It is an iconic technique that enhances the user’s explosive power. Of course, it also makes the skin more durable. The real Secret Method of our dojo is the Mammoth Secret Technique. This is a secret technique that we do not pass down publicly."

"A secret technique?"

"Yes, every dojo has exclusive martial arts skills called secret techniques that they selectively teach. In White Cloud Dojo, the Explosive Fist Technique cannot be considered strong because most dojos have similar techniques. However, the Mammoth Secret Technique is different. It is something unique that only we have and other dojos don’t. This technique allows the user to defend himself while enhancing muscle strength," Frank explained patiently.

"Now I will use one-tenth of my power to attack you. You should try to block me."

"Alright."

Garen readied himself in a guarding position as he concentrated fully on the opponent. All the strength in his body converged. He knew that even if he unleashed all his strength, in front of his Second Senior Brother, he was considered to be the same level as a bean sprout. He could easily be destroyed with one wave of his Senior Brother’s hand. However, during these times, he especially needed to be careful and not expose his secret.

No matter how much talent one has, it was impossible to perfect the White Cloud Secret Method and elementary Explosive Fist Technique within a month. To successfully do so was beyond the capabilities of a genius. Only a freak or a monster could achieve that.

The moment someone dug deep into the issue, they could find out about his secret abilities.

Frank stretched out his right arm and grabbed Garen’s right shoulder with his big hand. Like a handheld folding fan that was blasted down by a strong gust of wind, Frank pushed down.

The two of them stood together. One was unmistakably gigantic, the other was extremely petite. It was like an adult capturing a kid.

The speed of the palm was not that fast, but the way it moved seemed inescapable. The giant hand was quivering nonstop, as if at any time it could swing in any direction it wanted. This feeling of uncertainty clouded Garen’s judgment and he had no idea which direction to dodge if he wanted to evade.

Helplessly, he mustered 140 pounds of strength and met the palm with resolution.

After he struck, Garen felt like he hit a metal plate. The throbbing from the collision greatly pained his hand. A strange wave of power pressed down from the top of Frank’s hand. It wasn’t exactly heavy, however as soon as Frank’s palm contacted with Garen’s, a forceful shivering and numbness extended down Garen’s arm.

Subconsciously, to resist this numbness, Garen unleashed all his strength and ruthlessly pushed forward with two hundred pounds worth of strength.

The result was the same.

Flopping, he fell on his butt to the ground. His entire body was numb and he had no strength left in his body.

Frank nodded in approval and retracted his hand.

"Your physique is not bad. If you learn some fundamental combat arts and do not conceal a part of your strength, then achieving Amateur Stage Six is no problem."

"Really??" Garen lowkey celebrated. "Stage Five amateurs can earn five to six thousand monthly if employed…" He then bitterly smiled. He thought that he could battle equally with these Senior Disciples if he used all of his strength. However, the result was all the same because of his weak abilities.

"Only five to six thousand could make you this happy? Are you in need of money?" Fei Baiyun walked over and slapped the top of Garen’s head.

"I have something I want to buy." Garen then suddenly remembered that the emblem was gone. The happiness he felt died down.

"Before your Senior Disciples, you dare to hide your real strength? Did you know that your Second Senior Brother was born with monstrous strength before he was introduced to martial arts? At age 15, he had 200 pounds of strength, a height of 1.9m, and doubled your Elder Senior Sister in size. So you were born with more strength than a regular person, what’s there to hide?" Elder Senior Sister Rosetta teased.

Garen was speechless. As long as nobody found out about his unusual level in the Explosive Fist Technique and the Secret Method, he was okay.

Behind him a few people dragged out chairs and sat down. The three Senior Disciples began to discuss the details of the recent practice just now.

Elder Senior Sister advised on aiming only to hit the vitals of the opponent using speed and explosive force. Hitting the fatal areas of the opponent was the easiest and cleanest way to win a battle. Therefore, she taught Garen that in order to kill with one attack, he must pay attention, dodge, and respond to the opponent’s explosive power. It would most effective for him to concentrate all his time and energy on improving only one area.

Second Senior Brother advocated for overall strength. He lectured Garen to exercise his whole body because if he was able to fully improve physically, he could face any situation with ease.

Third Senior Brother believed in survival before anything else. If one cannot beat the opponent, one should run. He believed that practicing martial arts just to strengthen the physique was enough, therefore there was no point in fighting to the point of injury or death. It would be unpleasant to ruin relationships between people and enemies would only accumulate if one always fought every battle to the end. Based on his beliefs, the more friends the better, since everyone would live in harmony that way.

Third Senior Brother’s beliefs were unanimously despised by everyone else. Elder Senior Sister and Second Senior Brother’s debate over who was right became more and more heated. In the end, they could not reach a consensus and ended up battling it out physically.

After a few rounds that lasted for more than 10 minutes, Second Senior Brother was eventually defeated, though he did not admit defeat. It was obvious that his strength exploded too quickly and he was very afraid of hurting Elder Senior Sister. Because of his thick skin and fat, he was instead punched repeatedly, losing the battle.

Garen watched from the side with cold sweat spilling out of his pores. Only when these Senior Disciples battled each other did he realize their true strength.

He was terrified that he would be helplessly slaughtered in seconds the moment he went against any of them.

Eldest Senior Sister was the strongest, yet still was only at Stage E, so it was difficult to imagine what higher staged seniors could do.

"Alright, alright, everyone stop," Fei Baiyun announced while loudly clapping. He looked at Garen and said, "Don’t think too much. The reality is that the higher you go, the harder it is to step into the next stage. Those above the E Stage usually have a better understanding of the laws behind these techniques. Those big dojos are all the same. Strength like your Second Senior Brother’s can be placed at the medium to upper class anywhere."

"Those who achieve higher stages are usually stronger when it comes to special Secret Methods. For example, I know about a type of Secret Method that could instantly accelerate and achieve unmatchable speed for the user. Combine that ability with a sharp weapon and a high-quality killer secret technique is created. Different techniques have different effects based on different environments and the influences around them. In our White Cloud Dojo, we were enlightened with the Mammoth Secret Technique from the inspiration of the mammoth."

Garen knew that his real abilities were nothing before his master and his Senior Brothers and Sister. Everyone here was considered to be great figures within the martial arts community. Although Garen did not know how they would fare in real battles, regular people could not kill his seniors even if they had guns, unless they attacked vital areas.

Fortunately, his master and Senior Disciples did not even consider the fact that he had already advanced the White Cloud Secret Arts to the second stage. If he could reach stage three, then he could improve his strength attribute again.

None of this was actually important. From the Senior Disciple’s conversations, Garen learned that the White Cloud Secret Arts was used to enhance strength. With every increase in level, it could forcefully improve the strength attribute. However, the end result was already determined at birth.

The higher a person’s natural talent was, the greater the increase in strength, and the stronger the total strength.

Second Senior Brother was a perfect example of this. He was born strong and trained the White Cloud Secret Arts to a high level. Coupled with the Mammoth Secret Technique, his strength grew to a frighteningly powerful level.

The key point was that Garen’s strength attribute could be improved infinitely by his special ability. Therefore, he could reach the same level as his Second Senior Brother despite his lack of natural talent.

Compared to Elder Senior Sister’s style of hitting the vital points of the opponent, Garen was leaning more toward Second Senior Brother’s straightforward style of being holistically trained. With this method, there would be no vital weakness. No matter how critical the situation becomes, his fighting style could face it easily and effectively.

Even now, Garen’s heart was actually still filled with fear and insecurity toward this world. These emotions, along with his crazy passion for martial arts, made him more than willing to devote all his energy into training.

Chapter 25: Abilities (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After exiting the Dojo, the few Seniors came out for food and drinks. As Garen was practically force fed alcohol and had gotten somewhat tipsy, he was afraid to go back home and be punished for underage drinking.

Since his Senior Siblings bombarded him and requested him to drink, Garen had no choice but to give them the satisfaction and comply. Any one of them there had the ability to disable him with one hand.

After finalizing plans for next week’s Acceptance Ceremony, Garen finally managed to get out of the hotel. He wandered down the city roads at night to digest the alcohol.

As he walked, his head felt heavy while his feet felt light. After roaming the streets for a long time, he unknowingly returned to Pennington Street.

The moonlight was like a white veil that draped down, the entire street appeared milky and misty.

Faint lights peeked out of the windows in the two buildings on the side. People’s shadows moved from time to time beneath the faint yellow light, and a piano was dimly playing; its beats were crisp and a little choppy.

Garen walked along the right sidewalk. Gusts of cold wind blew onto his face, clearing his foggy mind.

In front of him, a black double carriage approached. On the carriage, the hanging horse lights shook from side to side, shining bright enough to see only the rider’s silhouette.

The carriage passed by Garen before turning into the corner and disappearing. Then, there were only the occasional echoes of breathing sounds from the horse.

Garen buttoned up his collar and quickened his steps.

Walking to the end of the road, he stood before Dolphin Antiques. He originally only wanted to clear his mind and walk around this area; however, the light in the antique store was still on.

Walking in front of the door, he knocked the door.

"Open up old man!"

The door creaked.

On the metal door, a round hole opened. The old man’s smiling face was now visible along with his sparse and messy white hair.

"Ah it’s you bastard," he sniffled and smelled the alcohol, "You dared to drink at your young age!"

The old man hurriedly opened the door and let Garen come in.

"Ughhh… Old man, do you have anything that can sober me up?" Garen’s head still felt heavier than his feet, like he was walking on a cloud. He tried to walk in a straight line yet his body kept on falling to one side.

"I own an antique store, not a grocery store." The old man sat down, he seemed to be taking pleasure in Garen’s pain. Turning his head and glaring at Garen, he said, "You’re scared that your family would notice that you’ve been drinking. That’s why you’re wandering outside trying to sober up, am I right?"

"How did you know?" Garen sat on a red-clothed stool, after moving the fake antiques on top of a table nearby, and massaged his temples.

"It’s very obvious just from looking at you. I was about to go home, but since you’re here, I will stay a bit longer. These days, it is not very safe in the city at night. You should be careful and don’t stay out too late."

"I know, I know, don’t worry," Garen dry coughed, "Old man, do you have any water here?"

"In the room at the back. You get it yourself, I’m too lazy to take care of you," Old Man Gregor was sitting at his desk writing something to help with the criminal case.

Garen wobbled his way to the only other room in the shop and poured himself a cup of water. The moment the cold water entered his stomach, he felt better.

Returning to the main room, he dragged out a chair and sat down beside the old man at the table.

Under the influence of the alcohol, Garen asked the question he had been wanting to ask for a long time.

"Old man, where is the book you showed me last time? Can you let me read it some more?"

Old Man Gregor bit the feather on the end of his pen, pretending not to hear.

"Hey old man, did you hear me?"

"I heard you! Why are you being so loud?" Old Man Gregor waved his hand, "Even if I give you that book, it would be useless. Without that ability, no matter how many times you read it, the result will be the same."

"Says who? That is because I didn’t read it carefully last time," Garen non-sensibly said, "If you give it to me this time, I will for sure read it very carefully!"

"You bastard sure know how to pick items. Do you even know how high the market price is for that book? If you damage it, you couldn’t afford it even if you worked through your next life," the old man sneered.

"It’s calling showing appreciation, do you understand? I simply appreciate antiques! It’s not like I asked you to gift it to me," Garen said. Nowadays, he came over to bicker with the old man every day. Even if he didn’t want to see that book, he would be requesting some other stuff from the old man.

"Also, what kind of ability do you need to read a book?"

"No ability means you have no abilities."

"You don’t understand," the old man nodded in satisfaction at his own writing, "Dale Quicksilver has some conjectures about the robbery."

"What conjectures?"

"They’re investigating a crime in the rural area right now. They found a clue that indicates that the stuff stolen in my shop is still in the city. Though they are still investigating, I have hope that most of the stuff will be returned to me."

The old man put away the pen and paper on the table and capped the ink bottle. He glanced at Garen, "Also, stop thinking about the book, I mailed it to a friend a while ago; it’s no longer here."

"Then do you have anything similar here? I’m only interested in stuff similar to the emblem and that book."

"You mean you like objects that have troublesome stories behind them?" the old man asked in shock.

"Troublesome stories?" Garen was a little stunned.

"The Bronze Cross Emblem belonged to generations of wastrels. The entire family’s savings were all wasted by them. The book has a similar story. They are all objects that ruined their owner’s life!" the old man sobbed a little and exclaimed.

"Objects with troublesome stories eh?"

Garen was deep in thought.

After walking out from the antique store, he sobered up a little and pondered this problem.

"If potential can only be found on objects with troublesome backstories…" he remembered the Halo of Tragedy from a while ago, "Then what kind of potential did I absorb from those objects?"

Without realizing it, he found himself walking on the sketchy road that led him home. The houses on the two sides were scarce, clearly displaying the black and green mountain and the empty forests behind the houses.

"This is the road…"

He froze. Looking at his surroundings, he suddenly realized that it was the road where he accidentally killed a person for the first time.

The white and gray sidewalks were rutted and uneven. The road in front also had a dark red bloodstain that was clearly visible, but he wasn’t sure if it was from the murder last time. There was not a single person around, only a white car’s front lights were flashing from far away.

Garen hastily walked past the puddle shaped bloodstain. After so long, the stain had completely dried. Mixed in it were a few strands of thin and long hair.

Cold wind kept pouring down his neck, he suddenly felt cold.

Marching forward a few steps, a person appeared from the left alley and swiftly ran towards Garen’s direction.

This person was wearing a black trench coat and a round hat, and the sound made by the person’s boots were rapid and snappy.

Garen shifted his body to make room for the person to pass.

As if drunk, the person crookedly walked straight into Garen.

"Watch out," Surprised, Garen extended his arm to stabilize the person. Suddenly, he seemed to see a spark of yellow light piercing through his belly. His stomach felt a pinch like he was bitten by a mosquito.

He felt no sense of danger, no shock and or fear. Garen was stunned at first then his heart felt cold. He realized what was happening immediately and extended both of his arms to tightly squeeze the person against his chest.

"Who sent you here?"

The bones creaked and cracked as they broke one by one. The person slumped and relied on Garen for strength. Losing all ability to resist, both of the person’s arms and multiple ribs were broken by Garen.

The eerie thing was, that person still tightly hugged onto Garen without a word.

Garen, holding onto the person, was about to ask some questions when he saw a silhouette from the faraway alley pointing something at him.

A shiver escalated for his foot to his brain, a surge of terror that he’s never felt before overwhelmed him.

Garen felt like the tip of a knife was placed on his nose. The closeness to danger made him numb.

Borrowing light from the moon, he was pretty certain that the person had faint red pupils and was holding a black gun.

Bang!

A crisp and loud sound.

Simultaneously, as Garen saw a spark, he also felt a small hot object entering his chest with precision. The person he was holding also shuddered, as he too had been shot.

His chest was burning as if the skin had been scraped off.

"They’re even using guns now!" Garen didn’t have time to think to push. He pushed away from the person on top of him and mimicked what he had seen in movies by making a fancy jump to the left. "Bang, bang!" He dodged two bullets.

Using his newly increased agility attribute, his reaction and physical speed were a little faster than his opponent.

The bullets almost hit his calf but instead created two yellow sparks on the ground.

Protecting his face with his arms, Garen was no longer afraid. Rather, he felt a mixture of excitement and astonishment.

He knew that the bullet went through a body before landing on him; therefore the damage was minimal and only resulted in dead skin being lodged inside him muscle. From that analysis, he roughly estimated how much damage each bullet could cause him. As long as his vitals weren’t hit at a short distance, he would not die at this scene.

After dying once, Garen had absolutely no fear of death anymore. He felt his heart beating crazily fast, but heavy and strong. All the strength in his body exploded out of him.

After three shots, he ran towards that person while protecting his face with his arms.

The person hiding in the alley thought the first shot had already killed him. The other two shots were only fired to make sure of that. The person thought Garen would have no more strength, let alone having that explosive force.

The distance between the two wasn’t far, only about ten steps. Dodging three shots, Garen aggressively dashed toward the person who panicked and raised his arm to shoot again.

PA!

Garen slapped the person’s hand, sending the gun flying for 20 meters before finally rolling down to the middle of the road.

Garen grabbed this person’s neck with one hand and punched the stomach with the other. A black shadow flashed and sliced across his arm.

Garen felt pain in his right hand, and looking closely, he saw the opponent was holding in the back of his palm a dark blue dagger. The blueness of the blade eerily shone under the moonlight.

Garen looked at his wound. The cut on his right hand was starting to turn blue.

"Poison!" Waves of coldness unexpectedly emerged from his heart.

He wasn’t sure what weapon the opponent held since it so easily cut through his skin. He also didn’t know what poison was applied to the blade; however, the numbness and itch he felt on his wound meant it was not a regular poison.

Garen suddenly remembered his sister Ying Er, who was studying at home. He remembered Old Man Gregor who fooled around every day in his antique shop. Finally, he remembered the martial arts he had found and planned to master in this lifetime.

He didn’t want to die. He only traveled to this world a while ago and had just adjusted to the life here. He didn’t want to die! Not when he finally had the chance to live again!

"If you want me to die, I’ll drag you down with me!" Garen snarled, he charged forward, held onto the person’s hand that was holding onto the dagger and slashed in the opposite direction.

Whooshing, the person’s chest was deeply cut, and a loud scream filled the air.

The voice was that of a woman.

Chapter 26: Ability (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The black trench coat was slit right open exposing the bandage covering the chest area underneath. The dagger had made a terrifying palm-sized wound.

"If you don’t want to die then give me the remedy!" Garen held the woman’s neck with one hand and almost lifted her into the air. "If you want me to die instead? I’ll finish you first!"

The bloody-eyed woman hung in the middle of the air. Her hand desperately tried to hold onto Garen's arm and break free. Her other hand reached into the inner pocket of the trench coat and found a small yellow package.

Garen violently wrestled it out of her hand.

"I’ll use it on you first, of course, if you are the type that is not afraid of death, I can also throw you on the street naked. I am sure those homeless people would not mind some free enjoyment." The poison began to overwhelm Garen as his breath shortened. He broke the package with an open hand and pushed the powder inside against the woman’s chest.

"No… Eat it…" The woman barely made out of a few words.

Garen put her down and squeezed her face as he poured half of the powder into her mouth before stopping.

"Cough…" The woman coughed as soon as Garen let her go. It looked like she was about to cough her lungs out but was afraid to spit out the powder. She covered her mouth and swallowed all the powder before she sat straight onto the ground, she wearily looked at Garen.

Garen felt the numbing sensation spread over half of his shoulder and knew that the poison was taking effect on his body.

When he confirmed that the woman had no negative symptoms, he tried to fight back the poison a little longer before he finally was certain and chugged the entire powder down his throat.

The yellow powder tasted sour with no odd flavor. It melted immediately as soon as it entered Garen's mouth.

"Go!" Garen lifted the bloody-eyed woman as he began to jog forward.

Ten minutes later, they arrived at a grass field on the shadowy side of a desolate hill.

Garen leaned against the tree and left the woman by the side as he sat down to rest. He raised his arm to see that the blue wound was fading. The numbing sensation still remained.

Under the shadows of the tree without the cast of moonlight, Garen finally had the time to carefully examine the hostage.

Her silver-white hair scattered across her shoulder. The delicacy and beauty on her face cast a slight hint of nobility vibe on her. Her figure was graceful with her slim waist to what appeared to be a perfect figure.

"Be honest, who are you? Why did you attack me?" Garen asked emotionlessly as he sat on the side. Without the help of a gun and given her poor combat ability, he was not afraid that she would be able to escape.

"You killed our man last time, of course we would have to find you," the girl regained her breath and answered. "There’s nothing you can do even if you catch me. I will not reveal any secrets."

"Why would I want your secrets?" Garen felt the last numbing sensation disappear from his wound and felt relieved. "If I told you that the last time I killed your man was only an accident, would you believe it?"

"Do you think that’s realistic?" the woman said mockingly. She stared coldly at him, "Enough is enough, the reason why you caught me is to f*ck me; as long as you don’t throw me to the homeless it’s fine."

Garen knew too well that if such a beauty were to be left in the hands of the homeless people, within one night the news next morning would report a naked body found beside the garbage dump.

"You woman..." Garen approached her as he began to touch the woman’s body.

She leaned against the tree slanted. She didn’t resist his hand movement as she chose to close her eyes.

But what surprised her was that Garen only searched all of her pockets and grabbed a few items before retrieving his hand.

"I would assume that your position within the organization is quite high? It would not be worth it for me to kill you right now." Garen pondered with a black gold coin in his hand. "Tell me where did you put the stolen artifact?"

"You are also looking for that?" The woman shockingly glanced at him, "We searched the item, but it’s not within the city."

"Just tell me where it is."

"You can find it if you go alone," she sneered. "I thought you belonged to the other side, but it looks like it’s only you alone." Through a few sentences, she was able to accurately guess Garen’s background.

"To be honest, the person you killed was not important at all. Since you can’t find the item either, why don’t we cooperate?"

Garen raised his eyebrows. "Do you think I’d believe you?"

"If only Jia Ti had been by my side, and if I hadn’t believed that I would have been safe with a gun, do you think you could have gotten within two steps of me?" the woman laughed with an icy tone.

"Then why did you shoot first?"

"I will always make the first move!" she arrogantly said.

"You only guessed I belonged to the other side, what if I wasn’t?" Garen’s voice turned cold.

"I’ll just tie you to a rock and throw you in the river after I killed you, no one would ever find you again," she didn’t directly respond, but her answer was clear. She would not let any victim escape even if they were innocent.

After a pause, she continued.

"Since I asked to partner up, then I have my ways to make you believe my genuineness. With your ability, you are at least a level four to five fighter. It is also mainly because of how strong your body is; a bullet can’t even go through you. If you work for me—"

"No way it will happen!" Garen interrupted her. "I won’t work for you. I almost killed you, so you must want to kill me too in your heart."

She laughed, "Your combat style is fairly similar to the White Cloud Gate’s, with a powerful explosive force which makes it difficult to avoid. But with such impeccable body condition at a young age, you must have trained a unique body strengthening technique. You can let the other side know to contact me and make a promise. The White Cloud Gate is not a small force within the city."

"The White Cloud Gate is also a part of this? It’s known within your circle?" Garen was slightly surprised.

"Renowned is an understatement," she sneered again. "In Huai Shan, Dojo Master Fei’s words are the governor general’s words. Especially in the shadows, he is similar to the underground emperor. Anyone who dares to challenge his supremacy is dead."

"Let’s go to the Dojo then." Without hesitation, Garen grabbed her and dashed toward the White Cloud Gate.

*****************

Twenty minutes later.

Fei Baiyun sat at the practicing hall on the second floor. He took a sip out of the coffee. He peacefully looked at the two people in front of him.

"This is not a big deal at all. It was just an accident that you killed one of their men." His vision settled on the silver-white woman with a ponytail. "Grace, how’s your mother, Madame Yalan, doing? The last time we met was years ago."

"Thank you for asking Dojo Master. My mother has been doing fine," she answered terror-stricken. She kept her head down afraid to look at Fei Baiyun. She had thought that Garen was only an ordinary trainee within the White Cloud Gate. Maybe he would be an actual Disciple, but even then it wouldn’t have mattered.

But as soon as she arrived, she realized that Garen was the Dojo Master’s Formal Disciple. Cold sweat began to drip as soon as she understood the situation. She knew how powerful Fei Baiyuan was in Huai Shan, especially for someone who lived in the shadows, and yet she almost killed his Formal Disciple.

Garen who stood by her side saw her sides drenched in sweat.

"This thing is not a big deal at all." Fei Baiyun took another sip of the coffee. "But since you used a pistol, then the nature of this accident is now different."

Grace lowered her head further.

"We’ll provide any form of compensation for you! This is our mistake."

"Since my disciple is running short on money, you can help him a little. Also, the artifact that he is looking for from you guys, return it at the same time."

"Lastly, and most importantly, Garen himself has to agree to settle this."

"We agree to all the conditions! We’ll do the best we can!" Grace said genuinely, "We’ll do the best to serve Master Garen."

Garen shook his head, "All my requirements are included, if you want to provide more compensations then give it to my master and my elder apprentices." He understood that if it were not for Fei Baiyun, this woman would have given him more trouble.

"You." Fei Baiyuan pointed at Garen and started laughing, "I just went to a gathering with the governor and you brought back a wonderful gift for me. This is only because we haven’t released any information regarding you joining the White Cloud Gate as a Formal Disciple. In a few days, no one would dare to cause trouble for my disciple."

"Grace is pretty unlucky this time. She mistakenly thought Garen was the opponent’s hitman. But I am curious as to why you wanted to stop their car?"

"I saw the stolen artifact that I wanted," Garen rushed to explain.

Grace, with a deep resignation, "You just became a Formal Disciple. I’ll admit that I was unlucky this time. If it had been a bit later, I would not have ordered to kill immediately if I had seen the face."

"That’s enough Grace. You have to repay for the mistake you made. Once Garen is satisfied, you’ll be free."

Fei Baiyuan stated with a soothing smile on this face. "But if I hear you that you are not genuine enough…"

The words sent a shiver down Grace’s spine as she immediately answered.

Fei Baiyuan’s appearance may have suggested that he looked calm and relaxed, but if he was angry… It would be normal for him to murder entire families and even go after the relatives in their hometown.

The underground emperor always believed in leaving no risk behind. Once he identified his enemy, from the children to the grandparents would have no way to escape under his dark reign.

"Ok, you can go now," Fei Baiyuan waved his hand as he dismissed Grace.

With respect, Grace immediately dashed to the stairs.

Garen sat straight with his head lowered.

"Master… I have caused you trouble with this incident."

"There is no trouble. I want you to know that your senior sister and brother all have their enterprises, or better described as forces, and are tightly knit with the Dojo. Together we are a strong force not to be undermined," Fei Baiyuan stood up as he said peacefully.

"I planned to tell you about these things later, but I didn’t expect that you were already involved with this. Today when you faced the pistol and escaped, you must have had a lot of thoughts."

"Yes." Garen nodded his head deep in thought.

"We practice martial arts not only because it strengthens our body. You’ll encounter similar incidents in the future. You’ll have to learn how to handle these incidents. There is also another thing I didn’t tell you." Fei Baiyun paused.

"I originally had seven formal disciples."

Garen was shocked, but then he quickly realized as he felt his heart drenched in ice.

He understood his master’s words.

Only three were left out of the original seven Formal Disciples. The other four were either dead or had other accidents.

"Grace will be your practice dummy for the Critical Fist Technique as part of her punishment. It will take her years to recover after. That’s all for this incident. Keep in touch with her after this; it would be up to you to see if you can convince her to join your force."

Chapter 27: Speechless (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Go to the treatment room to treat your chest wound." Fei Baiyuan left a few words before he casually strolled downstairs.

Garen stood in place as his expression changed. He didn’t make a sound.

He watched his master went downstairs as his figure disappeared around the corner. He waited for his footsteps to fade away before he gently stretched the cloth around his chest.

A copper bullet was embedded in the left side of his chest near his heart, penetrating his pale skin about one centimeter deep.

He dug the bullet out with his hand as the wound on his chest immediately contracted. The edge of the wound was a little burnt with only a sliver of blood flowing.

"So this is a bullet..." He gazed at the bullet in deep thought.

He went downstairs and asked the doctor at the White Cloud Gate to treat his wounds before he slowly walked out of the dojo’s main gate.

On the empty streets, a few patrol police dressed in full black strolled in front of the dojo. They were talking and laughing as they held a dim oil lamp.

A group of men in gloomy factory uniforms sat on a set of stairs across the street. Drunk from alcohol, they kept their hands their pockets. Garen didn’t know what they were talking about.

"There’s a clothing factory near here that manufactures jackets and cotton clothes,"a male trainer said casually as he passed by Garen. He glanced at the clothes Garen wore.

"Hey man, you’re training pretty late. Where are you going? Do you need a ride?"

"That’s fine; I’m waiting for someone." Garen smiled as he pointed at the black car in the front.

The car window rolled down as Grace’s delicate face appeared.

"Not bad!" The male trainer laughed a bit and patted Garen’s shoulder without saying anything else. He then approached the other parked car.

Grace stepped out of the car and walked in front of Garen.

"Garen…" She momentarily didn’t know what to call him as she hesitated.

"Just call me by my name." Garen shrugged, "Let’s leave and head to my home. I’ll listen to your situation on the car."

"As long as you are pleased, we’ll provide any compensations!" Grace adopted a pleading look.

"I didn’t dare to explain in front of the Dojo Master, but the actual situation is that we are not the

only ones who stole the artifacts. In Huaishan City there’s another company competing with us in this area."

"No rush, explain to me in detail."

Grace looked at Garen’s expression and slightly relaxed since as he didn’t seem to be irate.

Once the two got in the car and closed the doors, Grace slowly started the car as the antique vehicle began to lurch forward. Amid the rumble of the engine, Garen sat silently in the passenger seat as he stared at the retreating scene of the night.

The light fragrance of Grace’s perfume whiffed into his nose. The street lights cast shadows across his face one by one. His previous excitement finally calmed.

"I am part of the Manuyllton Corporation, one of the three biggest gang-related companies in Huaishan. One of the other two companies has no common business areas with us, but the Blackplume Corporation also accepts hiring missions and the selling of restricted items like us. They are the ones that escalated the tension between us," Grace explained as she drove.

"Restricted items and hiring missions? What are these?" Garen lowered his voice.

"Restricted items include firearms, artifacts, and drugs like rainbow candy. Hiring missions include, robbery, or even murder. This is nothing surprising and a lot of gang-related companies are similar. These two areas offer the most lucrative profits, while the primary operations of the company act as a cover. The money from the legitimate business is only considered a bonus."

Grace started to feel less tense.

"Your company is called Manuyllton Corporation? What’s the size of the company?"

"There are approximately 50 people that act as the core. The other supporting individuals total to less than 200 people. I am middle to upper management and in the middle of the pack. But don’t worry, with Master Fei, the upper management will do anything to compensate you. I am certain about this point."

"Do you still have the artifacts with you from the first time we met?" Garen asked as he remembered the Potential increase from when he tried to stop the car.

"The artifacts are still there and in one of my houses. Do you want them now?"

Grace let out a sigh of relief as she was afraid that Garen wouldn’t ask. But since he asked, the problem became much easier. Garen was clearly new to the scene, but with the backup of Master Fei and his three seniors, even the boss of the corporation would not dare shortchange the compensation.

"Now would be the best time. Where do you live?"

"Downtown, beside the central park."

"Not too far, let’s go grab the artifacts and then I’ll go home. This is part of the compensation." Garen nodded.

"Then the other compensation…"

"Let’s not rush this. You have some means of selling artifacts in your company right? Maybe I’ll have to ask you for help in the future," Garen said without any fluctuation in his voice.

"No problem, I’m at your disposal." Grace immediately nodded.

After a short while, the car slowly stopped in a downtown area with a circular park. Grace got out of the car and entered a white building on the left side. She ran out after a few minutes.

Once she got in the car, she placed a black bag in front of Garen.

"These are the artifacts we found in the city. There are a total of three items. Are these what you’re looking for?"

As soon as Garen touched the bag, streams of coldness flowed from the bag into his body.

Joy emerged in his heart as he opened the bag without much of an outward reaction. Inside was a white rectangular wooden box with a shade of yellow. The lock was open.

As he lifted the cover, there were three cross emblems sitting inside on the black velvet cover. From left to right, there was a bronze, a burgundy, and a silver-white artifact.

APM

The three emblems had the same design, only the letters in the middle were different. They were A, P, and M.

Garen immediately recognized that the burgundy emblem was the one lost by Old Man Gregor. It was also the one that had Potential.

The moment he opened the box, an enormous amount of Potential flowed evenly into both of his hands. The cold streams flowed directly from the veins in his arm, past his shoulder, and across his neck before they concentrated around his eyes.

Garen clearly saw the Potential Meter in his visual field increase steadily.

From 80%, it rapidly rose to 90, and then to 100, 110, 120, 128, 133.

In the few minutes since he had opened the box, his potential skyrocketed to above 200%.

At this moment, the stream of energy from the box began to slow down.

Garen then felt a source of potential from the burgundy cross emblem in the middle, the same artifact he had discovered at the old man’s antique store.

While the burgundy emblem continued to release potential slowly but steadily, the other two emblems had released all of their potential.

He gently touched the bronze cross emblem’s surface as the rough and cold sensation transmitted to his fingertip. He only took this emblem.

"Nothing else?"

"No, these are the only things I have with me. Out of the three emblems, only the middle one was collected from the city. The others were transported from other places." Grace rushed to answer.

"I’ll take this emblem with me. The other requirement is that the rest of the compensation goes to my master. Now take me back."

Garen responded simply and did not say any more. He slowly caressed the bronze cross emblem.

"Ok. So when should I train with you?" She looked relieved as her feeling of impending doom subsided.

"It will start after the Formal Disciple ceremony."

Grace forced a smile. She had heard about the role of practice trainers at the White Cloud Gate. Certain explosive techniques must be practiced on humans to measure the results. Only a few knew the details about the practice trainers. Rarely would they be healthy without any injuries.

The best case scenario was to have a few broken bones, while more severe consequences included organ damage. It would take at least a few years to recover, but it was also normal for the practice trainer to be killed. Usually, they would find people who only cared about money and not life. If she wanted to survive this time, it would depend on Garen.

******

The car gradually came to a halt two hundred meters away from Garen’s neighborhood. Garen gently closed the door after walking out of the car. He watched the car turn before it disappeared.

He raised his right hand and looked at a piece of white paper. The Confederation Bank’s name and an absurdly large number were printed on it.

"One million dollar bank deposit. Money comes pretty fast." He shoved the deposit slip in his pants pocket and he strolled toward the direction of his home.

"I am back."

As he closed the door behind him, the living room was pitch black. Only a yellow light slipped through the door cracks of his sister’s bedroom.

No one responded.

"Only two people at home again?" He took a breath before he changed into his slippers and turned on the light.

He sat on the sofa. A dark yellow wooden cup filled with brewed black coffee was left on the table.

Thirsty, Garen chugged the coffee. It tasted bitter but sweet as it was completely cold. The edge of the cup had the scent of a cigarette.

"Father didn’t finish after he brewed it." He put the cup down and leaned against the sofa. He felt the bronze cross emblem in his pocket continue to provide him with potential.

"I don’t know how much potential this emblem will provide. The other two were finished in just a few short moments."

He felt joyful as his potential in his vision continued to rise.

"As long as I have sources of potential, I can continue to grow with the help of Potential points. There is almost no limit. I am confident that I can surpass anyone!"

Suddenly, the smile that appeared on his face faded.

He realized that the potential increase had slowed down compared to moments ago.

The coldness from the emblem continued to flow without any difference in thickness, but the numbers on the Potential Meter began to slow down.

"What’s going on?"

Garen sat straight as he carefully examined the increase in potential. From the moment he touched the emblem until coming home now, the potential points had already rocketed to above 300%. Now, however, the rate of increase began to diminish.

Chapter 28: Speechless (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the beginning, the Potential meter would increase by one percent every two seconds, but now, it would only increase by one percent every four seconds. Furthermore, the speed of this increase was still regressing.

Garen closed his eyes to fully experience this change. From his pockets, the Potential flowed into his body, eventually ticking the Potential meter in his eyes. Soon, he immersed himself into the process of increasing the Potential.

"The density of qi has increased… but the concentration has decreased." Garen opened his eyes as he slowly stroked the emblem in his pocket.

As the density of qi decreased, the speed of his Potential meter’s increase had also slowed down. Finally, after ten minutes or so, the qi had steadily slowed down. Only a very thin flow of qi was still entering his body, and the Potential meter would only tick once in a long while.

"Normally, the antiques and jewelry would return to normal after having the qi inside them absorbed, but this emblem isn't doing that. Does it still have more Potential, or is the absorption of qi just slowing down? Could it be possible that the Potential has already been used up, and the emblem is producing more?"

Creak.

The door opened.

Garen stopped his thought as he saw Ying Er, in her white pajamas, walk in while yawning.

"Why’d you come back so late?" After the accident from last time, she had become more relaxed around him. However, they still had not spoken much out of embarrassment.

"I had some business to deal with at the dojo," Garen casually answered in a low voice, completely forgetting to imitate the original Garen’s usual tone.

"Something at the dojo?" Ying Er was suddenly interested. "What, you finally got expelled?"

"You really want me to get expelled?" Garen asked back in disappointment.

"With your strength? I’m not gonna lie, but I can beat you up with one hand and one leg," Ying Er replied with despise in her voice. "Dealing with business; a kid trying to talk like a grown man. What kind of business could you possibly have?"

Ying Er yawned again after the rant and left to get some water. she went back to her room and turned off the light.

Garen sat in the living room a little longer before going back to his room after brushing and cleaning up. His Potential meter was still growing slowly, and this absurd situation was out of his expectation. The absorption of qi had all been a one-time thing, and none had this decreasing speed at the end. Turning on his desk lamp, Garen sat in front of his desk and took out the emblem. He touched the emblem and moved his focus onto the attribute panel.

"This time, the Potential meter increased to 361%, I can use three Attribute points. "

"Enhancing intelligence would enable me to quickly master some subjects, and my studying ability would probably improve as well. I don’t think this is useful right now.

The entirety of his last life was spent on studying: he went to college, got a master’s degree, and got a good job. However, that job’s salary was still pathetically low. Studying is only useful in order to reach a higher social class later; it’s more useful in the sense of improving one’s competency. Since he had already received the higher education from Earth, Garen wasn’t too concerned with improving his intelligence.

"Agility increases the reaction speed for both my body and my nervous system, and, in addition, it would also increase my speed. This is quite useful.

"Strength and vitality are both fundamentals to the White Cloud Dojo. By enhancing these attributes, my strength, explosiveness, and my body’s resilience and recovery would all improve. These are all great options."

Garen thought. A few days after the Formal Disciple Ceremony, he would be able to learn both the White Cloud Secret Arts and the Explosive Fist Arts, maybe even the Mammoth Secret Technique.

At that time, these three Attribute points would come in great use. Using them right now seemed like a waste.

He carefully estimated the speed of qi absorption right now. "If this speed of absorption doesn’t change, I could probably get one more Attribute point in a week."

He didn’t know when this emblem would stop emitting qi; if all the qi was used up, it would be hard to find another antique like this in the entire Huaishan City. These antiques were extremely rare on their own, and they could not reproduce qi after absorption.

After confirming the situation to himself, Garen decided not to enhance his attributes frugally. These Attribute points were precious, so he could not afford to lose them on pointless enhancements.

"Let’s wait until after the ceremony."

************

The next morning, Garen woke up early and went to school after eating a pear. Ying Er had already left before him; the result of the competition had come out, and today was the day of the award ceremony.

Garen watched in the crowd and applauded with all his strength as Ying Er stood on the stage and received her third place prize money and award medal. Next to him were a few girls who wore heavy perfume that was cloying to his nose. As soon as the archery award ceremony ended, Garen hastily squeezed his way out.

"How was your sister, Garen?" Kalidor came out of nowhere and asked, tapping Garen’s shoulder.

"Third place, kind of expected, her opponents were too strong," Garen replied while covering his nose. "There’s too many people in there, I couldn’t bear the smell. How is Ai Fei, have you seen her?"

"I apologized to her about the other day, yet she didn’t say anything. What’s going on between you and her?" Kalidor asked in confusion.

Garen bitterly laughed. "She’s not talking to me either, I don’t know what’s going on."

"Who’s not talking to you?" Fayne joined from the side. "Let’s go over there. Also, Kalidor, I have to warn you about that thing."

"What thing?" Kalidor froze and asked.

"Jake told me all about it." Fayne smiled as he put his arm around Kalidor’s shoulder.

Jake came from the back and tapped Garen’s shoulder. "Fayne is overreacting, it’s not a big deal. Let’s go, Garen."

"What’s going on?" Garen was confused.

The four strolled on the path behind the classroom building; on the sides were tall and dense Winter Heron trees.

These trees were extremely cold-resistant, and their leaves do not fall during the winter. Piece by piece, the green leaves covered the morning sunlight.

Under the shades, Fayne spoke up in a low volume.

"Kalidor, do you really know Ai Fei?"

"She’s all right, a nice and kind girl." Kalidor blinked and asked, "What is it?"

Fayne hesitated before continuing, "We’ve been friends for so long, I’ll just say it. Ai Fei, she’s a gold digger. To be honest, I don’t think she’s right for you, man." He saw Kalidor’s face changing color.

"You are different from me. We all know I’m with a different girl every other week, but I’m not invested in them like you do, Kalidor. This is who you are."

"And, you know where I’m from and my family… I’m used to these kind of things…"

"Okay, enough, I get what you mean." Kalidor’s expression turned gloomy; he didn’t argue with Fayne, because he was already familiar with this friend of his.

Jake looked at Garen with a sympathetic expression.

"Why are you staring at me like that?" Garen asked.

"Don’t you like Ai Fei?" Jake whispered. "You even asked her out and got rejected."

"What?" Garen was dumbfounded. "I asked her out? And got rejected? Where did you hear this? When did I ask her out?"

"Ai Fei told her roommates so." Jake glance at Kalidor who was walking in front of them, and then gave Garen an even more sympathetic look.

"I… f**k…" Garen was speechless. These few days, he had been busy at the dojo, without paying much attention to things at the academy. He didn’t expect Ai Fei to gossip to her friends about that night’s misunderstanding. He was only trying to ease her embarrassment at the feast the other day, but Ai Fei misconstrued it as flirting

And, when he asked to escort her home and Ai Fei refused, that became him getting "rejected".

"When did I say I liked that girl?" Garen didn’t even want to say her name. He originally thought she was a nice and independent girl, yet he suddenly learned that she could make up a story out of thin air.

"So Ai Fei and Kalidor are together now?" Garen asked.

Jake nodded. "Ai Fei went to Kalidor’s dorm room last night and didn’t go back." Jake patted Garen’s shoulder. "Don’t be too upset."

"Garen, don’t blame Kalidor on this one, Ai Fei approached him first. To tell you the truth, Jake and I knew what kind of person she is; she got in touch with me a while ago and said she had a crush on me. I rejected her, then she started hanging out with all of us."

"Seems like she’s taking a move on Kalidor after knowing his family’s background."

Garen was speechless as he looked at Kalidor who was also looking back at him with a guilty expression.

"Don’t be like this, Garen. A girl like Ai Fei isn’t worth getting upset with." Jake once again patted Garen’s shoulders in an attempt to comfort him.

"But I honestly don’t even like her!" Garen helplessly explained. "Think about it, with my sister watching all day, how can I be interested in other girls?"

The three of them didn’t seem to buy it.

"I didn’t think she was this good at acting. I’m telling you the truth; I didn’t ask her out, she’s not my type. That night, I thought she was in trouble and helped her out. Since we went together, I asked if she needed me to escort her back. She said no, and I went home. That’s it."

"Don’t worry about it, we won’t look down on you. These sad memories, just let them go." Jake shook his head.

"Jake and I saw you guys getting really close to her, that’s why we couldn’t approach you these days," Fayne added. "Garen, she’s not worth it, don’t overthink this."

Garen helplessly shrugged his shoulders; he knew all of his explanations were in vain. "Does everyone in the class know about this?"

Jake and Fayne sympathetically nodded.

"Okay…" Garen felt a bit confused. "Well, not that I know what kind of person she really is. Who are we going to copy our homework from?"

"I guess I’ll ask Lan Ruo; see if she’s willing to lend us a hand," Fayne answered.

"Never mind, I’ll do it myself." Garen shook his head. Seeing the commiserative expression of the trio before him, he felt frustrated.

"That girl isn’t a virgin," Kalidor suddenly said.

"That’s for sure." Fayne nodded with a smirk. "Right, Garen, my cousin’s friend, Felicity, came to visit again. She asked if you have time. Apparently, she wanted to ask you something. Since when did you two hook up?"

"Felicity? That girl who went to Jaderipple Lake with us?" Garen asked. After receiving a positive answer, he was puzzled. "Why is she looking for me?"

"I don’t know." Fayne shrugged.

"She must have fallen in love with you at first sight." Jake laughed next to him. "Felicity’s family isn’t just ordinarily wealthy; if you could date her, you don’t have to worry about money for the rest of your life."

"Do I look like that kind of person?" Garen twisted Jake’s arm and said, "Can you talk like a human being?"

As they were speaking, two innocent girls approached them, with both of them holding delicate lace parasols, wearing white dirndl dresses; they both looked like daughters of nobles.

As the two groups approached each other, all the boys including Garen straightened their backs, paying much more attention to their appearances.

"Garen, your fly is open!" Jake suddenly shouted.

Right as the two girls looked over, they heard the shout. They both turned around and giggled while covering their mouth.

Garen’s face heated up as he looked down at his pant’s zippers. Thank god it was closed! He furiously turned around to go after Jake who had already ran far away.

"You’re dead!"

Chapter 29: Surprise (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Morning of October 1st.

White Cloud Martial Colosseum.

Bright light beamed in from the wooden window, landing on the carpet. Faintly visible dust floated in the air.

While Garen respectfully stood in the middle of the colosseum, Master Fei Baiyun sat in his high chair with Senior Sister and 2nd Senior Brother standing beside him.

Third Senior Brother stood to the right, holding a square wooden plate covered in red cloth.

Both sides of the colosseum had a row of chairs and a dozen men sat scattered in these seats, divided into two groups. They were all wearing white robes with sharp and fiery gazes. Leading them were two elderly men between the age of fifty to sixty.

"Since you were directly chosen by me as a disciple, the extra etiquette will be unnecessary. Today we are honored to have Master Hurley and Master Hester here as our witnesses. Let’s begin."

Fei Baiyun nodded towards Joshua, his third disciple.

"Begin the ceremony!" Joshua shouted. As flippant as he usually was, he did not dare to be glib at events like this.

Two young girls wearing white robes walked up. One of them held a red envelope, the other held a maroon wooden cup. Each held a wooden plate.

"Read the code of conduct," Joshua proclaimed.

Garen straightened his body and picked up the red envelope. He opened the seal and recited the code of conduct inside.

"Do not disrespect your master; do not be ungrateful! Do not flaunt and show off; do not be arrogant! Do not commit crimes; do not take what is not yours! Do not be conceited or complacent, do not be lazy or procrastinate!"

"Disciple Garen Lombard promises to follow these rules and make our dojo proud!"

"Memorize these rules. Do you have anything else to say?" Fei Baiyun looked at him with a smile.

Garen closed the envelope, then kneeled on the floor.

After three kowtows, he lifted the wooden cup from the plate and presented it to Fei Baiyun with both hands.

Fei Baiyun accepted the cup and drank a sip of black tea from it. He then took a feathered pen from Joshua and swiftly wrote down his name on the envelope. He presented the envelope to the two witnesses.

"Will the witnesses please sign their names!" Joshua shouted again.

The two elders both smiled and each signed their names on the envelope.

The bald elder to the left said with a salute, "I didn't expect Master Fei to have another disciple at his age. He has great talent and a calm mind. Congratulations!"

Fei Baiyun let out a satisfied smile. "I’m getting old too, Garen will be my last disciple. I will not have the energy for another one. My hopes and the White Cloud Gate’s hope depends on the four of them from now on."

The past few days Master Fei had been investigating Garen’s background, his personality, and the way he treats people. Fei Baiyun was extremely satisfied with the results.

Most importantly, Garen’s talent might not be the greatest, but it was worthy of the gate’s martial arts inheritance. At the very least, the Mammoth Secret Technique would continue. Currently, only his second disciple Frank practiced this move and fighters like him were prone to danger every day, leaving his Secret Technique at risk of being lost forever.

"Brother Fei, what are you talking about? If you are old, what about us? We are about the same age, but I still want to live for few more years and have a few more disciples of my own." The red-haired elder said while nodding his head.

Fei Baiyun stood up. Behind him on the rosewood table were a few memorial tablets. Words from an unknown language were written all over them.

"With the sixth generation of our White Cloud Gate under my leadership, let us kowtow to honor our former masters and ancestors."

Garen kowtowed respectfully toward the tablets. Fei Baiyun watched the obedient Garen and nodded in approval.

"It is unfortunate that your parents are out of town today. The two masters are always busy, so we had to rush the ceremony. Since the ceremony is finished, you will henceforth be my last inheriting disciple. You will take the Gate’s pride as your own."

"Yes, Master!" Garen nodded with a solemn and respectful expression.

"Very well, now you may rise."

Garen slowly stood up as the ceremony concluded.

The colosseum was on the second floor of the White Cloud Gate and a crowd of mostly Formal Disciples from the dojo had already gathered at the staircase entrance. The dojo had three types of students: regular, formal, and core disciples.

Garen had become a core disciple in such a short time, in part due to his talent and young age.

Fei Baiyun’s White Cloud Gate was different from the other Gates with regards to the process of accepting students because of its status in the city.

From reading the code of conduct earlier, Garen noticed that the White Cloud Gate was a sect of both good and evil since the code of conduct did not mention anything about morality and ethics.

Basically, as long as one did not betray the gate and did not do anything that would harm the gate’s reputation, one could do whatever he or she pleased.

After the ceremony, Fei Baiyun and the other two masters stayed behind to chat, while the other disciples and students left to get ready for lunch.

Garen followed his Senior Sister and Senior Brother downstairs. Walking behind them, he saw Rosetta’s white tiger tattoo on her naked back. The tiger looked ferocious and the tattoo moved with Rosetta’s movements, emitting a blood scented vigor.

The tattoo spanned from her back to her chest and across her shoulder. The back of the tiger had a clearly visible blood red spine.

Upon closer inspection, Garen realized that there was actually a blood red scar on her shoulder. She had tattooed the tiger on the scar, and used it as the tiger’s spine.

Second Disciple Frank was tall and sturdy, he was speaking with Master Hurley’s disciple enthusiastically. That man was also a bruiser, the two seemed to be just each other’s type. They were also old acquaintances.

Senior Sister Rosetta was speaking with one of Master Hester’s disciples. The guy seemed to be interested in her and was making a move on her.

Garen sat next to Joshua as he listened to the boring conversations from both sides.

The two junior disciples were both the type of people who were unable to sit still for a second.

"Senior Brother, is it true that Formal Disciples can only get to the intermediate level of the White Cloud Secret Arts?" Garen asked.

"It’s true because the later levels require some rare medicines and other conditions. Only the core disciples can obtain these medicines from the dojo. Why do you ask? You’ve only learned the beginner level of the Secret Arts and are still far from the intermediate so what’s the hurry?" Joshua was puzzled. "Well, since we aren’t doing anything and you have now completed the ceremony, I suppose it won’t hurt to explain the later stages to you."

"I’m just curious," Garen laughed. "Any man who is in martial arts would want to know the future direction of his training."

"You sound pretty mature." Joshua nodded, "From my own experience, the intermediate level of the White Cloud Secret Arts can increase your strength by half. The expert level, which only our Master, Senior Sister, and Senior Brother have achieved, can actually double one’s strength. Our Senior Sister’s strength grew by 100 pounds, and our Senior Brother grew by 150 pounds. The expert level of the White Cloud Secret Arts is the highest level achieved by people from our dojo. The master level was only achieved by the founder who created our gate. I hear that combined with the Mammoth Secret Technique, his strength could really match that of a mammoth!"

"Force of a mammoth! That would be over two thousand pounds!" Garen was astonished.

"Nobody has tested it before, but it is indeed very powerful," Joshua said, stroking his chin with great anticipation.

After some chatting, the Gate provided lunch for everyone, then the two masters left with their disciples. Some other guests showed up at the dojo to congratulate them on the ceremony.

These distinguished guests included the mayor and the governor.

With the addition of these other guests, the ceremony was enough to influence all of Huaishan City.

After the reception, it was already late afternoon. The food eaten at lunch had already been digested and expended as energy.

After dinner, Fei Baiyun called Garen in front of a small, narrow room.

A bald and half-naked elder sat cross-legged on the ground in front of the room. His body was full of muscle, his veins were like dark snakes coiling on his body, and his long white beard descended onto his chest. Bowing down and showing great respect, Fei Baiyun went up and whispered a few words to the old man.

The bald elder nodded, opened his eyes, and looked at Garen, seemingly trying to memorize his face. Then, he closed his eyes again without saying a word.

Fei Baiyun nodded to Garen and pushed open the door.

Creeeaaak.

The door opened to a room shrouded in complete darkness. Fei Baiyun lit up an oil lamp on the wall and the dim light filled the cramped room.

In the room there were some notebooks scattered between many bookshelves.

"These are martial arts practice notebooks from our ancestors. You can go through them as you wish. But never mind that for now. Follow me inside."

Fei Baiyun stopped Garen from opening up one of the notebooks and strode past the bookshelves.

"This place is safely guarded by uncle Bai, who has remembered your scent. As long as you don’t bring others, you can come here on your own from now on. This is one of the privileges of being my disciple."

"Yes Master, I understand."

Fei Baiyun nodded as they approached the last row of shelves. On the last shelf was a red teapot-shaped container.

Fei Baiyun took down the teacup and emptied into his hand. A small red pill rolled out of the spout.

He handed the pill to Garen. "Eat it!"

Garen took the pill, put it into his mouth, and he swallowed it without any hesitation.

"Master, what was that pill?"

"Body Enhancement Pill. Your White Cloud Secret Arts is intermediate level already, right?"

Fei Baiyun looked at Garen with a faint smile. Garen was shocked and didn’t know how to reply.

"Don’t worry, the beginner level of the White Cloud Secret Arts is the easiest to surpass. In addition to my special herbal medicine incense, advancing in a short time isn’t that rare. Some of our former masters in the gate reached the second level even faster because they had great talent and potential. However, once you reach this level, you cannot advance to the next without specially made medicine."

He put the red teacup back on the shelf.

"Remember to come here and take a pill once per day and you’ll be able to improve your White Cloud Secret Arts. This technique cannot be mastered with just practice, but practice is also crucial of course."

"Yes, Master." Garen held his surprise and replied. He felt like Fei Baiyun’s eyes were like a pair of searchlights and he couldn’t hide anything from them.

"Don’t try to hide your skills. You are only at the elementary level of the Explosive Fist Arts, which is not that big of a deal. I’ve seen a lot of people like you and in the real martial arts community this is quite average."

Fei Baiyun spit out all of Garen’s secrets at once. Watching his new disciple’s face of embarrassment, he felt a sense of gleeful satisfaction. If he hadn’t found out this disciple’s secrets, he would not be in such a rush to take him as a disciple.

As for the "real martial arts community" he mentioned, if there were really that many students easily learning the Explosive Fist Arts, the White Cloud Gate would have taken over the province already. He only said this to make sure Garen wouldn’t be too full of himself.

Someone with talents like Garen had only appeared once in the history of the White Cloud Gate. He was born a White Cloud disciple, his body perfectly fit with the White Cloud Gate’s techniques, and he had great talent.

Garen knew his secrets were exposed, so he didn’t say anything else, but laughed it up.

[ And here I was, afraid I was too exceptional…]

Chapter 30: Surprise (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"It’s fine if you want to hide your true powers. It’s impressive that you reached such a level at your age, and it is probably better for you if fewer people know what you are capable of. It will seem more reasonable if you revealed your skills after several years of training," Fei Baiyun said, patting Garen’s shoulders.

"Okay, let’s go to the training floor. Today, I will teach you the White Cloud Combat Arts. These skills are not only used in combat, but also used in killing your opponents," he continued.

"Yes! Master!" Garen was excited.

**********

Several minutes later.

On the second floor of the Martial Arts Hall.

Fei Baiyun and Garen stood across from each other. The evening sun made the carpet shine scarlet.

"Your fundamentals are good, so I will teach you the entry level stances first."

Fei Baiyun stepped forward and raised his right palm, slanting it upwards. He also put his left fist by his waist.

"This is the basic stance of White Cloud Combat Arts. Take a closer look," Fei Baiyun said with a clear voice. He saw Joshua coming from the first floor and nodded his head. Joshua looked at him and closed off the stairway with a cover.

"There are four basic skills in the White Cloud Combat Arts: Swing, Rush, Stomp, and Strike. These skills will help you in attacking, dodging, defending, and assassinating during fights. You can use them in whatever order you want. I will show you the Stomp first," Fei Baiyun continued.

After finishing the sentence, Fei Baiyun stomped forward with a single foot. His body leaned forward and it looked like he put all his body weight on that foot.

*Pong*

The floor shook and the noise it made echoed in the hall.

"And the Rear Stomp!" Fei Baiyun kicked his other foot backward and it sounded like his foot slashed apart the air. Wearing an ordinary pair of flats, his extreme burst of speed and strength made each of his movements look flawless. Garen couldn’t even imagine what would happen to someone if they were standing behind Fei Baiyun.

"There are two different types of Stomps, one is more about speed,, and the other about strength. You need to combine them with the Explosive Fist Arts skill and use them on your feet. In order to do it properly, you need to harden your blood vessels and your muscles before applying the force to your feet. When you use the Stomp skill, your Qi and blood will be drawn to your bottom half. This will not only hurt your enemies, but will also surround yourself with Qi. You need to carefully manage your breathing and your heart rate while using it," Fei Baiyun said and demonstrated the Stomp several more times. He asked Garen to try it after the demonstration and whispered Garen the secret techniques before letting Garen start.

It was fine if Garen’s stance was wrong, but if Fei Baiyun found that Garen was not matching his breathing with his heart rate, he would slap or kick Garen. The kicks and slaps actually helped Garen perform the actions properly.

"There is one universal rule in the White Cloud Gate, and that is Stability. Whatever you do, you do it with stability. You need to make sure your Qi and blood are stable, then apply them onto the skills you use. You will be able to modify your skills and make them explosive this way," Fei Baiyun said.

"If you turn on the water faucet and block the water with your finger, the water will burst out when you let your finger go for even a bit," he continued

Step by step, Garen started to focus on practicing the Stomp and tried to make sure his breath matched his heart rate, following everything Fei Baiyun said.

He was still thinking about the Stomp when he got back home. The White Cloud Secret Arts would bring him incredible power when the skills were combined with the Stomp.

The White Cloud Secret Arts technique was like an engine, and the higher the level he reached, the bigger the burst of power he would have. Every skill in the White Cloud Combat Arts aimed to increase one’s strength.

Garen kept practicing the skills he learnt over the next several days as Fei Baiyun taught him all four forms.

The Swing was all about swinging the feet and arms like a whip. The Rush used the Mammoth Strike to counterattack. The Strike could help Garen reach his peak for a short duration, allowing him to use his arms like knives to stab into the enemy’s eyes.

There were many possible combinations when using the four forms and different combinations were designed to be used against different opponents. Garen found some useful books in the tiny library room and there was a lot of information written by previous Masters of the White Cloud Gate. Garen found the standard combinations and applications of the four forms and also created some combinations by himself.

Garen learned the four forms in a hurry and he made sure he could at least reach the standard level. One month had passed since the final exams and he began to think about his attribute points. He finished the exams with no problems, but he was not expecting a high grade. He only wanted to focus on practicing martial arts.

He could increase the level of the White Cloud Secret Arts as long as he had the requisite medicinal herbs, though it would take some time. The Explosive Fist Arts, however, required tempering the body by beating it with wooden clubs in addition to some special potions. Advancing to the next level of Explosive Fist Arts was not a simple matter of using Attribute points.

***********

The noon of November the 2nd.

In the White Cloud Dojo.

Garen was topless; he had recently started training under the sunlight. There was sweat all over his tanned skin.

He stood in the middle of the training room as two apprentices hit him in the back, chest, and the arms with two arm-sized wooden bars.

Garen closed his eyes as he tried to move his Qi and blood to the places getting hit in order to recover faster.

[It’s been a month since I started practicing the White Cloud Secret Arts and the Explosive Fist Arts, but nothing is leveling up. It’d be much easier if I could just apply points to the skills,]’ Garen thought and shook his head. He could still see his attribute bar and his skill bar after closing his eyes.

There were some changes to his attributes, but on the skill bar he could only see that the Basic Combat Techniques was replaced with the White Cloud Combat Arts. The two skill sets were combined and they were set back to the first level.

01

On the attribute bar, Garen could see his Strength and Stamina had both increased by 0.1. His current attributes were Strength: 1.78, Agility: 1.10, Stamina: 1.04, Intelligence: 1.20, Potential: 377%.

[There’s barely any potential left on the Bronze Cross. One month passed, and I only got about 10%. I need to find some new antiques,] Garen thought, as he raised his hand to ask the two apprentices to stop.

The two stopped hitting Garen with the bars and were sweating heavily. They put down the bars and sat aside to rest.

"Garen, you are so strong. My arms are sore and you’re not even hurt!" one of the apprentices said admiringly.

"Keep training and one day you will be just like me. You will be able to learn the Explosive Fist Arts after you become a Formal Disciple," Garen said while he started to think about the distribution of his attribute points.

[I don’t need to apply points to the White Cloud Combat Arts since it will level up just from practicing. I thought I could just simply apply points to the White Cloud Secret Arts and Explosive Fist Arts, but it seems that it won’t work. These skills that need external help won’t be leveled up so easily,] Garen thought. He tried to apply points to the two skills many times, but it would not work. The only thing he could do was apply the points to his attributes.

He still remembered the night he met Grace, how he felt helpless against the pistol, and how fast the poison could travel through his body. Garen made up his mind as he stared at the Strength and Stamina attributes.

[Stamina increases my resistance, recovery speed, and will also increase my general defense. During the tests, I thought my organs were much stronger than before. The dojo’s arts did not make my organs stronger and I never specifically trained my organs. The effect probably came from the point I applied to the Stamina attribute,] Garen thought. He sat and took a rest, then finally decided to apply all his points to Strength and Stamina.

He stared at the Stamina attribute for three seconds as it changed from 1.04 to 1.34. Adding one attribute point increased the Stamina by 0.3. Garen could feel heat rush through his whole body; this sensation lasted for about ten seconds.

When he opened his eyes again, he felt he could see things clearer and that his hearing was enhanced as well. He looked at his right arm and his skin looked denser. Garen touched his skin; it felt silky smooth.

"You two can leave now, I’ll stay here for a while and will clean everything up after," Garen told the two apprentices. The two were used to situations like this and they knew Garen would stay late to train more, so they smiled and left.

Garen closed his eyes again, and he stared at the Strength attribute. He applied one point to it and it increased from 1.78 to 2.08. Garen could feel his body getting stronger and the 0.3 increase to Strength raised his total force by 60 pounds, which was a third of a normal adult male’s peak strength. This meant that 0.1 Strength equaled 20 pounds.

[One more point,] Garen thought, as he was about to apply it to Stamina. Suddenly, something from the skills bar caught his attention. A word changed as he was preparing to apply the point to Stamina.

"White Cloud Secret Arts: Advanced."

[What is this… Applying points to my Stamina can allow me to increase the level of White Cloud Secret Arts?!] Garen wondered excitedly.

[Can I apply points to it now?] Garen speculated. He stared at the White Cloud Secret Arts for three seconds and the status changed again. "Advanced" was no longer there and he saw "Completed" instead.

There should only be three levels of the White Cloud Secret Arts and the attribute point made it advance to the last level.

Garen was elated with the result, but he suddenly felt pain when he tried to stand up. His skin, muscle, and bones started to ache. He could feel heat cycling around his chest and it slowly spread to his four limbs. When the heat was almost gone, he started to feel a chill from the center of his chest travel through his body chasing after the vanishing heat.

Chapter 31: The Spiral (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen sat on the chair without moving as hot and cold Qi continuously circulated through his body.

It was not because he did not want to move, but actually that he could not move at all. As the hot and cold Qi continuously circulated, it would increase with every revolution. Within more than ten minutes, the growth of the hot and cold Qi had actually reached a level where it had spread to his entire body; he could not even distinguish the feeling between circulation and flow.

As Garen sat on his chair, the muscles in his body alternated between red and white. When they were red, he felt they burned like a cooked shrimp whose shell was peeled. When they were white, he was like a patient that had just recovered from a serious illness.

After an uncertain amount of time, a crashing noise sounded out.

Garen suddenly opened his eyes; they were extremely clear, as if a black pearl was embedded within a top-grade red jade.

Ssss...

When he breathed in deeply, there seemed to be a faint wind in the room, even his clothes hanging nearby on the hanger were fluttering. The clothes were four meters away and not directly in front of Garen; it was bizarre that they would be affected by his breathing.

As Garen opened his eyes, he slowly raised up his right arm—it was stiff like a robot’s—he arduously and slowly lifted it up from the armrest of the chair.

Kaka... A series of bone cracking noises came from his arm.

It was followed by the rest of his body: left arm, both legs, chest, and neck. As Garen slowly stood up, his entire body made a series of creaking noises at once.

"This happened because the sudden increase forced by my special ability was excessive, which caused my physique to improve by too much. If it were those experts that had been training for a long time, the result wouldn't be this exaggerated."

He didn’t know how strong he currently was. Even his master and senior sister had only reached the third level of the White Cloud Secret Arts. He was only able to reach the fourth level by forcefully increasing it with his attribute points.

It was a state that no one had reached before.

"Even though I’m so strong right now, my body is still not used to it. The increase in strength this time is too large, so it will take me a long amount of time to acclimate. Otherwise, I might accidentally kill someone again." After some thinking, Garen immediately understood his current situation.

"And I am only physically strong right now, my combat skills are still too weak. If only I could greatly increase the amount of attribute points I have, then I would be able to save the time I need to increase my proficiency and just improve my combat ability."

Shaking his head, Garen pulled on the clothes on the hanger. However, he forgot to adjust his strength.

The sound of cloth tearing echoed out.

His clothes were immediately torn into two.

He looked at his clothes in surprise: a corner of them was caught on a nail on the hanger. If it was another person, they would’ve stopped when they felt the resistance.

However, he could not. He was too strong, and thus the little resistance was completely negligible for him.

"I knew it."

Shaking his head, he walked out of the room, still shirtless.

As he walked out of the room, he immediately noticed a group of youths wearing yellow gi in the hall. They were chattering among themselves while a young female instructor was leading them.

Two of the headquarter staff were standing by the side, greeting them.

A beautiful woman with a cold aura stood up from a chair nearby. She wore a white top with a matching tight black skirt. She had dark red pupils with dark brown hair combed to the side and glowing, fair skin. Her eyes were slightly squinting as she walked next to Garen, and automatically received the clothes in his hands.

"They're the second batch of new students visiting the headquarters this month. What's wrong with your clothes?"

This woman of course was Grace. After accompanying Garen in his Critical Fist Technique practice for a month, her internal organs received extremely serious damage and it took a while before she fully recovered. However, her dispute with the White Cloud Dojo was found out by her company. Perhaps it was the company's arrangement or maybe her own volition, but either way, she became Garen’s personal assistant.

"I accidentally tore them just now. How is your body?" Garen casually asked. "Even though I intentionally held back during the practice, your internal organs were still injured. Even if you rested for a month, you couldn't have recovered so quickly."

"After taking the secret medicine provided by the dojo, I feel much better now. This result is already better than expected, so there's no need for you to worry."

The both of them chatted as they walked. They passed by the new students in the hall and headed toward the practice hall on the second floor.

"You're more or less a part of our dojo now, so are you still participating in your company's activities?"

"Not anymore, my current mission is to take care of your daily life. In fact, I've basically been abandoned by the company as a compensation for the previous incident." Grace bitterly smiled, "Master Fei is currently away. The person currently in charge is your senior sister, Rosetta. She's currently training in the private room, and I am not sure when she will leave."

Garen nodded and said, "As long as there is no major incident, the external instructors and the management staff can handle it. There's no need for us to worry about it. Your connections are better than mine, so do you know whether there's any progress with the case on Dale Quicksilver's side?"

"I am not sure, but I heard that detective Quicksilver returned to the Dolphin Antiques that you mentioned previously, these past few days. I don't know what happened, and the men that I sent didn't receive any information either. My previous connections were actually the company's, and since now I don't have any funds on hand, I can't make use of the other connections," Grace said with a frown.

"If you're looking for detailed information, you could try asking your seniors. They have their own connections and would know more than we do."

"We'll see." Garen accepted a white towel that a girl handed to him and wiped the sweat on his body.

He rested at the practice hall and ate lunch. As it was a weekend, Garen let Grace drive him to Pennington Road and stopped at Dolphin Antiques.

The furniture within the store had already been changed to black from the original red.

The old man was still sitting in front of a bookshelf, wearing reading glasses as he carefully adjusted the brass pocket watch in his hands. When Garen entered, he only glanced at his direction without even lifting his head.

"There's new stock that just came in, do you want to take a look?"

Garen looked around the store and saw that there was actually a customer: an elegantly dressed old lady with white hair. From her clothing he could tell that she was not from an ordinary family.

The old lady was carefully looking at a black necklace in her hands, and she seemed to be slightly preoccupied.

"Old man, where did you get that pocket watch? It looks like an authentic Buvich, doesn’t it?" He walked toward the old man and sat down on a chair in front of him.

"What do you mean by it looks authentic? It is authentic!" The old man glared at him. "That old lady is trying to pawn this. I am checking whether the internal structure is original."

"You're a pawnbroker as well?" Garen was speechless. "By the way, Dale Quicksilver came back, right? Did he find out anything?"

He had already obtained the emblem, but did not dare tell the old man. He had come to inquire about Dale Quicksilver's situation.

After all, getting the emblem back had something to do with the company behind Grace. Dale Quicksilver might one day trace it back to him.

Also, during the exchange of information with the old man, he felt that Dale Quicksilver's recent actions were strange.

"He's still chasing after the Golden Hoop. Anyway, I've already given up. I didn't lose much anyway. The Golden Hoop isn't just an ordinary thief, but a powerful killer as well!" Old Man Gregor put down the pocket watch and wiped its surface with a microfiber cloth.

Garen's eyes slightly flashed. "You mentioned the other time that the detective is also interested in troublesome antiques, just like me. What did you mean?"

"I am not sure. Anyway, he chose a few pieces of those kind of antiques from the ones I had just gotten. I made twice the profit from just reselling it, so that transaction was definitely worth it!" The old man had a triumphant look on his face.

"He preselected from this batch again?" Garen knitted his eyebrows. It was not the first time that it happened.

"What? You want it as well?" The old man glanced at him. "I'll sell it to you as long as you can pay for it. Let me tell you this, it's not only happening here. Dale Quicksilver has bought all the antiques of this kind that are being sold in the entirety of Huaishan City."

"So he has collected a lot of them?" Garen's eyes lit up. "Honestly, I am very interested in these kind of strange and dangerous antiques. They excite me."

With a loud thump, the old man's hand viciously landed on Garen's head.

"Exciting, your head! You don't even have an income and you want to collect antiques like him, you wastrel!"

Garen did not get angry and only laughed. "Oh and where's that book? You already got it back from your friend, right? Can you let me see it again?"

"I already said, there's no point if you have no talent. Nothing will change no matter how many times you look at it." The old man impatiently waved him off. "Alright, hurry and do whatever you need to do."

"It's not like it would disappear if you just let me see it once more. Stupid old man, you're still so stingy." Garen shook his head.

The both of them happily chatted for a while, before Garen got up and left.

After a while, Old Man Gregor stood up and closed the entrance of the shop.

The old lady put down the necklace in her hand and looked at Old Man Gregor with a complicated look.

"It's been a while, and you've completely turned into an ordinary person."

The old man smiled, but strangely did not refute.

"This is fate. This was the choice that I made. I am merely reaping what I sowed."

"How long do you plan to stay here?"

"How long? Until they find me, I guess." The old man sighed and sullenly replied, "I've been avoiding and escaping from them for so many years..."

"Are you really fine with spending your days like this?" The old lady calmly said. "We've already entered this circle, it's not possible for us to leave anymore. They've already come looking for you."

"Are you threatening me?" The old man's expression darkened.

"I am only here to give you a reminder. They won't let go of anyone who has come in contact with you, including that boy. "

"He's only an ordinary person, don't get him involved with this!" The old man's expression became solemn. There was no longer the usual joviality in his eyes, only a slight gloomy sharpness remained.

"You're saying that to the wrong person." The old lady walked toward him and sat on the chair that Garen sat on. "He saw that book as well, right? There's no need to deny it, I heard your conversation. That boy really resembles you when you were younger. He really does..."

She silently looked at the old man, eyes glimmering like the sea.

Chapter 32: The Spiral 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Perhaps, but he's still different from me in the end. He can't do anything without talent..." the old man said sullenly as he lowered his head.

"Stop being foolish, Gregor. Give the book to me, only I can keep it safe now." The old lady slowly reached out her hand toward the old man.

Old Man Gregor held his head down and did not say anything for a while.

"Influence, wealth, reputation. In the end there’s nothing more dependable than your own ability. Gregor, you've fallen." There was a trace of pity in the old lady's eyes. "Time flies; in the blink of an eye, we're already at this age. And you, who had made the wrong choice, no longer have the right to safeguard it."

******************

Garen was ambling down Pennington Street -- while looking back in the direction of the antique store from time to time -- when he saw the old man covertly closing the store's entrance.

"Good lord! That old woman still hasn't come out, right?" He was stunned. "They're still so bold at their age? They couldn’t even wait until nightfall... As expected of the vulgar old man..."

Shaking his head, his mind suddenly conjured a juicy story between the old couple, and goosebumps immediately appeared all over his body.

"They were making eyes at each other back at the store too, but I didn't think that they were so impatient that they would immediately start after I left. It seems that the elderly have such needs as well..."

He ambled along the street with his hands in his pockets. As he watched the ongoing stream of carriages and automobiles, he continued along a small distance until he reached a black sedan and entered the vehicle.

Grace was sitting in the driver's seat with one hand on the steering wheel and the other holding a paper-wrapped sandwich. She was eating voraciously; there was no sign of the "cold lady" image she should have.

While eating, she asked, "Where are we going?"

"Home. We need to find a way to earn money as well. Grace, do you have any connections?"

Grace thought for a while and then replied, "I have some, but it would depend on whether you're willing."

"Tell me. I haven't used that check you gave me yet. I can invest using that."

"The money isn't mine: I took it out of the company's accounts. It's rather appropriate to use as your capital." Grace nodded. "What's your motive? Are you aiming to start a career or just to earn money?"

"It's best to just earn money. Of course, the source should be clean."

"That's simple then. The most suitable method would be tutoring using the dojo's name. Of course, it depends on your master's reputation. You could ask your seniors to introduce tutoring work to you as well. With your identity, you should be able to easily earn a large sum of money," Grace explained.

"Oh, that might work. However, I haven't even mastered it myself, let alone being able to teach others. Are there any other methods?"

"There’s also Miss Felicity; she started her own auction company. Aren’t you trying to earn money to collect antiques? You can just cooperate with her. Lastly, you could work with my company. My company can pay you a considerable sum every month. It's just that you might be called up to solve any... problem.. that arises."

"There's no need to hurry, let me think about it." Garen knitted his eyebrows. The three methods did not meet his requirements, especially when he found out that Dale Quicksilver was actually collecting similar antiques. He was slightly tempted.

"It would be great if I could make contact with Dale Quicksilver and look at his collection. The problem is, what kind of excuse could I use to contact him?"

He looked toward Grace.

"Do you have a method to contact Dale Quicksilver? I want to take a look at his collection of antiques, but I need a reason to do so."

"That's simple. If you tell him that you have some antiques and would like to show and exchange some of your collections with him, he probably wouldn't refuse if you use our company's name. Do you need me to make preparations immediately? It's just that you will need to put on makeup first. You’re still too young, after all," Grace swiftly replied. "As for the antique needed for the exchange, my company will arrange it."

"Arrange it, see if he agrees."

************

In the next few days, Garen traveled back and forth between the school and the antique shop, behaving completely like an ordinary student.

However, as the effect of the emblem had become almost negligible, he could only obediently learn martial arts every day from his seniors. White Cloud Combat Arts were moves developed from the Mammoth Secret Technique; its four forms were interchangeable and abnormally powerful. Garen spent every day practicing the moves with his seniors while suppressing his own strength.

For the past few days, he did not attend classes even when he was at school. He was only waiting for the end of term results to be announced.

"How did you fare?" Fayne and Kalidor gathered together to check each other's result.

"Alright, I’m twentieth in the class, it's not that bad." Kalidor grinned.

"How can you even be happy with twentieth place, there are barely even twenty people in our class..." Garen jokingly scolded as he walked over with papers in his hand. "I messed up my foreign language paper. There's no hope for me: I just answered randomly."

Kalidor looked at Garen's foreign language paper: 20 marks were clearly drawn on it.

"Impressive!" Kalidor gave Garen a thumbs up. "Oh and let's go to the White Eagle Saloon later. They just imported a batch of purple grape wine! I made the owner keep a bottle for me."

"I am not going, you guys can go. I have something else i need to do," Garen declined.

"Again? You've been refusing to hang out with us for quite a while now. Just what exactly are you so busy with all day?" Kalidor was slightly unhappy.

"I really have something to do." Garen helplessly shrugged his shoulders.

Ever since Kalidor and Ai Fei got together, the gap between Kalidor and Garen grew larger and the group was not as harmonious as before. Even though the two of them intended to mend the gap, the incident with Ai Fei was like a thorn between them that could not be removed.

Both Fayne and Jake noticed it and tried persuading Kalidor to forget about it. Little did they expect that after Kalidor became enamored by Ai Fei, even the two of them were both left by the wayside.

"Alright, if you really have something going on, then forget it. It's just as well, now I can go out with my girlfriend: I only have the first few days of this vacation to play around. My father will probably force me to help him out the rest of the time," Fayne continued.

Kalidor's expression only slightly improved after his two friends’ persuasion, but he still angrily left.

Garen could not do anything about it as well.

"Garen, are you going to the dojo?"

"No, I’ve stopped going to the dojo for now. I'll be staying at home this vacation. It's another matter." Garen no longer needed to go to the dojo on a daily basis. He had learned everything he could; he only needed to practice on his own.

After the matter with Grace was settled, his life seemed to have completely returned to normal.

After chatting with his friends for a while, Garen checked the time. When he realized that it was almost time to leave, he slowly walked out of the school.

There was a line of carriages and automobiles queueing outside the school to pick up students. From time to time, a vehicle would hurriedly arrive and leave shortly after. Garen slowly walked toward a black sedan and entered it.

"The arrangements are ready," Grace softly said from the driver's seat. "Dale Quicksilver has agreed to our request. The meeting will occur at his temporary residence in the suburbs."

"Where is it?"

"Canoe Town."

"Canoe Town? Is there a place nearby called Silversilk Castle?" Garen was slightly surprised.

"Silversilk Castle?" Grace slightly hesitated. "It seems like it... I've never been there before, but Dale Quicksilver seems to be quite interested in that place. He's currently resting over there."

"Is his case solved?"

"It's not completely resolved. He only found half of the antiques that the Golden Hoop stole. The rest were sold through various channels. Our company was only one of the channels used. I am sure you know about that."

"That's true." Garen knew the company behind Grace, the Manuyllton Corporation, was the biggest antique reseller in Huaishan. "How far is the place from here? How long would it take?"

"We'll first go to another place to pick up somebody to help you put on your makeup. Then we'll go to Canoe Town to meet Dale Quicksilver. The meeting time is around 3 p.m."

"It's only 11 a.m. right now, there's still time." Garen nodded.

He had always wanted to go to Silversilk Castle to check out the source of the Bronze Cross Emblem and see what was special about it. As the strangest and longest-lasting Potential Antique, Garen had wanted to find out the secret behind it. He did not think that Dale Quicksilver would actually be investigating the matter as well.

"From the looks of it, it's not a coincidence. He's collecting Potential Antiques and is even deliberately staying around Silversilk Castle. It would be strange if it's only a coincidence."

Garen turned his head to the window and looked outside. With a roar of the engine, the vehicle started to gradually move forward. He could see groups of students on both sides of the road entering and leaving stores. The girls were dressed in short skirts and black stockings; most of them were youthful and charming. The boys were dressed in shirts with long pants and leather shoes; they were lively and slightly charismatic even if their looks were ordinary.

This was a special aura that only Shengying Academy had; it was not possible for ordinary schools to possess it. Even the clothes that they wore were not affordable for ordinary students.

There was more than one academy within Huaishan City. There were a few high schools and Shengying was the best among them. It was not just due to having a spectacular score while enrolling annually l -- the environment, the quality of the students, and other various aspects all mattered as well.

As Garen watched the students from the window, he suddenly remembered his young sister, Ying Er, who had been obediently staying at home for the past few days,

In regard to the matter of acknowledging his master -- after he told his parents about it -- they personally visited his master's residence to make up for their previous absence.

Garen's parents were simple people. They did not understand the actual status and power of Fei Baiyun. They were only surprised by the seriousness of the whole situation. Fei Baiyun's residence was not extravagant either. Instead, the furnishing was quite simple.

His sister, Ying Er, also knew that he acknowledged Fei Baiyun as his master but she did not know about the details. After she found out about the entire process, she understood that it was a formal ceremony and it changed her opinion about him. However, for some reason, her recent relationship with Garen became even colder.

Clearing his mind, Garen laid back on his seat and glanced downward toward his Skills in the attribute pane.

"Right now, I am only lacking in actual combat skills. It would be great if I still have any Attribute points. At least then I could just rapidly raise my White Cloud Combat Arts, which would help save a lot of time and energy. I only wish that meeting Dale Quicksilver this time would give me some sort of reward..."

Chapter 33: Silversilk Castle (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Huaishan City, southern suburbs

Green mountains and rugged rolling hills were reminiscent of a thick green carpet covering the land.

On one of the hills scattered several yellow and white dots. Upon a closer look, these were actually small residential houses. These houses were in the shape of cubes, built with cream-colored marble stone.

The building walls and door frames were covered in green ivy, of which some of had blossomed small flowers.

Below one of the houses stood two arched gates, inside was a semi-outdoor resting area.

There were two tables inside, and sitting by the left table were four people, resting and drinking tea.

Two middle-aged men and two young women sat across from each other.

The older man had a well-trimmed beard, he was wearing a nice and delicate black suit. He looked around 40 years of age and had a wooden cane in one hand. He lifted the teacup from the table and took a sip.

"Mr. Kelly has come all the way here to discuss the collection of antiques of misfortune, this kind of enthusiasm is rare nowadays."

His eyes landed on the middle-aged man sitting across from him.

The man’s skin was a bit pale. He had blond, curly hair, and a blond goatee, wearing a tidy white suit. He seemed relaxed and elegant. He was much younger, about thirty instead.

His eyes were the most dazzling, they were like the finest rubies, transparent and crystal clear.

"I am also amazed by Mr. Quicksilver’s enthusiasm, to not only collecting these antiques and jewelry by yourself, but also looking for their places of origin and background stories.

The man sighed.

"Collectors like us, aren’t we all intrigued by these things? The dream life of coming home to a house full of antiques with mysterious backgrounds. It’s like… like…"

"Like our own house and lives had become mysterious, filled with powers unknown to men," Dale Quicksilver added with a smile.

"Exactly! That’s the feeling!" The blond man nodded. "Life is always so boring, that’s why we long for us, for our lives to be filled with puzzles and mysteries. That is the most interesting part of finding these antiques of tragedy."

"Indeed." Dale Quicksilver approvingly nodded, his eyes glanced over the man’s wrist, "I unexpectedly came across an antique of tragedy while investigating a case, and I got hooked on collecting them ever since. Time flies by like an arrow, over the past decade, I’ve collected hundreds of them in my house."

"Hundreds!?" The blond man’s eyes gleamed with light, "That’s incredible! Only a man such as Detective Quicksilver is worthy of these treasures, I’m sure they are completely different from the stuff you had earlier. Anyway, the reason you have come here, is it related to antiques?"

"Not exactly." Dale Quicksilver shook his head, he took over the pipe from Ms. Si Lan and smoked from it, he slowly blew a smoke ring. "We are here for a well-known criminal in detective business, it’s a serial killer case. The case was settled, that’s why we have time to come and investigate."

"Is that so? The well-known criminal, would that be the Golden Hoop?" The blond man mused as he pinched his beard. After receiving a positive answer, he continued, "Golden Hoop had committed dozens of crimes all over the federation. I heard that other than you, only one famous detective had met him face to face before. Would you be kind enough to inform me of this Golden Hoop’s story?"

"I do apologize, it’s not that I don’t want to tell you, I have a non-disclosure agreement with the police department," Dale Quicksilver shrugged, "Well, we might get going soon, I have to go to the Silversilk Castle this afternoon, would Mr. Kelly be interested in joining us?"

"The Silversilk Castle? I’ve heard of that shabby place over the years of living in Huaishan City, it’s the inheritance of a military officer, he didn’t have enough money to maintain the castle, and he had sold most of the stuff in there," Kelly replied. "I’ve heard that the castle was for sale, but it was too worn out and desolated, visitors had left as soon as they saw it. Are you planning on buying this castle?"

"Just visiting the place, I don’t plan on buying it." Dale Quicksilver laughed. He turned around and said a few words to Si Lan, who nodded in reply and walked out towards a two-floored house nearby, disappearing behind the green and thick bushes.

"The vegetation here is rich, and there are no signs of withering this late in the fall, if it wasn’t too far from my home, I’d love to move here," Dale Quicksilver blew another smoke ring and lamented.

"I agree, that’s why I’ve moved here and never wanted to leave," Kelly replied. He spoke a few words with the blond girl with ponytail next to him, the girl stood up and walked towards the black car parked outside.

"From here to Silversilk castle is a two-hour drive, it’s almost 5:00 pm now. If we go at this time, we would have to come back during the late night. Or perhaps Mr. Dale was prepared to stay there for the night?" Kelly stood up and questioned.

"I’ve spent a few nights there the past few days, no big deal. I talked with the castle’s owner Mr. Nusves and paid him some money, I have rented the castle for two months. Since everything in there was already sold or moved out, he didn’t worry about it too much." Dale Quicksilver also stood up, "On another note, you don’t have to bring your car, there’s nowhere to fill gas, we’d be better off riding in a carriage."

"That’s true, I guess I have to bother you for a few days."

"No problem, we are all fellow collectors, and it’s hard to find a friend with the same interest. I won’t lie to you, my other friends are not too fond about this hobby of mine. Okay, enough talking, I’ll get the carriage so we can get going soon, I’ll see you in a bit."

"All right, I’ll be right out."

Kelly stood next to the table, he took a cup of tea and drank it bottom up. He watched as Dale Quicksilver walked over the grass towards a black carriage coming from afar. Ms. Si Lan was wearing a white trench coat, she jumped off the carriage to wait for him.

The winding road stretched on, like a gray snake coiling towards the horizon. Far away on the road, two bullock carts filled with golden wheat moved slowly.

A warm wind breezed over, sending the hems of Kelly’s white suit flying, a relaxed and leisured atmosphere permeated the air.

Kelly touched his chin.

"This beard feels so real."

"Of course it does." The blond girl who left earlier had come back to him. "The road to Silversilk Castle is going to take at least two hours in the carriage, we’ll have to walk quite a distance in the mountain as well. I’m afraid we’ll have to stay there for the night."

"Mr. Dale said we could stay at the castle for the night," Kelly smiled and said. "Let’s go, don’t let our detective wait too long."

The girl watched Kelly’s back as he left, her eyes glimmered with suspicion. Even though she knew he was undercover, it was still strange that from all aspects, Kelly was too mature and too real compared to Garen. He didn’t seem like a teenage boy. As if Garen was Kelly’s disguise, and the Garen-turned-Kelly was his true self.

She shook her head and stopped the thought, quickly followed up. The two walked towards the waiting carriage on the road.

Before getting into the carriage, Garen snapped a violet flower from the side of the road, he smelled it, and upon closer look, he discovered there were many tiny black bugs near the center of the flower bud. They looked like ants, and the flower was odorless.

The group of four boarded the carriage, Dale and Si Lan sat in the front row, Garen and Grace sat in the back.

The riding whip made a crisp snap sound, as two tall and strong horses pulled the carriage forward, the bells on their necks started ringing.

Noticing the flower on Garen’s hands, Dale Quicksilver commented.

"The flowers here are all odorless, but they seem to attract a lot of bugs, I wonder how that happens."

Garen stretched out his index finger and let a bug climb onto it from the flower petal, it tickled his finger. The bug looked like a miniature ladybug, its semicircle-shaped wings flapped occasionally to maintain balance.

"The origins of antiques of tragedy tend to involve different kinds of unusual phenomenon, this is quite common, isn’t it?" Garen smiled, "If it were the same as any other place, I wouldn’t have bothered to come here. It is a pity that you didn’t bring any of your collections with you, I could have had the luck to take a look at them."

Dale Quicksilver started laughing.

"I initially thought you were just a boasting fraud, I never thought you could tell apart the knockoff replicas of antiques of tragedy from the real ones so easily. I didn’t expect to find such a bosom friend at a place like this. I thought I was the only one interested in these things."

"Same as I." Garen laughed along as he stripped a flower pedal and flicked it out of the carriage. "What is it about the Silversilk Castle that drew your interest? I’ve lived here for so long without knowing anything remarkable about it."

Dale Quicksilver handed the horsewhip to Si Lan. He took out a stack of papers from his leather bag and handed them over. "These are some documents I’ve collected, take a look."

Garen took them over, he saw the title of the first page: Castle Owner Found Dead. Underneath the title was a large paragraph of writing, describing how the body was found.

He flipped to the next page, it was a similar title.

The third page was the same, except this one had a picture, it was a picture of the Silversilk Castle.

Three owners of the castle died for no reason, killer unknown. They all died peacefully in their sleep without any trace of a struggle, like old-aged seniors who had lost their last breath. Strangely enough, these three owners were all strong, middle-aged military officers.

Chapter 34: Silversilk Castle (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"The most recent death was the owner of the Silversilk Castle from about 30 years ago. I am not sure which Antique of Tragedy it is, but I am trying to see just what’s going on there, and I might even find it if I’m lucky," Dale Quicksilver added, while Garen nodded his head.

Garen knew what an Antique of Tragedy was, and he thought his Bronze Cross was one of them. Although it could barely provide him with any potential, only about 1 point per week, it was better than nothing.

Garen had no idea why an Antique of Tragedy could provide him with potential, and he wanted to know where the name came from. Those were the main reasons why he decided to travel to the Silversilk Castle with Dale Quicksilver.

The carriage left the city before noon and arrived at a green and yellow slope in the afternoon. There was a small forest in front of them and the sun was beginning to set. The four got off the carriage and surveyed the forest.

By the end of the forest, they could see an old-looking graycastle built upon a hill. The surface of the castle had burn marks all over it, and it was completely devoid of plant life.

Outside the castle, the lawn was surrounded by fences and several trees, but they all looked gray and burned.The castle had three bartizans, and Garen could see many windows around it. However, everything looked black from a distance.

"This is Silversilk Castle. I heard it caught fire 30 years ago and the next owner had no money to fix it, so now it looks like this. It was pretty sad, since the castle was famous for its garden. The word silversilk came from its beautiful exterior. Before the accident, the facade looked like it was covered with silver silk." Dale Quicksilver said, pointing at the castle.

"I don’t think that’s possible Mr. Dale. If the accident happened thirty years ago, why does it still have this gray and black appearance. There should at least be some ivies or moss growing on it," Grace speculated.

"No one knows the reason. Some said the ash stopped the plants from growing, and some said plants just wouldn’t grow there. There were many strange rumors about the castle, but they were all hard to believe," Si Lan said.

"Did you ever ask the locals about it?" Grace scrunched her eyebrows and asked.

"No one lives around here. Farmers cannot grow anything on an area like this, and the closest towns are about 30 miles away," Si Lan answered.

"We will be staying in the castle tonight, right? Do we have enough supplies?" Garen touched his fake beard and asked.

"We have more than enough. Me and Si Lan have stayed here for days, and the only problem was that we had to travel a long way to get back to the city. The environment here was good, and it was nice to stay in the castle. Let’s go. We still have a long way to walk, maybe half an hour," Dale Quicksilver said as he nodded his head.

"What about the carriages?" Garen asked.

"Just leave them here and someone will drive them back. I have everything planned. We took the carriages to get here, but we will have to walk back after we visit. It’s about a four hour walk from here to Canoe Town, the nearest settlement," Dale Quicksilver explained.

"We will have to stay here for several days I think," he continued.

"That’s fine. I will enjoy my vacation I guess. Grace, can you go back to the city and tell my family not to worry about me? Just tell them I am staying at my friend’s home and I will be back after several days," Garen said with a light tone.

"How about letting me drive the carriage back and I’ll leave it in town?" Grace suggested. She knew Garen wanted her to hide the truth from his family. He was still a high school student and did not want his family to be worried about him.

"Sure," Dale Quicksilver nodded.

The three watched Grace and the carriage disappear at the end of the road.

"Let’s go. It’s better if we can get there before the evening," Dale Quicksilver said, shaking the long bag in his hand.

"I brought my rifle and we can hunt some wild animals for a barbeque," he added.

"Sounds great! You’re really well prepared." Garen smiled.

"I brought some spices, tea, and coffee beans. There is a river nearby and we can get some water from there." Si Lan smiled and showed Garen the red pouch in her hand.

"Let’s see if you can make some good coffee," Garen said.

"I have some secret techniques!" Si Lan had a mysterious smile on her face.

"I assume Mr. Kelly rarely goes camping. Unlike us detectives, sometimes we even have to camp in forests when chasing criminals, so we have to be prepared," she explained.

"You are right." Garen shrugged his shoulders.

"I only brought some emergency tools, some clothes, and some daily supplies. I am not as prepared as you," he replied.

"Well, let’s get moving before it gets dark. We need to clean up a room for you. From here on out we’ll have to rely on the oil lamps I brought," Dale Quicksilver said lightly as he looked at the setting sun.

"Sure, let’s go." The three started to walk towards the Silversilk Castle.

*****************

Inside the Castle’s iron gate, Garen could see white ashes on the charred ground. It looked like the road was covered with a layer of soot.

There were two small triangular fire towers on either side of the road, and there were two braziers on top of them. A metal railing separated the castle from the trees on the outside, but Garen had no idea out of what type of metal it was made from.

Outside the railings, Garen could see fresh, dark green bushes. Beyond that, everything looked dead. The dying trees and withered lawn made Garen feel a bit depressed.

The three people entered the gate holding their bags in hand. They followed the dusty road to the door of the castle. The wooden door had a metal frame around its perimeter, and there was a white keyhole in the middle. Dale Quicksilver took out the key and unlocked the door.

The door opened and Garen followed Si Lan into the empty main hall. He checked around but there were no decorations, no furniture, not even a carpet. It was also dark since the wall lamps were also gone .

The sunlight entered the hall through the dormer on the side, opposite to the door, and it made the hall just slightly more peaceful.

"Which room you want? You can pick one and then we need to start preparing dinner." Dale Quicksilver closed the door and put the key back to his belt.

"Cooking for myself in a castle in the middle of nowhere, this feels so novel to me," Garen said and smiled.

Si Lan brought him to a room on the right side of the castle and made the bed for him. Garen put a blanket on the bed and was good to go.

After dinner, Garen could barely see anything in the dark and they did not have enough oil to keep the lamps going, so they decided to go to bed early and explore the castle tomorrow.

Garen went back to his room and sat on the bed.

The room was extremely quiet. There was a door sized window on one side, the floor was made from light red hexagonal tiles. There was only a large bed in the room, surrounded by metal racks upon which mosquito traps used to be placed.

Garen could barely move on the bed as he did not want the rust to flake off the metal bedframe. There was an oil lamp on a chair beside the bed, the only thing that was keeping the room in light. He walked towards the window in his underwear and looked down. He could see nothing but darkness.

He couldn’t see anything on the lawn; the whole castle was dead still. Dale Quicksilver and Si Lan were sleeping in two different rooms, so Garen was the only one awake in the castle.

Garen opened the window, and a chilling wind gusted into the room. Garen could hear owls hooting from the forest, barely illuminated by the shining moon in the sky.

"I should go to bed. I will see what Dale Quicksilver can find here tomorrow. I am not sure if he knows I am undercover. I don’t know if he is a genius or not, but I know he’s observant," Garen thought. He practiced some Fist Arts in the room, before closing the door, and laying down on the bed.

After a while, Garen turned over on the bed. Strangely, he heard the sound of the door being opened; it sounded like someone had opened it from the outside. Surprised, he sat up and looked at the door. The door was ajar, but otherwise not moving. He got up and closed the door carefully.

"It was the wind,"’ he thought.

Garen lay down on the bed and began fell asleep, but the sound of the door opening stopped him again.

Garen woke up one more time and he grabbed the oil lamp by the side. He stared at the door carefully, but nothing was there.

"Are you playing with me?" Garen yelled.

"Dale?" he yelled again.

His voice echoed in the room, down the grand hall across the castle, and finally back to him. But no one answered. It was still quiet outside.

Garen put on his slippers and walked towards the door with the lamp in his hand. He closed the door again and locked it. He fastened the door with the latches so that no one would be able to open it again. Garen took a deep breath and returned to the bed. However instead of sleeping, he just sat there and tried to figure out what was going on.

Suddenly, he heard the sound of someone putting a key into the keyhole of his door.

Garen stood up immediately and forcefully swung the door open. The noise stopped. No one was outside. He was really confused.

"I... thought I locked it?" Garen looked at the latches, and was surprised again.

"I locked the door and fastened all the latches!" he yelled. He was sure he had locked the door, but the door had just opened without any resistance.

"What the hell?!" Garen yelled. He slammed the door closed and stepped back. His scalp tingled and he stumbled on the corner of the bed.

"If I find whoever it is that’s pulling this prank, you’re dead!" Garen yelled with anger.

Chapter 35: Silversilk Castle (3)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Kelly! Wake up, Kelly! Come on!"

Upon hearing the sudden shout, Garen opened his eyes. The bright light in front of him forced his eyes into a tight squint. Dale Quicksilver was anxiously tapping his face.

"What’s going on? Why’re you here, Dale?" Garen sat up, realizing that the event that had just occurred was only a dream.

"Why are you asleep down here in the basement?" Dale looked at Garen curiously. "Were you here looking for something by yourself and ended up falling asleep? Didn’t I tell you to wait for me to move together?"

At this moment, Garen found himself lying against the wall in the basement. Dark and narrow walls made from cold stone bricks surrounded him. The room was completely empty.

The basement was partially underground. Sunlight spilled in from a window near the ceiling, making this place resemble a dungeon more than a basement.

"What’s going on? I clearly remember going to sleep in the bedroom…" He lowered his head as a wave of excruciating pain rose.

Suddenly, his heart skipped a beat -- the sound of silence greeted him.

In the blink of an eye, Dale Quicksilver had vanished right in front of him.

The room was empty again.

"Dale?"

"Dale!"

Garen crawled up from the floor and yelled again. There was no answer.

A sharp pain arose from within his head once more, and then he remembered: Dale had woken him up from the basement. That had happened three days ago.

"Three days ago?" He covered his head, his vision blurry. "What happened? If that was three days ago, what was I doing in these past three days? How come I don’t remember anything? He was right here in front of me!"

He felt the pain assault his temples again. His mind was in chaos.

"No, I can’t stay in this castle any longer!"

He pushed open the door and rushed out of the basement, running toward the castle’s gate through a straight and empty path.

His footsteps echoed inside the castle.

‘Peng!’

The castle door was slammed open. He then stumbled through the door and fell down the stairs, tumbling onto the grass.

‘Gasp’

He lied on the grass, breathless, gasping for air. Suddenly, he felt a sense of drowsiness encroaching upon him. Unable to resist the drowsiness, he passed out.

Not knowing how long it has been, he slowly opened his eyes. he was still lying on his bed inside the castle.

"Kelly, are you up yet?" Dale Quicksilver’s voice came from outside.

"I’m back here again? Was that all a dream?" Garen sat up from the bed. "This place… this place is too strange!" Goosebumps formed all over his body. Even though sunlight was shining on him through the bedroom window, he didn’t feel any warmth. Thinking back, the images in this room seemed more real than those in his dreams.

"Was it all a dream?" He took a deep breath.

After getting up, he quickly dressed up and opened the door. Dale Quicksilver was standing there with a surprised look.

"What’s wrong? You look like you stayed up all night."

"It’s nothing, just a nightmare." Garen forced out a smile.

"Nightmare?" Dale Quicksilver laughed. "A nightmare could scare you like this? What happened in it? Come, tell us and grab some breakfast."

"Fine." Garen rubbed his eyebrows. He knew it was ridiculous. "Although that nightmare was unbelievably real."

"You go down first, in the main hall downstairs. I’ll lock the doors." Dale Quicksilver tapped Garen’s shoulder. "Seems like I shouldn’t have shown you that document."

"It’s okay, I’m not so easily frightened." Garen laughed and left for breakfast. He didn’t notice Dale Quicksilver’s gloomy expression behind him.

********************

Main hall

Garen followed the stairs down to find Si Lan sitting in the corner of the hall. She was drinking a cup of tea, wearing a dark brown hunting uniform. Her blonde ponytail hung from her back, contrasting against her clear skin.

"Mr. Kelly is up too? You don’t look too well. Did you not have a good rest?"

"I had a nightmare… it was … too real." Garen rubbed between his eyes and sat down at the table.

"Have some tea. I got it from the Garfield Province." Si Lan made an inviting gesture.

"Thanks."

Garen lifted a cup of hot black tea and put it up to his nose, smelling the fresh minty scent mixed with a hint of milk cream.

He sipped from the cup and found that the tea tasted like mint water.

"What kind of tea is this? Tastes a little weird."

"I’ve added some other spices so it will help you wake up. One of my uncles is a doctor at Sirius University and he taught me how to make this," Si Lan said.

Garen nodded. "Not bad, I’m already feeling better."

Dale Quicksilver came to the table and sat down as well. He took a cup of tea and chugged the tea down his throat.

"So here’s the plan: We’ll go hunting first, get the food for lunch and dinner, then get some water and clean our equipment. Then we’ll spend the rest of the afternoon investigating the castle and its surroundings."

"You’re the expert, you make the plans." Garen shrugged.

"Oh and Mr. Kelly--"

"Just call me Kelly."

"All right, Kelly. You said you had a vivid nightmare. Just what kind of nightmare could it be to have exhausted and dispirited you so?"

Garen drank some hot tea, allowing the hot water, combined with the cool mint flavor, to bathe his throat. The tea flowed into his stomach, filling his body with warmth, and sobered his mind.

"I dreamed" -- he paused for a second -- "of someone opening my door at night, over and over again every time when I’m about to fall asleep." His eyebrows furrowed. "This is very strange. I’ve never been here before, so I didn’t expect to have this kind of dream on my first night."

"I remember the documents I showed you contained information about the deaths of the three owners of this castle. It was mentioned that the previous three owners all had nightmares before their deaths. Maybe you were worried after reading that document, causing you to have a nightmare," Dale Quicksilver analyzed.

"Do we have information on what their nightmares were about?"

"We don’t know anything about that. I had a dream last night as well. It wasn’t a nightmare though." Dale Quicksilver looked up through the window, his expression told Garen he was reminiscing about something.

"You are thinking about it again?" Si Lan seemed worried. "It’s been that long, yet you still can’t let it go?"

"If only it was that easy," Dale Quicksilver laughed, somewhat bitterly.

Garen was completely silent, carefully watching their expressions.

After the morning tea, they had some breakfast. The three of them went to prepare their weapons and gear.

Dale Quicksilver held a rifle and suited up in a military hunting uniform with a top hat. Garen had a half-meter long saber and wore the same clothes he had on the day before, which were completely unsuitable for the occasion. In the end, he also grabbed a sack, ready to help with logistics.

They cleaned up the dishes and headed out of the castle.

After locking the door, Dale Quicksilver led them toward the right side of the castle. "There’s a hole in the fence. We can get to the forest through there." He loaded the rifle as he spoke.

"There aren’t many animals around here. It’s a good thing we don’t have many mouths to feed. Even small prey would be enough for a few meals."

Garen nodded in reply. He didn’t speak, but instead raised the sack in his hand, indicating that he was going to be taking care of the prey. The rest was on Quicksilver.

Dale Quicksilver laughed and tapped his rifle without saying a word.

The three arrived at the right wing of the castle. Located on the black steel fence was a giant hole as wide as two people. The poles on the fence had been destroyed by some force, bent inwards haphazardly.

Dale Quicksilver carefully sneaked past the gap and waved from the other side.

Si Lan and Garen followed him through the hole, and Garen almost caught his clothes on the fence.

Outside the fence was a dark and green forest. Trees around four to five meters tall filled the area, while thick and wild bushes scattered around the ground. A cold aura could be felt emitting from deep inside even before they entered.

The morning sunlight could not pierce through the dense leaves. Even the warmth could not penetrate through. The sounds of birds chirping continuously came from within the forest, with the occasional noises coming from the bushes as something moved inside.

"That’s the noise of mountain mice, sounds like big ones." Dale Quicksilver lowered his voice and crouched down, trying not to make any noise. "I didn’t expect to have something good this quick."

Si Lan smiled while moving behind Dale.

Even if Garen had never hunted before, he knew not to make a sound at this moment. He tipped his toes and followed behind.

"Bang!"

Garen looked forward and saw Dale Quicksilver lower his rifle, smoke snaking from the barrels with the smell of gunpowder permeating through the air.

"Your aim is pretty good, Dale! How did you hit it so accurately through all that grass? The mouse was moving so fast!" Garen gave him a thumbs up and said, "Looks like we’ll have enough food for today."

"That’s not enough at all. We’ll have to gut it and skin it. After that, there would hardly be any meat left. We’ll need some more," Dale Quicksilver said, shaking his head.

Garen had never hunted wild animals before. Although he didn’t know what was going on, he was fascinated by everything. His bad mood from last night’s nightmare improved.

The three continued to wander inside the forest. Garen followed behind with the giant mountain mouse in his sack. It was quite heavy, around twenty pounds.

While walking behind Si Lan, Garen checked his attribute pane. The attributes had not changed much, although his strength did grow a tiny bit from the original 2.08 to 2.09. This was mostly as a result of his White Cloud Secret Arts.

"Many people know about the effects of the level three White Cloud Secret Arts, but no one has reached level four before. I don’t think anyone knows what kind of effect it will have. My martial arts are heading on the right path now, but my Potential Meter stopped growing again. If only I could find the reason behind the increase of potential from the Antiques of Tragedy, I will have a direction to look in, instead of blindly blundering everywhere like I’m currently doing."

Garen reflected on his current situation while closely following behind Dale and Si Lan. These few days, due to his combat training with his senior brother and sister, he had grown to resemble a real martial artist. This was a change from within, a natural change, caused by his increase in strength and experience.

After a while, with no new prey in sight, Dale Quicksilver turned around and shouted, "There’s a castle dungeon in the front. Do you want to go check it out? Since we are already close, we can go there to take a break. I think the gunshot had scared the other animals. There’s nothing to hunt around anymore."

Chapter 36: Silversilk Castle (4)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"A dungeon? Sure, your call."

The group continued wandering through the forest after Dale Quicksilver found the marking he made on a tree from before. After being led by a few more of these markings, they arrived at an area of open ground.

"This is it. Last time I was here, we even had a barbecue at this place." Dale Quicksilver laughed as he strode on the grassland. His facial expression, however, suddenly changed after stomping on the ground a couple of times.

"Something’s different, someone has been here already! Si Lan!"

Si Lan hurried to him. She bent down and started fumbling around the ground. Soon enough, she pulled out a metal ring from the soil.

It was a dark red ring, corrupted by rust resulting from the long passage of time. The color of rust greatly contrasted with its true hue, which showed a glint of silver.

Dale Quicksilver, who had also been searching on the ground, rushed to Si Lan immediately after she found the ring.

There, a square wooden cellar door revealed itself as it was pulled up. Chunks of grass and dirt slid off the surface, revealing a dark hole underneath.

Garen didn’t ask how Dale Quicksilver knew that someone had been here, but seeing the expressions of the other two, he felt a bit nervous as well.

He walked up to the edge and looked down. The hole was deep and pitch black.

"I’ll go take a look." Surprisingly, Si Lan was the first to volunteer, not Dale Quicksilver.

"Be safe." The detective unexpectedly answered her. He nodded at her with a respectful expression.

"Let me go down instead, this is not a job for a lady…" Garen said, feeling hesitant.

"It’s fine, Si Lan isn’t your usual lady, just watch out for her." Detective answered calmly.

Si Lan pulled out a white bandana out of nowhere and tied it around her face to cover her nose. She pulled out her black dagger, secured a rope to a nearby tree, and threw the other end of the rope down the hole.

"I’ll go down first; you guys watch out up here. The trace is fresh, so the person may not be far from here!" Si Lan warned them.

"We got it, take care of yourself." The detective pulled Garen two steps back, his face even more serious.

Si Lan grabbed the rope and jumped down, quickly disappearing into the darkness. The rope instantly became taut.

Ten seconds later, it became loose again, signifying Si Lan’s successful landing.

"Sir, you better come down as well, there’s something wrong here!" Si Lan’s voice came from below.

Dale Quicksilver’s stony face turned even darker.

"If Si Lan is calling for help, it must be very serious. I have to go down myself. Mr. Kelly, the task of guarding this place is on you now. I’ll leave this rifle to you, please don’t go anywhere."

Garen was slightly surprised. He didn’t know why Dale Quicksilver trusted him so much. However, he still agreed. He still needed something from the detective, so it would be unwise to have any funny ideas right now.

"Don’t you worry, I won’t move an inch."

Dale Quicksilver nodded. He handed the rifle to Garen and fixed his belt, organizing the items he had on him. He then slid down the rope into the dungeon.

After about ten seconds, he was not visible from above ground anymore.

Garen stood alone next to the cellar door. Holding the double-barreled pipe rifle, he was on high alert.

Fortunately, there was no movement around him except for the tree leaves rustling as they blew in the wind.

After a short while, Si Lan climbed out of the hole with a dirty and tired face.

"There are two corpses down there. It seems they have been rotting for some time already."

"Corpses?" Garen faked a surprised expression and gulped. "Ms. Si Lan, you’re not joking, are you?" In fact, he had already either directly or indirectly killed two people, and after comprehending his school’s teachings regarding the heart, his mind had become calm and fearless. Two corpses no longer frightened him.

"No joke, there are two men’s bodies down there."

Si Lan sat on the grass and stabbed her dagger into the ground next to her. She took out a white handkerchief with a fading red handprint.

"What is this?"

"This handkerchief has the perpetrator’s bloody handprint; this is an important piece of the puzzle." She carefully folded the handkerchief and kept it inside a small pocket.

"These were taken from inside the dungeon. As skilled as Mr. Dale might be, he couldn’t identify them either." She pulled out a few pieces of black objects covered in mud. "He said that this might be an antique. He is still examining the area, so he asked me to bring this to you first."

"Oh." Garen carefully received the objects and peeled off the mud on them.

Soon, four small objects were laid on the grass. They were four small iron plates about the size of a knuckle, each of them rectangular-shaped.

These four objects were thick, and had some indistinct letters carved on them.

"Well?" Si Lan asked.

"This antique is useful, quite useful for me." Garen’s face twitched for a second, but it quickly returned back to normal.

"He said that if you like them, you can keep them as a reward for this unpleasant journey."

Garen touched one of the plates. He felt the same qi from the emblem, and he shook his head.

"I’m sure Dale knows how valuable these iron plates are. This reward is too much compared to my work, but I’ll have to accept it."

He couldn’t put them down since he had them in his hand. Garen glanced at Si Lan, only to see her looking at him with a faint smile, which in turn caused Garen to blush.

He could not refuse. If he could absorb all of the potential inside these plates, he was certain of having an increment of 10 points in his attribute. He had a feeling that this could even be an antique that supplied continuous qi just like the emblem.

"This gift is a little too heavy…" He gripped the iron plate in his hand. The sensation was akin to one directly holding an ice cube. A biting chill permeated his hand as though it was beginning to freeze his skin, yet it hadn’t done so in reality.

"This speed of absorption is too slow, it will take months before I could absorb them all."

Garen looked at Si Lan, his eyes squinting. "I have a check for one million dollars." He took out a bank check from his chest pocket, neatly folded it and placed it next to the plates.

"If I identified it correctly, this plate is the Black Jade Disk Dale mentioned earlier. A while ago, this disk was auctioned for the price of six million dollars in the Weisman Empire. It’s still quite a bargain for me."

He paused for a second, feeling hesitant about something.

"I’ll take it this time, but I owe Dale a big favor."

He gave her his solemn word. Even in his former life, Garen was one who valued his own promises. Once he swore an oath, he would always honor it and keep his promise.

This plate was like a great treasure for him. What it brought was not only wealth, but also the enhancement of his attributes. As long as he kept it close to him, it was bound to bring great improvement to his overall strength. He could probably catch up to his senior brothers and senior sister, and even surpassing his master Fei Baiyun, achieving a great leap in strength in an extremely short period.

"Mr. Dale knew you would accept it, and luckily, you can do him a favor right now to repay him." It was as though Si Lan had already expected Garen’s response.

"What does he want me to do? I’ll do everything in my power to help him." Garen’s pupils shrank slightly, knowing that Dale Quicksilver might have seen through his cover.

"Stop the approaching Golden Hoop." Si Lan’s eyes turned fierce, and she said in a low voice, "If you can delay him for half an hour, our help will be here! Of course, it would be better if you killed him!"

"Golden Hoop?" Garen turned around to look to his right.

A man wearing a camoflague suit along with face covered with black bandana, and had a golden ring hanging from his right ear was approaching in the grassland.

"You guys hunted me last time, but now, it’s time for me to hunt you instead."

The man’s voice was hoarse, which sounded grating and harsh.

At this moment, Dale Quicksilver climbed out of the hole, panting as he glanced at Golden Hoop.

"It’s on you, Kelly!" He tapped Garen’s shoulder and made an eye gesture to Si Lan, the two turned around and escaped toward the castle without looking back.

"Sir, that Kelly… Can he really stop the Golden Hoop?"

"Gasp… gasp… as long as he can hold him for a little while. I never expected him to stop Golden Hoop to begin with." Dale Quicksilver gasped as he ran, "The Black Jade Disk I left to him is for trading his life, and by Golden Hoop’s rules, he won’t take Kelly’s life."

"So you had all of this planned out huh." Si Lan was only slightly panting, her stamina seemingly unabated.

"Let’s keep running, Golden Hoop will catch up to us soon." Gale Quicksilver said as he climbed through the hole in the fence.

*****************

Inside the forest.

Garen collected the Black Jade Disk and slowly stood up. His bones made a series of loud cracking noises. "I owe Dale a big favor, and killing you will repay it. Don’t blame me, blame your own misfortune."

His body swelled up like an air balloon with his height growing from 1.7 meters to over 2 meters. A strong and violent aura began to emanate from him. His muscles and skin turned from pale white to a leather-like black color.

Golden Hoop’s expression changed. Under the strong force of Garen’s aura, he was pushed back two steps.

"Who the hell are you?"

Garen didn’t answer. Instead, he flexed his arms and reached toward Golden Ring with a grasping motion. His fearsome and muscular arms coiled with purple veins clawed toward Golden Hoop’s head as he crossed a few meters in milliseconds.

Chapter 37: Leave (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

With a sudden and violent attack, Garen's arm caught the tip of Golden Hoop's head—and like the giant claws of a vicious beast—he clasped it tightly as if he were going to crush it.

This was the Acceleration Technique of the White Cloud Secret Method. Combined with any other action, it could achieve the effect of instantaneous acceleration to create a sudden attack.

This was the first time Garen had used White Cloud Combat Arts in a real battle. White Cloud Combat Arts required an imposing momentum to it: every single action had to exhibit a crushing force.

When his palm was about to catch Golden Hoop's forehead, Golden Hoop produced a dagger out of nowhere and stabbed upwards, aiming for Garen's wrist.

The move was swift and agile. The tip of the dagger seemed to instantly accelerate, as if some special force technique was used.

Whack!

Garen turned his palm sideways to avoid the blade, then he hit Golden Hoop's wrist with the side of his palm. With a swoosh, the dagger flew out of his hand and landed in the bushes.

Golden Hoop took the opportunity to back up a few steps, opening up some distance between them.

""

"You think you can win by force? Fool!" Golden Hoop reached his right hand behind his waist, and suddenly, four small black throwing knives were flung towards Garen.

Swoosh! Swoosh! Swoosh! Swoosh!

The four throwing knives flew out in a flash and accurately struck onto Garen's chest.

Garen didn't manage to respond in time. He wanted to cross his arms to protect his chest, but when he raised his arms, the throwing knives had already pierced his clothes.

The throwing knives merely ripped his clothes and were nailed to his skin, but they didn't cut through the skin.

He grabbed one of the knives and threw it at Golden Hoop. A violent whirling sound followed. The throwing knife turned into a round disk and flew straight at Golden Hoop, but he evaded it with ease.

Garen flung the three remaining knives in succession, but they were all casually avoided by Golden Hoop. This time, Garen took the opportunity to pick up the double-barreled rifle while Golden Hoop was distracted.

Bang!

White smoke came out of the barrels as the shot hit a tree trunk and left a black indent. Some leaves and bark fell off the tree like raindrops from the force of the blast.

Golden Hoop was extremely fast. He started dodging once Garen showed signs of his next actions, which made him impossible to aim at. After a few evasions, he seemed to realize that Garen's reactions were not as quick as his, and his eyes narrowed into a sneer. His astonishment at Garen's physical change earlier instantly faded.

""

"I thought you wanted to kill me? Do you think you can?"

""

"Go to hell!" Garen roared. He raised the double-barreled shotgun and flung it at Golden Hoop like an iron bar. Garen's force caused the gun to give a loud, piercing whistle in mid-air. This was to no avail either: Golden Hoop turned his body to the right and easily avoided it.

"What's the use of having a ton of strength? If you can't hit me, it's all in vain," Golden Hoop jeered. With yet another dagger in hand, his body suddenly drew close. He did a slight flick with the dagger, then stabbed towards Garen's wrist.

Angled upwards, this stab was quick and precise. He had targeted the moment when Garen's large range of motion created some space.

"It's over." A trace of malice flashed across Golden Hoop's eyes.

At this instant, Garen squinted as he swung his right arm backwards, avoiding the dagger in a flash.

The slow pace he had a while ago had seemingly transformed. His right arm flung out like a rubber hose at a lightning-pace and hit Golden Hoop's left arm.

The speed of this attack was different from before. Only a glimpse of a shadow could be seen from the swinging arm. His speed had almost doubled!

Golden Hoop stared wide-eyed. His dagger was only halfway through the stab when he felt a crack in his right arm, which was then followed by a burst of pain. Suddenly, his body turned light as it involuntarily leapt towards the right.

Wham!

Golden Hoop crashed into the bushes. After some ruffling, he created a trail in the shrubbery, trampling over a large amount of plant and leaves. He went on for a good seven to eight meters before colliding against a large white rock.

Garen stayed put and didn't give chase. As his body gradually restored to its original state, he shook his right arm a little as a relaxed smile broke across his face.

"You really thought I was slow? Even though I'm not as fast as you, I'm not that slow. I deliberately said I wanted to kill you first, then acted like a clumsy doofus. All of it was to lure you to stay and duel with me, and to make you think that you could get rid of me easily without wasting too much time, with the added benefit of relieving yourself of your hatred towards me. Too bad…"

He slowly walked over. He saw Golden Hoop try to hold his body up from the ground, but his every attempt was met with the same result: he kept falling flat every time. It wasn't just his right arm; when he was stumbling through the bushes, it was obvious that there was an unnatural distortion in his left arm—it was broken.

"I am not as fast as you. If you ignored me and directly pursued Dale Quicksilver and his companion, then I wouldn't have been able to stop you. Good thing you were agitated by me enough to stay put." It was the first time he had used the combat arts strategy taught by Fei Baiyun in an actual combat. The fact that it worked like a charm gave him an immense sense of relief.

Golden Hoop's face was livid. Fresh blood slowly dripped from the bottom half of his body. He must have cut himself somewhere when he was stumbling through the bushes.

"You got hit by four of my knives, but you weren't… cough, cough… weren't even injured. Even so, don't get too cocky. Someone will avenge me!"

Upon finishing the sentence, purple blood instantly spilled from the corner of his mouth. His head bent askew, his eyes clouded over, and he eventually stopped breathing.

Garen squinted and quickly crouched down to apply pressure on Golden Hoop's chest. His body was still warm, but his heartbeat had stopped.

"Dead? The infamous thief, Golden Hoop, can’t possibly die so easily from my trickery, can he?" He felt that it was all too simple.

Golden Hoop and Dale Quicksilver had been battling wits for a few years. If he could so easily be dispatched, he should have disappeared ages ago—it wouldn't be up to Garen to do it.

Garen gave a puff as he stood up and surveyed his surroundings.

The forest was quiet: only the fluttering of tree leaves blown by the wind could be heard.

He crouched down again and started examining Golden Hoop's belongings and clothing.

The man had nothing on him except some money and throwing knives.

Looking at the cloth covering Golden Hoop's face, Garen frowned. When he removed it, he was instantly shocked at what he saw.

Under the mask was a half-burnt face with a black scar of the number "102" on his right cheek, as if he was branded.

"102? Looks like Golden Hoop is not a person, it's an organization." Garen suddenly felt that things had become more complicated. "That means there is probably someone else pursuing Dale Quicksilver and Si Lan. This guy was just a decoy."

He stood up, mindfully examined his surroundings, then quickly ran towards the direction of the castle.

"This Golden Hoop is just an ordinary person with some training in combat arts. Most people could easily impersonate him with a bit of practice. He just knew some Explosive Speed Force Technique. The real Golden Hoop wouldn't be so simple. "

Recalling the "102" on that man's face, Garen felt a heavy weight in his heart.

"If that number represents a rank or a serial code, that means Golden Hoop is an organization with more than a hundred members. So why would such a big organization dedicate itself to stealing antiques? Purely for profit? Or is there another purpose?"

From how Dale Quicksilver casually gifted him the Black Jade Disk, it showed that he didn't know what that meant to Garen. He probably thought that Garen had great skill and also liked antiques.

Valuable antiques of tragedy like the Black Jade Disk were absolutely irresistible for such a collector.

But that was Kelly the collector—a fake persona. The real Garen was, in fact, merely a high school student.

The thought of facing a murderous evil organization like Golden Hoop alone made Garen uneasy, even though he had been training in martial arts for so long. Although he had lived for decades in his past life and he wasn't actually a teenage high school student, that life was led in a lawful and socially stable environment.

He quickly ran back. Soon, he was in front of the hole in the castle fence.

Garen hurried through the hole before turning to a corner and heading towards the main gate of the castle. Suddenly, he glimpsed a flash of light to his right.

He stopped in his tracks. He focused his gaze towards the direction of the light, and he could vaguely make out a black telescope withdraw into the trees in a distance. The flash of light earlier was the reflection of sunlight off the lens of the telescope.

"I didn't think there would be someone surveilling. That means my every move has been monitored." Garen was stunned. "No wonder Mr. 102 said someone would avenge him. This is troublesome."

He thought he had killed that person in the forest without being seen, and his organization shouldn't have noticed him. Now, he realized this thought was too naïve.

"I'll just have to find Dale Quicksilver and Si Lan first, then figure it out from there. To be marked by the organization but still remain unclear about the situation, that's courting death."

He walked around the side of the castle to the front gates.

The castle gates were ajar. It was unusually quiet inside; he couldn't hear the voices of Dale Quicksilver and Miss Si Lan.

Garen quickly walked through the gates. In the castle hall, the previously set white-colored wooden coffee table had been overturned, and the tea from a glass pot had spilled all over. A clutter of footprints could be faintly seen all around the floor, as if a lot of people had rushed past this place.

Garen briefly scanned the footprints. Most of them were moist black footprints, with some green moss mixed into them.

"Someone was here, and they were not alone." He lightened his footsteps as he crept up to the first floor, then he started patrolling the corridors.

The castle walls and floor were covered in burnt ash, the type that was white with some black mixed inside, like black and white paint that wasn't fully blended.

Remnants of half-burnt oil paintings still hung on some parts of the walls along the corridor.

Walking towards Dale Quicksilver's bedroom, Garen tried to breathe as softly as possible, all the while listening for movement within the castle.

It seemed like he was alone in the entire castle; there was no sound. The air was filled with a dead silence and desolation.

Soon, he reached the entrance of Dale Quicksilver's bedroom. The iron door was ajar.

Garen gently pushed it open and went in through the gap without making too much noise.

There was a white bed in the room, a single sofa, and a large rectangular crate.

The thick curtains covered most of the windows, only allowing a ray of light to shine in through a small part. The whole bedroom was eclipsed in shadow, and it seemed dark inside.

The crate was placed at the end of the bed; an oil lamp was still alight on top of it. The dim light from the oil lamp illuminated the parts of the room eclipsed by the shadow of the curtains.

Chapter 38: Leave (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

§§§382

Garen treaded lightly into the room. The stale and depressing air made him feel slightly uneasy.

[This room is too quiet...]

He could not hear any movement. The windows seemed to have particularly good soundproofing, insulating the room from the outside sounds of birds chirping and the wind blowing. The whole room was oppressively silent, as if there had been someone resting here moments ago who left in an instant.

Garen slowly walked to the large package at the end of the bed. He was suddenly curious about Dale Quicksilver's large crate.

[I thought he said he didn't bring much kerosene? Why is the lamp lit in the daytime?]

He reached out to pick up the kerosene lamp.

Creak…

The sound came from the door behind him. Startled, Garen turned around to see that the door had closed on its own and had been locked from the outside when he was not looking.

He strode over and tried to turn the doorknob, but it kept clicking without turning. He could hear the footsteps of someone outside running away hastily along the corridor.

Garen's face sank.

[This place is strange indeed…] Suddenly, he recalled the information that Dale Quicksilver had showed him. The detective had annotated his key analyses at the end of the material:

[There was one common factor on the bodies of the victims in the mysterious deaths of the three previous masters of Silversilk Castle: they were all wearing the Bronze Cross Emblem handed down to them by their ancestors.]

[According to legend, this Emblem was a second-tier military medal awarded during wartime for meritorious achievement. But in fact, according to my research, the masters of the castle had obtained this Emblem as early as two hundred years ago, so it couldn't have been something awarded during the war which occurred later.]

At this thought, Garen quickly pulled out the black thread around his neck. A magenta emblem hung on the thread with a letter "P" in the middle. It was the Bronze Cross Emblem that he always had on him.

The color of the Emblem seemed brighter now, like it had just been polished. There was no sign of it being timeworn.

"This is indeed the problem!" Garen's expression was somber as he glanced around the entire bedroom. He yanked the Emblem off his neck, put it into the crate, closed the lid, then rushed to the window in a few strides.

Crash!

He smashed the window with his fist.

All of a sudden, the whole bedroom seemed as if had escaped from a silent film. As though someone had turned off the mute button, everything livened up in an instant.

Garen had a spooky feeling in his heart, as if danger was rapidly approaching, and he subconsciously did not want to leave through the door.

He stood by the window and looked down. This was the second floor, more than ten meters away from the grass lawn.

[I need to get some bed sheets to make a rope. It's quite high from up here!]

As he was about to turn around, he suddenly felt someone push him hard from behind. The force was stronger than his could muster, even in his current state.

Uncontrollably, Garen fell straight out of the window.

"Who!!" he roared. His mind blanked and his whole body was extremely tense.

"Hehe…"

A faint laughter came from behind.

Bam!

Garen stretched his arms out to cushion his body against the grass. Fortunately, he had a very good physique and he was strong enough. His arms merely suffered from slight dislocation due to the trauma of the fall and his poor arm positioning.

He rolled over and got up quickly, then turned to look up at the bedroom on the second floor. The curtains were fluttering in the wind, but no one was there. He took a look at the castle gates, but they were now locked shut. The gates that were ajar earlier were now locked from the outside.

Garen resisted the pain from his shoulder dislocations, took a long look at the castle, then turned around to sprint into the distance.

He passed the castle fence, but did not show any signs of stopping. He headed directly along the mountain trail that he had come from, rushing to Canoe Town.

[From that push earlier, an ordinary person definitely would have been killed by the fall. In that position, falling head first, the neck would have snapped. If I wasn’t someone trained in martial arts, I would have been crippled even if I survived!] Garen still had a lingering unease. Fortunately, he didn't go up to inspect the third-floor bedroom. If he had fallen down from the third floor…

Recalling the report on the previous three masters of the castle, there were multiple incidents in the records about servants falling out of windows to their deaths while cleaning the rooms.

[I thought those were accidents, possibly due to a flaw in the castle design. But now it seems that they must have been pushed like me!] Garen felt sure of it because the servants had all fallen head first to their deaths,, the exact posture they would have been in if they were pushed.

As the pain from his shoulders grew, Garen rolled up his sleeves to take a look: they had swollen into a red mass.

"I need to hurry into town to get treated!" His pace accelerated.

********************

Snap!

"OUCH!!" Garen’s left shoulder was swollen like a red pastry bun. Baring his upper body, he was sitting at the pub where he previously had tea with Dale Quicksilver.

A doctor in a grey suit was sitting beside him. He grabbed Garen's left arm and forcefully shifted it back into place.

Garen instantly gasped as the pain made his whole body sweat. A crisp 'crack' came from his joints.

"Done, it's relocated!"

"Thank you very much, Dr. Ash." Garen nodded, then took out a stack of cash notes with his freshly relocated right arm and put it on the table. "Money for the treatment."

"Very well." Dr. Ash was the veteran healer in town who often treated the locals. Although he lacked a formal license to practice medicine, his bone manipulation skills were very reliable. After all, in small towns like these, most patients were afflicted with similar minor ailments.

Once he arrived back in town, Garen had immediately paid the townsfolk to call for Dr. Ash. Now his dislocated shoulder is fixed.

"I'll prescribe you some medicine. Apply a little to the injuries every day according to the dosage on the label and you'll recover in no time." Dr. Ash took the money, smiled, and said, "It's rare to encounter a major patient like you. I'll gladly take this $1,000."

"You deserve it. After all, I woke you from your afternoon nap for treatment. Think of the extra money as compensation for your troubles." Garen nodded indifferently. "Sorry to have inconvenienced you."

"Not at all, not at all." Ash rummaged through his portable small white medicine box and took out a milky white glass vial, then put it on the table after checking the label.

"This is the ointment that you have to apply every day. Remember not to be too vigorous and you should be fine. I'll take my leave first."

Garen nodded.

"Thanks."

He watched as Ash carried his medicine box and left, walking along a narrow path before disappearing past the bushes.

Garen sat at the table, gently lifted the wooden cup, and downed the coffee inside.

"Boss, another cup!" he turned and shouted into the small building.

"Of course!" A plump middle-aged man with a black beard came out, carrying a glass coffee pot. He carefully poured Garen a fresh cup of coffee.

At that moment, two fit-looking farmers carrying hoes walked in and plopped down at one of the tables.

"Two beers please!"

The boss hurried inside and carried some beer out.

Garen sat in place, sensing the constant cool flow of energy from the Black Jade Disk that he had just acquired. For a moment, the pain in his shoulders seemed to have diminished.

When he was training at the dojo with the seniors, shoulder dislocations were a common occurrence. He could still handle the pain and did not find it too unbearable, so it did not really affect his normal activities.

While sitting in this small pub , he had recovered enough to reevaluate Dale Quicksilver's actions.

[Putting aside the oddities of the castle itself, I didn't expect Dale Quicksilver to leave the case and deliberately live in a small castle in the countryside for so long. It's unusual no matter how you think about it.] Garen took a sip of the coffee.

[But from another perspective, some people from the Golden Hoop had appeared around the castle. Assuming Silversilk Castle was their intended target, Dale Quicksilver might have been after them instead of the castle. Then it all makes sense.]

[Golden Hoop's target is Silversilk Castle. Dale Quicksilver tracked them because of the case, and out of random luck I got mixed up in all of it. As someone whose identity is unclear, letting me face the Golden Hoop was a way to test if I was a spy sent by them. There's probably more to it, but that should be the gist of it.]

[If that's the case, where is Dale Quicksilver now?] Garen subconsciously wanted to rub his eyebrows, but couldn't raise his shoulder. A piercing pain followed and he let out a wry smile.

Nearing noon, the sun turned red. Business in the pub improved as more and more people came in and the boss brought a few more chairs and tables out to accommodate. Noise filled the entire pub as farmers and townspeople ate, drank, and conversed loudly.

Garen moved to sit alone in a corner. Unlike the rowdy crowd, he sat quietly on a chair drinking his coffee.

"Boss, mind if I ask you something?" Garen called out when the boss passed him.

"What is it, sir?" The plump boss stopped in his tracks. He remembered that this Mr. Kelly was the one who had tea here previously with the gentleman with extraordinary flair. Customers with such elegance were not something the average townsfolk could match up to, so he treated them with a careful attitude.

"I'd like to ask whether the man who had tea with me yesterday has come back to the town yet?" Garen inquired casually with a whisper. With the detective experience that Dale Quicksilver had, if he intended to hide, he wouldn't allow himself to be so easily discovered by someone like the boss.

"He has, he has! He even came here for tea earlier today," the plump boss answered quickly.

He didn't expect the boss to react immediately and answer him so definitively.

"He's back?" Garen was stunned. "Did he have anything to say?"

"Oh, no he didn't. He merely ordered the same black tea as you had yesterday and sat in the exact same place," the boss replied quickly.

"I see…" Garen nodded thoughtfully. Obviously, this spot was a clue that Dale Quicksilver had intentionally left for him, but Garen did not intend to find Dale at the moment.

[Seems like getting myself mixed up with this detective has been somewhat detrimental… It's better if we go our separate ways. If what Dale said is true, then he's tracking the Antiques of Tragedy and the secret contained within. If that's the case, I can follow in his footsteps anyway since it would be difficult to find the Antiques of Tragedy using the normal routes.]

[If my speculation proves accurate, coupled with the fact that the Golden Hoop seems to be searching for the same thing, both of them could help me track down the Antiques of Tragedy. I'll just have to find the right opportunity to approach them and exchange something for it.]

Garen made preliminary plans for what was to come. Although it had been dangerous, he had managed to benefit. Even though he lost the Bronze Cross Emblem, he acquired the Black Jade Disk. The latter was much more valuable since it still had potential left to be absorbed.

Chapter 39: Felicity (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

When he reached the city from Canoe Town, it was past eight o'clock at night. Garen headed straight home, washed up, and went to bed.

His parents were not home. They were probably at some work gathering together. His sister Ying Er, who was reading on the sofa, raised the book to cover her face when she saw him come in. He couldn't figure out what was up with her.

Garen still felt some pain from his shoulder dislocation even though he had applied the ointment. Coupled with everything that happened at the castle today, he was too physically and mentally exhausted to take notice.

He had been resting at home for a week. The swelling in his shoulder had reduced, but he still couldn't do exercises that were too intense, including training in martial arts.

Garen couldn't bear to stay at home any longer. His sister was always sulking and didn't talk to him. Things like computers and television, which could occupy free time, did not exist in this era and world. He took a little change with him and went directly to the library in the city.

"This is your library card. Keep it properly, and don't wear out the serial number."

The receptionist at the lobby service counter handed a black square card over to him with both hands, a smile on her face.

"Thank you." Garen took the card and glanced at the serial number: 233. "Is the serial number based on the number of people?"

"Yes it is, sir." The receptionist nodded. "Turn left for general reading, and head right for classics, rare books, and the special and foreign language collections."

"Okay."

Holding the card, Garen directly headed down the left corridor.

It was slightly dark inside the black corridor. On the walls on both sides were yellow wall lamps that dimly lit the whole corridor.

Only after entering the corridor did he notice two young girls walking in front of him, one in front of the other. The ground was covered with thick black carpet. There was almost no sound of footsteps.

"There are too few people, mainly because it's too expensive. 5000 dollars for a card, someone has to introduce you, and you're only allowed to loan for a month. Most of the people who are really interested in coming here to read can't afford it, and the people who can just don't have the time."

Nodding slightly, Garen followed them for a distance and turned left into a small, narrow room.

The room was illuminated with a pale yellow light. All the walls were covered by bookshelves, and the densely arranged red-covered books had completely blocked the walls behind. In the room were two single red sofas and a black wooden table full of books.

Looking straight across from the entrance, there was a door on the opposite wall that led to another room similar to this one, and there was another door opposite of that room, connected to the new room.

The rooms linked into a straight line like meat on a kebab, door to door, until they reach a corner at the far end. Guests could walk in a straight line through all of the rooms.

The two girls walking in front of Garen didn't stop. They kept walking on until they stood in front of the third room.

Garen retracted his line of sight and scanned the books on the walls. Wooden category signs hung below the wall lamps. The books in this room were history books.

He kept walking on through to the next room. The second room was geography.

The third room was dance, drama and illustration arts. The two girls weren't pretty, but as they stood there with a book in each hand, they looked quite ecstatic.

The fourth room was mathematics, chemistry, and philosophy.

The fifth room was marriage, sex, and healthcare. In fact, it was the place where they stored those books.

The culture in the Confederation was influenced by the Weisman Empire: it was very liberal. Even though there weren't many of these types of books, but they could be publicly published.

Inside the room, a 30-odd-year-old woman sat on the sofa immersed in her reading.

In the sixth room, once he stepped in, Garen noticed a girl in a white skirt with black lace sitting on the sofa. Her pale blonde hair was draped behind her with a white hairband tied in the middle. She looked extremely ladylike.

"Felicity? You're here today too?" Garen was slightly surprised but instantly laughed. He walked to the girl and sat down beside her on the sofa.

"What a coincidence." The girl looked up, showing her delicate and pure face.

She had porcelain white skin which had a slightly translucent quality to it. Her eyes were big and clear, the dark blue irises focused coolly on Garen. She gave off the impression of a cool young girl, completely different from the arrogant rich girl at the riverside picnic.

This was her in real life, the mild side that only showed when around recognized friends.

Felicity sat on a wide comfy sofa. Her petite frame almost sank into it, enveloped by the sofa’s redness. She had a large red-covered book on her lap. The book covered most of her upper body, which made her look dainty and cute.

But Garen already knew that this pretty girl was the type that was cool on the outside but friendly on the inside, so he wasn't deceived by her appearance. It was, after all, Felicity who introduced him for his membership at the library. Otherwise, he would not have gotten in because he had no idea about the existence of such a library in the city in the first place.

Garen switched to a more comfortable sitting position, took a red-covered book from the table and casually browsed it. The book was a record about coats of arms. It had detailed entries about the coats of arms of famous families within the Confederation and throughout the world.

"Even though it's a holiday, how did you find the time to come over to Huaishan?"

Felicity continued to read with her head down. "It's quiet here, unlike in Manroland, where I'd be bothered by a bunch of flies."

After they had previously met, they chatted about Jewelry of Tragedy. Garen's immense interest in Antiques of Tragedy had fueled Felicity's eagerness to chat about the topic, given that she had always been fond of unique and mysterious antiques and jewelry.

Felicity could tell that Garen wasn't the type of person that would deliberately approach her for ulterior motives, so she let down her guard. When it came to her favorite topic of mysterious antiques and jewelry, he showed a very serious attitude and seemed very eager to listen. Felicity couldn't help but have a good impression of Garen, and the both of them chatted in a small café for five to six hours before reluctantly calling it a day.

Since then, Felicity had taken the initiative to help Garen apply for access to the library and a library card. Both of them could be regarded as pure antique and jewelry enthusiasts.

"That must be tiring for you, always hiding." Garen smiled. "Oh yeah, I thought you said you found a new goodie the last time? How's that going?"

Felicity put down her book. Her brows furrowed; she seemed frustrated.

"It's difficult for me to get my hands on it. The seller wouldn't sell it, even after I made him two offers. Looks like he is genuinely reluctant to part with the item."

"What is it?"

"A lucky bow from the great maritime era—a mermaid bust that has been said to bring luck."

"A mermaid bust? How much did you offer?" Garen licked his lips and asked.

"Two-hundred and fifty thousand."

"For a mermaid bust bow, two-hundred and fifty thousand is indeed a bit low."

"But this is the maximum amount of cash I can move recently, any more and I can't afford it. I don't even have much pocket money." Felicity's small face looked distressed.

"Let's not talk about that then. Oh yeah, any news about the two pieces of jewelry I asked you to help me investigate?" Garen changed the topic.

"That's easy." Felicity paused, and started recalling, "Those two pieces of jewelry, one of them is Marceline's Blue Fantasy. According to legend, it was an antique jewelry created by a master jeweler named Marceline for her lover. The master passed away due to illness shortly after finishing the piece. But peculiarly, the lover wearing this jewelry had continuous good fortune. Soon, he grew from an ordinary person to become a jewelry master himself and became very wealthy. The jewelry in question was displayed in one of his jewelry stores as a store treasure. Later after it was stolen, a series of countless forgeries kept appearing, and this made it impossible to recover the real thing."

"This person isn't dead?" Garen was surprised.

Felicity rolled her eyes at him. "He's alive and well. Why would he be dead?"

She enjoyed this relaxed feeling whenever she chatted with Garen. In front of others, all they cared about was her beauty, family, and background.

In front of this ordinary boy her age, he didn't care about her appearance and background, but instead valued her most for her knowledge, her understanding of antiques and jewelry, and especially her knowledge of mysterious jewelry.

"Hehe… I misspoke." Garen gave an embarrassed smile. "What about the other piece?"

Felicity leaned back, caught a black rope hanging from the wall, and gave it a light tug. "Wait a minute. What do you want to order?"

"Uh… Cuzzolini Black Tea then," Garen casually said.

Felicity nodded.

A while later, a girl in a black-and-white maid uniform entered the room. "Anything I can get for the two of you?"

"A cup of Tornado Coffee, a cup of Cuzzolini Black Tea, both warm," Felicity ordered softly.

"Your order is coming, please wait." The girl maid bowed in ceremony then left the room.

To a side, Garen was laughing at her. "I thought you liked cold drinks?"

"What are you laughing at?! Can't I occasionally have a change in taste?" Felicity's cheeks turned red and started to get defensive. "Do you think I'm copying you?"

"Yes, yes, yes, I know, I know." Garen kept waving his hand and suppressed a smile. "I understand," Upon saying that, he couldn't help but burst out laughing.

"Alright, get serious!" Felicity hit the top of Garen's head with a book. The force seemed heavy, but it was actually light. "Let's talk about the other piece, also a store treasure owned by this jeweler. Called Avril's Eye, it was inspired by a princess of the Weisman Empire named Avril. According to legend, she was blind from birth, but had a pair of extremely beautiful eyes. This piece was named after her eyes. It doesn't have any mysterious background, but it is said that the piece was blessed by Weisman the Third, in hopes that the princess' eyes would forever be as clear as the jewelry. Rumor has it that ever since this piece of jewelry went into circulation among the masses, it hasn't been seen for years, and it's unclear whether it is even real."

"It should be real…" Garen touched his chin and whispered.

"How do you know?"

"Just a guess."

"…"

Garen smiled then got serious. "Alright, down to business. Last time you mentioned there was a new change in the Halo of Tragedy you bought. What change? Mind letting me have a look?"

Felicity pondered but did not say anything. At that moment, the maid entered bringing in the black tea and coffee, served it in front of them, and then quietly left.

Hot steam rose slowly from the brown cups. Suddenly, the room seemed unusually quiet.

After a while, Felicity started to open up. She frowned and rubbed her temples, seemingly bothered.

"I can't put my finger on it… It's just… it's just a peculiar feeling. Nothing has gone right recently: my pocket money has been restricted, friends quarreled with me for no good reason..." she paused.

"You know that I don't have many friends in the first place. My circle has always been narrow. Ever since I bought the Halo of Tragedy, it's been like this. Do you think it's really the effect of that thing?"

"Where's your Halo of Tragedy? Let me have a look." Garen started frowning too.

Felicity's face went scarlet in an instant.

"I didn't bring it with me. I'll bring it over to you next time."

Chapter 40: Felicity (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Felicity!"

Suddenly, a blond young man wearing a black overcoat walked into the room.

"Why are you still here? Still researching your antiques and jewelry? Stop fooling around, go home. You have to catch the afternoon train. Quickly go home and pack."

The young man glanced at Garen who was sitting at the side. He could tell that Garen was close with Felicity.

"Don't keep obsessing about jewelries and antiques all day. Can you please apply yourself to something more meaningful?!"

"Felix, I can decide my matters for myself. I don't need instructions from you!" Felicity bluntly replied. "Researching antiques and jewelries isn't meaningful? Doing what I want to do, that's meaningful!"

"You!" The youth's face turned scarlet. "You only know how to talk back at me! You leave the family business unattended, you leave your own company unattended, and you come to this godforsaken countryside to do research about jewelries and antiques! That's just perfect. You're doing great! I dare you to not go back today!"

"So what if I don't?!" Felicity coldly replied, then turned away to ignore him.

"Hanging around with these jewelry and antique freaks all day, skipping the family banquet… I want to see how you manage on your own when you get into trouble!" The young man was fuming. His gaze turned to Garen.

"One moment you're meeting this enthusiast, the next moment, another. I tell you, Felicity, these people who only know how to research antiques and jewelries, the most they can be in their lifetime is a jewelry appraiser. Hang around these people all day, and see what you'll become!"

"Mind your words!" Felicity brusquely stood up. "He's my friend!"

"Hmph!" The young man expressed his disdain. "Father already knows about the nonsense you get up to, researching antiques and jewelries all day. He's not happy. I want to see how you explain yourself to him."

"That's none of your business! Don't think you can lecture me freely just because you're my brother! How rude!"

Garen, who was sitting at the side, frowned too. This young man, Felix, was Felicity's biological brother. His tone seemed to convey his displeasure about his sister's preoccupation with antiques, and naturally, that made him dislike the person discussing antiques with Felicity as well.

"Please keep your voices down!" A bespectacled middle-aged maid came in and whispered. "This is a public place. It's the library. Please keep silent."

"Apologies." The young man nodded before striding out the room.

Felicity apologetically smiled at the middle-aged woman. "Sorry about that. How embarrassing."

The woman nodded and left with a strict look on her face.

Felicity sat back onto the sofa, her expression distraught.

Sitting at the side, Garen frowned and said, "Go back first if you're busy. Our discussions aren't that important."

"My brother was rude. I apologize on his behalf." Felicity was slightly frustrated.

"It's nothing. I can tell your family seems to disapprove of you researching antiques and jewelries."

"Yeah. They think I'm loafing around. I've been reprimanded for this multiple times," Felicity helplessly said. "My family situation is complicated. My parents allocated more resources to me than others, so my peers aren't too happy about me. They keep finding trouble with me."

"You can't help it either." Garen had known about Felicity's family background from Fayne.

That wasn't any ordinary business family. It was a mega family with ties to the upper class of the Confederation, with assets and businesses across several big provinces. Compared to Garen's uncle and his master Fei Baiyun, they were on a completely different level.

Felicity's family even had their own private militia, and her father was one of the most significant figures in the family.

They sat for a while before a middle-aged man with a mature look walked into the room. He wore a black suit, had a fit physique, and looked polite.

"Miss, it's time to head back. The time you set is up."

Felicity nodded and sat up straight on the sofa. "Got it."

"This is my bodyguard, Anchor. I'll be going first, you take your time."

"Okay." Garen nodded. He glanced at the man called Anchor, and he couldn't help but narrow his eyes.

He got a trace impression of Golden Hoop No. 102 from him, yet he seemed even stronger than Golden Hoop.

Garen's took a quick glance at the man's waist: it seemed to bulge slightly, like there was something stuck there.

"Someone with his skill, if coupled with a handgun, as long as his marksmanship is not too bad, I'm no match against him. They are veritably a powerful family. Metropolitans are indeed different."

The pride he felt from his big display of skills earlier instantly evaporated.

After Felicity and her bodyguard left, Garen sat on the sofa alone. There was still a hint of girly fragrance in the air.

"If the Golden Hoop that day were good with handguns, I wouldn't have been able to defeat him so easily. Firearms are indeed the natural enemy of martial art practitioners…"

He sighed and took a sip of black tea.

"Fortunately, I have the Black Jade Disk. I now have new Attribute Points to enhance myself." He scanned the Attribute Pane at the bottom of his vision. The Strength on it had increased by 0.1 due to the White Cloud Secret Method: it was at 2.11 now. Potential had also increased to 164%.

"It's just that this is too slow a speed. Only one point increase in a week."

He took a look at the Skills Pane. He skipped through the academic subjects and directed his line of sight at the White Cloud Secret Method. He paused on it for three seconds. The White Cloud Secret Method didn't move; apparently, it could no longer be increased.

"So it has indeed peaked?"

"I give up. I'll just add it to Intelligence. Recently, the situation has been chaotic, let's see how adding to Intelligence will help me sort it all out."

He hesitated, then directed his line of sight onto Intelligence.

Snap!

A clear force streamed into Intelligence.

It increased from 1.20 to 1.50 in an instant.

Garen felt his brain cool over. His stale mind instantly became unusually clear. It seemed that his reasoning, response, logic, and memory were markedly enhanced. However, this kind of enhancement was vague; there was no way to practically compare the effects before and after.

"According to the standard units that I initially formulated, the average level for an ordinary person would be at 1. So now, I have more than one and a half of an ordinary person's average intellect. The intellectual restrictions for certain subjects should be gone."

Under the Skills column, many subjects were restricted to a base value of Intelligence. Without reaching that limit, one could only acquire the skill in accordance with normal progression. Once that base value was reached, one would have photographic memory skills. Any content from a subject would be easily absorbed, thought processes would be quicker, and one would rapidly attain the level of mastery expected from enhancing with points.

Now that he felt much more clear-headed, Garen started to contemplate the current situation.

"If I want to obtain Antiques of Tragedy without risk, I could pull out now and let Grace keep track of the case progression of Dale Quicksilver and the others. I could also approach Golden Hoop through Grace's original company to buy the Antiques of Tragedy. Once they find a new Antique of Tragedy, I could offer them the highest bid possible to get it. My only worry is that I wouldn't have enough money to buy it. This is a way, but the amount of capital required is huge."

"I could also come at this from another perspective. I am able to analyze whether an antique is real by absorbing Potential. That way, in respect of Antiques of Tragedy or mysterious jewelries, I have the absolute appraisal authority. As long as I improve on my knowledge and experience of identifying jewelries and antiques, it shouldn't be difficult for me to become the expert Antiques of Tragedy appraiser for the detective and the others."

"It is likely that Dale Quicksilver isn't aware of the Potential within Antiques of Tragedy. Otherwise, he wouldn't have handed the Black Jade Disk to me so easily." Garen already had dealings with Dale Quicksilver, so he was clear about that key point.

In others' eyes, Antiques of Tragedy were just mysterious precious objects backed by a strange legend. In his eyes, they were valuable objects from which he could absorb Potential to strengthen himself.

"I don't necessarily have to own them. I could plainly gain contact with the Antiques of Tragedy with my hybrid identity as appraiser and collector. I just need to let both sides, the detectives and Golden Hoop, recognize that I am the only one who is able to identify a real Antique of Tragedy without error. This way, I could stay out of the whole ordeal, yet achieve my purpose."

It had to be said that since adding points to Intelligence, Garen felt much more clear-headed. He had everything planned in a flash, and he even found a suitable role for himself.

"Right now, all that's left is to improve my knowledge of antiques appraisal. The old man should be experienced in this." Garen instantly thought of Old Man Gregor from Dolphin Antiques.

"Then, there's the book that Old Man Gregor mysteriously took out the other day. I have no idea what it was. It seems like the old man has secrets of his own, but it doesn't matter as long as it's not troublesome."

As a man of action, Garen stood up and searched for books on antique appraisal in the series of rooms, but unfortunately, there were none. He went over to the right side of the library and searched in the special collections room, but there was nothing there either. It was a pity that there was only a handful of books in the right side of the library.

Coming out of the library, Garen hailed a horse carriage and headed straight for Dolphin Antiques.

Sitting in the carriage, Garen had a faint sense of irritability in his heart. He had added so many Attribute points on himself, his strength had reached a high level, but when he met Felicity's brother earlier, he nevertheless failed to counter his condescending tone.

Regardless of whether it was at Fei Baiyun's White Cloud Dojo, or his uncle's shady company, he was just an ordinary small character in their eyes. Even with the martial art prowess that he was so proud of, never mind firearms, he couldn't even defeat his Senior Brothers and Sisters; martial arts weren’t a pure contest of strength.

He slightly closed his eyes to rest them. Hearing the crisp clatter of hooves and the sound of wheels rolling through pavement, Garen recalled everything he had been through since arriving.

"Even though I have special abilities, I am currently still a common disciple at the dojo, a student at Shengying Academy, and the son of an employee at a common company. I still have to take everything one step at a time; I'm still miles away from being a true great force…" He then recalled his encounter at Silversilk Castle, which made him even more conscious of his feebleness.

Chapter 41: Entanglement (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The carriage slowly came to a stop in front of the Dolphin Antique Store.

Garen jumped out of the carriage and paid for the ride. He stepped in front of the antique store only to notice that the door was completely closed and that it was surprisingly quiet inside.

He raised his head to look at the store name and knocked on the door.

"Open the door Old man!"

"Coming! I'm coming!"

A seam appeared in the doorway as it cracked open. Old Man Gregor grabbed Garen as he forcefully dragged him in and immediately shut the door.

The store was oddly dark. Only a single oil lamp was lit on the table in front of the bookshelves. Under the dim yellow light, there was a brown and red colored miniature hourglass. The fine black sand slowly slid down through the slim aperture and its sound echoed.

Garen adjusted to the darkness within the room and glanced at the hourglass on the table.

"What’s this? Your new toy?"

The old man didn’t respond. He slowly strolled to the table and sat down. The dim light cast on his face highlighted his fatigued and aged expression.

"A friend gave me this black hourglass. It is used for tracking time and can measure a long period of time with every reset." He shook the hourglass with his hand. "I have already had this for two weeks and only one-fifth of the sand slid down. Don’t you think it is slow?"

"Indeed." Garen raised his eyebrows as he gazed at the old man’s aged appearance. "Are you alright, old man? You haven’t looked so well recently."

Garen took a chair and sat beside the table as he adjusted the light for the oil lamp. The room brightened up. "Maybe I am sick." Old Man Gregor smiled, and his perverse nature seemed to have faded. "Speak your mind, why did you make a trip down here? You usually don’t visit me when you are free."

"I am here to take care of the elderly. I am afraid that no one will take care of a lonely 80-year-old man." Garen laughed, "Oh, where are your children? Relatives? How come I’ve never seen them before?"

"Who knows?" The old man complained as a glimpse of despair flashed across his face. "Okay let’s talk about something else. What’s happening with you? You wouldn’t visit me if you didn’t have something on your mind."

"You know me too well." Garen saw the old man’s expression and knew the topic of children probably touched on the old man’s past sorrow. He changed the subject. "I am here to ask for advice on how to appraise antiques and jewelry. Since you have an antique store, you must be knowledgeable in the area?"

"This is simple!" The old man sat up straight and glanced at Garen. "But..." He extended his palm in front of Garen.

Pa!

Garen slapped a stack of cash into the old man’s hand.

The hand was still extended.

His face solemn, Garen added $1,000 more to the pile.

"Old man open your eyes, that’s $1,000 per stack!"

"I know it is $1,000 per stack, but it takes years of knowledge and experience to build a career in appraisal. My long history in this business would warrant a small cost." Old Man Gregor pocketed the $2,000 dollars with a pleased face.

"It’s only $2,000. I am going easy on you."

"Let me teach you about the basics about the appraisal." The old man cleared his throat. "Appraisal includes techniques in a few areas, the first being authenticity identification. The second is determining the age of the antique, the third is tracing the origin, and the fourth is understanding the value of the craftsmanship. All four areas would require an extensive amount of time to learn and practice. Which one do you want to learn first?"

"Can I learn all of them at the same time? I am confident in myself."

"Learn at the same time?" The old man looked at Garen under the light. He gazed blankly as his vision seemed to have blurred. "Learn all of them at the same time? Confident? It’s unfortunate, but you don’t have the talent," the old man said, murmuring the last sentence under his breath.

After Garen improved his physical status, his hearing was also augmented. He overheard the old man’s murmur, but didn’t seem to mind. Everyone had their own secrets and some chose to keep them private.

"Can I learn about authenticity identification first?"

"No problem." The old man suddenly seemed interested. He touched his lips as he opened the drawer below the table. He took out a stack of white paper and two quills and then wetted the tips with ink from a jar.

"Authenticity identification is the most difficult area to master in appraisal. It is dependent on the experience and time spent with antiques." He drew a circle on the white paper and marked the circle with a cross.

"Do you know what this is?" He pointed at the shape.

"No. A circle shaped window?" Garen attempted to guess the shape on the figure.

"It’s a unique symbol that belonged to a master jeweler from the Voyager Era. If you understand this symbol, then it would be possible to deduce the year, level, and category related to this crucial detail. If you don’t know, it would be impossible to identify anything meaningful."

Garen nodded his head deep in thought. "You are trying to tell me that for authenticity identification, it is not only about the craftsmanship details related to the antique. It is also necessary to use history and special background knowledge to be able to determine whether the antique is authentic or not."

"Hmm? You are pretty bright and quick to understand." The old man was about to state the key point, but Garen managed to guess it. He looked slightly surprised. "I was about to give you a counterfeit. It would be impossible to determine the authenticity without the unique symbol. But you are quick to realize the critical insight."

He paused. "Since you already understand, then you know that to identify authentic antiques you must be knowledgeable in history, craftsmanship from different eras, famous master craftsmen, genres, classifications, renowned case studies, manufacturing specifics, and production origins. A lot of times you must combine everything together to reach an accurate conclusion when appraising antiques and jewelry.

"So the first thing I need to do is to learn the background knowledge?" Garen nodded. "Are there any books?"

"There are, but books alone won’t help you that much. Take a look at them first, then I’ll teach you about my appraisal experiences and special techniques. Let’s do this step by step. A lot of things are not covered in the books. Other than by sight, you must also use smell, hear, touch and taste in appraisal. Only understanding the theories would be pointless without practical experience, but read the books first."

The old man dug through the bookshelf and found a white book. "This is ."

He then grabbed a thicker black book, "This is ."

He stacked the books together and pushed them in front of Garen.

"Take these home with you, then find me after you are done."

Garen stared at the two giant books speechlessly. "How long would it take for me to finish these two? It’s at least 1000 pages per book."

"No rush, take it slow, as long as you finish it within a month." The old man shook his hand. "Now get out of here. I need to clean up and sleep now."

Garen grabbed the two books. "Okay I’ll come and find you after I finish."

"Oh, hold on." The old man smacked his head. "You were asking about the other book last time, right? Since you seem to have fancied that book, I’ll give it to you as a small souvenir."

He dug in his pants and grabbed a small pendant. It was shaped like an open book.

"Here you go." He threw the pendant over.

Garen caught the pendant and began examining it. It was only the size of a fingernail. The pendant was delicately crafted with a pitch-black color. The opened book had a peculiar dark red symbol inside.

"What’s this?"

"It was a gift from when I bought the book. Just keep it for now." The old man scratched in his pants again as if he were itchy.

Garen quivered and stuffed the pendant into his pocket "Where did you find this? That’s disgusting. Ok, I’ll go now."

"Go on." The old man waved his hand with an irritated look.

Garen came out of the antique shop and waited for a carriage. After none were seen for 10 minutes due to the isolated location of the store, he had to walk toward Pennington street with his books.

When he passed by his uncle’s place, he looked up at his uncle’s window. He caught a glimpse of Lombarth hastily walking away from the window, leaving the window shaking. It felt like he was avoiding Garen.

Garen originally intended to visit his uncle, but he lost his interest when he saw that Lombarth was at home. After the conflict with Lombarth last time, Garen felt annoyed every time he saw his cousin’s face.

"This guy has been quiet lately." Garen had walked a few steps before he heard hasty footsteps behind him.

"Brother Garen!" A girl’s youthful voice echoed behind him.

Garen turned around and saw a young girl blushing as she ran towards him.

The girl wore a white cotton shirt along with a pair of white jeans. The jeans flawlessly traced her graceful and energetic figure. At the age of 14, she didn’t seem to have hit puberty.

The girl carried a light fragrance that only belonged to a teenage girl. Her short light red hair set an energetic vibe in the air.

"Brother Garen, you are already here. Why don’t you come up?" The girl was his uncle’s other child, Phelia. In contrast to Lombarth, Phelia always acted energetic around Garen. Because of this, Garen always enjoyed playing with younger kids.

"I didn’t see you, Phelia." Garen smiled as he gently pinched the girl’s nose. "Why did you cut your hair?"

"I am learning martial arts right now." The girl performed a rudimentary move.

"Where’s uncle?"

"He is hosting some visitors right now. They only talk about complicated subjects. It’s boring there. Can you come up and play with me?" Phelia shook Garen’s arm. "Next time, since Uncle is busy right now. It would be rude of me to interrupt."

"Also, my father was unhappy when he heard the news about the acceptance ceremony." Phelia lowered her voice. "My father said that he doesn’t want you to waste your time studying martial arts as long you learn enough to protect yourself. It would be a waste of time to put all your energy in it."

Garen raised his eyebrows. "I thought Uncle would be happy."

Chapter 42: Entanglement (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"My father said he wanted you to take care of the family business. He was always fond of you, even when you were young. As for Lombarth and I, we are not talented enough to manage the business. If you spend too much time in martial arts, you would fall behind in other areas. He would not object it if it was in the past, but now the times are different. Regardless of how skillful you are in martial arts, a couple of guns would be enough to take care of you," Phelia explained in her father’s tone.

"Uncle wants me to take care of the business?" Surprised by the comment, Garen questioned back, "How is that possible?"

"How is that not possible? My dad had already decided on this a long time ago. I don’t care. I’m bad at studying and not talented in martial arts. My teacher said I have no potential. If I can’t feed myself, I’m going to count on you!" Phelia hugged Garen’s arm as she acted pettishly toward him.

"My father said that among the children in the younger generation, only you could succeed his business to ensure that it remains prosperous. In the hands of Lombarth or me, we would ruin the business in a few years."

"My uncle has high expectations of me."

Garen was quite surprised. He had always felt that his uncle cared more for him than an uncle should--almost better than his own children. In his childhood memory, if Lombarth and Garen were ever in a conflict, Lombarth would, for sure, be punished. The favoritism shown was plain to see.

This caused Lombarth to hold a grudge against Garen. He was extremely unsatisfied by the preferential treatment Garen received.

"Let’s go, let’s go." Phelia dragged Garen by the arm.

He could not help but follow Phelia into the door. He had taken a few steps before a grim-looking, towering figure came out of the door along with a couple of strangers.

"Are you Garen?"

The teenage boy wore a tight, white shirt with a pair of black pants. The outfit proudly displayed his muscular appearance.

Garen stopped and glanced at the young boy. "You are?"

"I am Lombarth's cousin. I heard you’ve been bullying Lombarth with your martial arts? Is this true?" The young boy stared at Garen with a frown.

"What do you mean? I’ve been bullying Lombarth? Where have you heard this?" Garen wanted to step in the door, but the young boy intentional stepped in to block him. Garen winced. "That’s enough, I need to go in.""You are also part of the family. It would be inappropriate for a stranger to teach you a lesson. I’m here today to educate you for my cousin." The young boy forcefully blocked the entrance to the door.

Then, there was a conflict of interest. Due to their inability to manage the assets, the returns from his aunt’s family had decreased over the years, and with that, the center of attention shifted onto his uncle’s new business.

When his uncle first ventured out, he received an extensive amount of support from his wife’s family to grow the business. Her family was a critical factor in the success and expansion of the business.

However, his uncle, as the owner, now stated that he would pass the business to his sister’s son, what did this mean?

Garen quickly realized: It implied that his uncle thought all the youths from his wife’s family were incompetent when compared to Garen. Only Garen could ensure his business to thrive in the future.

Since the wife’s family invested a lot into the business when it was still in its initial stages, they already considered the business to be a part of their own. The unexpected statement about his sister’s son inheriting the business would displease her family with the decision.

Garen looked at the young boy in front of him and had an idea.

"It’s Lombarth's idea to come and find me right? Ok, enough of this game, don’t block the way. We can chat when we are inside."

The young boy laughed grimly and twisted his body as he blocked the way again. He put his arms in front of his chest and stared fiercely at Garen.

Garen frowned. "This is not what you guys think it is. We can chat about it when we are inside. Don’t get used by Lombarth. Don’t believe everything he says."

He didn’t want to start a conflict with the young boy and the group of strangers, for the size of his family was not to be underestimated. They were not saints and were intertwined with gang-related business. If he received a bad name from this conflict, it would become problematic later on.

"That’s not what Lombarth said." The young boy with a vicious look slid his body across the door as he obstructed Garen’s way.

"Are you going to get out or not?" Garen was losing his patience. He didn’t want to play fighting games with a young boy.

"What if I don’t get out?" The young boy didn’t back away.

Garen’s eyes turned icy as he extended his right arm out, aiming for the young boy’s neck.

Pa!

The young boy launched a side kick into Garen’s palm, generating a loud sound from the impact. Fine dust fell off where they collided. He immediately retreated his leg and performed a roundhouse kick, forming a circle. His foot targeted Garen’s wrist.

Pa!

His pants created a draft as it viciously skidded through the air from the kick. The young boy’s move was executed elegantly and smoothly. Both of the two kicks landed in the same location on Garen’s body. It was only after taking two steps back that he was able to stabilize himself.

"That’s all?" Garen stared at him, bewildered.

"You!"

The young boy’s face turned pale as a bead of sweat emerged from his forehead. It was clear that the last couple of moves were not easy to perform; however, when he saw that the opponent wasn’t even forced to budge, he already knew the difference between them.

Garen glanced at him impassively without even budging. He patted the dust off his palm and entered the wide, open entrance. His palm and wrist didn’t even turn red from colliding with the kicks.

"Don’t you dare to leave before you explain yourself today!" The young boy burst out hysterically. He dashed as he kicked straight at Garen's chin.

Garen’s face turned grim. He pushed his right hand forward as he redirected the young boy’s right leg. After that, he turned around instantly and kicked out behind him.

Peng!

Kacha.

The adult male behind Garen took a side kick to his body and collided with the wall behind the door. He was the young boy’s bodyguard. He had intended to attack from behind, but he didn’t expect Garen to turn around and perform a side kick. A couple of bystanders gasped at the forceful side kick that had directly slammed into the bodyguard.

The bodyguard’s entire body collided with the doorframe like a sandbag. The sound of bone fracturing was audibly clear. Just imagining the sound was painful. Everyone felt goosebumps shivering down their arms.

The bodyguard’s arm couldn’t feel a thing as the bones were shattered on collision. He couldn’t even stand up straight. The opponent’s power far exceeded his expectations! He leaned heavily against the door, trying to stand up without being able to do so. The way he looked at Garen changed drastically.

Garen, who stood across from him, glanced at him with an icy stare, his eyes displaying a boundless sea of emotionless cruelty.

The bodyguard suddenly felt frightened. He had seen a similar stare coming from his team leader before. He knew that if he made any movement...

"He will kill me." He froze in place and dared not to move.

The sudden change not only stunned the young boy motionlessly but also shocked Phelia, causing her to gape with her mouth wide open. No one moved.

Garen sneered. He knew that the conflict could not be resolved with just this. He walked in front of the young boy and pressed his finger against his forehead.

"Even your bodyguard is weak. No wonder uncle is passing the business to me. What’s the purpose of your existence if you are so useless? Go die in a ditch."

Pa.

His finger lightly pushed forward. The young boy’s head swayed backward as Garen left a red mark on his forehead.

In front of Garen’s killing intent, his pupils immediately contracted. At the very moment when Garen touched him, he felt as he was about to die.

"Don’t kill me!" He frighteningly burst out in a cry. He rolled and crawled backward to hide behind a large vase. His eyes were full of fear. Garen smiled and stood straight up; he knew that he had broke the young boy mentally. He would be the boy’s worst nightmare. Even if someone provoked the young boy, he would not dare to bother Garen anymore.

That was also his intention. The boy had yet to develop a mature metal state of mind. This situation was solved by simply scaring him.

Since the conflict couldn’t be resolved during the moment when the bodyguard tried launching a sneak attack, Garen was resolute and decisive in his actions; he went with the simplest solution that will solve it once and for all: destroying them mentally.

"Let’s go, Phelia." He turned his head to look at the girl beside the door. The girl’s lips trembled as she gazed at him. A glimpse of fear could be seen in her eyes.

When Garen pointed at the young boy’s forehead, she thought he would be killed.

She had only seen such viciousness coming from her father’s bodyguards.

When she heard Garen’s voice, she opened her mouth with a slightly hesitant voice.

"Brother Garen, his name is Delai Xima. He is a professional martial arts practitioner who had passed the amateur stage. His…"

"Don’t tell me that he is a godlike combat grandmaster?" Garen responded speechlessly.

"He is part of the gang?" Garen frowned.

Phelia nodded.

"He is the leader of the outer province gang."

"You know pretty well."

"I heard it from my elders during the holiday season. You have to be careful. This is not just a conflict between the younger generations," Phelia said worriedly.

"Don’t worry."

Garen nodded. With the Black Jade Disk in his possession now, he is growing stronger by the minute. Even now, standard pistols at a far distance would not be able to damage him; it is only with accurate shooting at close range that pistols would be able to threaten him.

"The conflict within the family has rules as well. Don’t worry too much, let’s go up and see uncle."

Garen moved his neck around as it made a crisp sound. The internal conflict within the family permits neither the usage of gang forces nor dishonorable tactics. Most of the competition is based on timing in an honorable fashion. Otherwise, it would not receive the support from the elders of the family.

He was not interested in his uncle’s business -- with his unique ability, he could easily develop his own business and it would only take time and energy; however, this was not his goal.

Only with his power would he be able to achieve what he desired.

"As long as they don’t cross the line, anything is negotiable." Garen licked his lips.

Chapter 43: The Way (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen followed Phelia to the fifth floor and discovered that the steel door by the staircase was opened, with a man in black suit and crew cut hair standing by the side. The man eyed Garen before asking, "You’re Garen, right? Your uncle is waiting for you at the study."

Garen nodded in return. He then changed his shoes, tidied his outfit and followed Phelia to the study after closing the door.

Fire crackled inside the chimney by the main hall, and the room was warm from the radiating heat. While passing the main hall, he spotted a girl with a red ponytail delicately sleeping on the couch in her white training robe.

Garen laid his eyes on her and paid special attention on her arms and thighs before continuing to the study.

There was a corridor between the study and the main hall, with sides filled with mirrors as clear as the sky. Garen stooped in front of the mirror and, from it, he saw his own reflection staring back at him.

Purplish-black short hair. Deep red eye sockets. Wearing a black t-shirt that barely covered his jam-packed body. With that slender figure of his, he couldn’t help but give off a robust temperament.

From the look of things, it was obvious that Garen had been spending time training. It was of great timing that it was during his puberty, causing him to look taller and stronger than before.

Without wasting any time, Garen pushed open the study’s redwood door. He saw two rows of bookshelves lying on each side of the wall, with a long blackwood table positioned in the center of the room.

An old man with white hair and his uncle were sitting beside the table enjoying their coffee, and the air was filled by the aroma of their drink.

Knock. Knock.

Garen stood still as he gently knocked on the door.

It couldn’t be more obvious that his uncle had been gaining some weight. His thick black eyebrows wrinkled up, and he seemed to be piling up in his seat caught up in his thoughts. He only turned his head towards the door when he heard Garen knocking.

"Ah, Garen, I almost thought that you had forgotten me after not visiting for so long! What have you been up to lately? Even Ying Er said that she hasn’t seen much of you recently. You’re not still training at that dojo, are you?" Garen’s uncle said while pointing at the seat across him. "Come take a seat, it’s been so long since we had a conversation between uncle and nephew."

Garen nodded and spent no time taking his seat. He gave a glance at the white-haired old man while sitting down. From his appearance, the old man must be at least seventy to eighty years old— he had white beard and white hair, and he was wearing a white robe.

But what really captured Garen’s attention was that, since the moment he set foot in this room, the old man had been eyeing him, seemingly troubled.

Turning his attention away from the old man, Garen sat up straight and looked at the direction of his uncle.

"Uncle, I heard that you wanted me to inherit your property. Is it true?" Garen asked, showing his concern.

"Of course it is true," Uncle Anjer answered as he arched his eyebrow. "This decision has been made since a long time ago."

He gently tapped his fingers on the table, letting out a rhythmic sound.

"How do I say this… How about this, I will tell you everything from the beginning. After all, I know that you are not the type of person that is interested in power or money. So, if I don’t make things clear for you, I’m afraid you might not want to accept my inheritance."

Garen was taken aback, not knowing how to reply. However, it was indeed what his uncle had said, he did not care about having power or money. Perhaps it was because he had an ability that made him ignore these types of possession, or perhaps there was some other reason. but it was definitely what his uncle had said, if things were not discussed clearly, he would’ve prepared to convince his uncle to drop this decision.

Uncle Anjer muttered to himself before speaking again, "You know the situation of my two children. It is certain that they cannot inherit the property. Be it Lombarth or Phelia, they are playful and immature. They might change in the future, but the chances of it happening is too slim."

"As for the youngsters from my wife’s line of family… They are too ambitious! Though I have to admit that they have some capability, but I am certain that if they inherit my property, there will be nothing left! What will happen to Phelia and Lombarth then? The efforts that I had put into building this business and network JUST to be handed to them freely? Impossible!"

Garen nodded.

Uncle Anjer took out a cigarette and lighted it before continuing, "I admit, this situation must have placed you in an awkward position. For this, I apologize. However, I really don’t want my legacy to be in the hands of someone else! I still have two kids! Yes, Phelia and Lombarth. Though Lombarth always makes me worry, but he is still my child, Garen."

He stared into Garen’s eyes intently.

"Since you were young, you showed an outstanding talent of handling a business, and only you can help me stabilize my inheritance. I know that you have never yearned for what I have in life, but think about Phelia. Even though Lombarth never managed to get along with you, but Phelia has always liked you, right? You liked her too, right? I can assure your engagement with her."

Garen was startled—he was almost speechless. He had never wanted to divert his attention on other paths, but, as of this moment, he didn’t know how to reject his uncle.

Moreover, looking into the current situation, it seemed like Uncle Anjer was at the end of his road—only forty years of age, yet he was already arranging his inheritance.

Uncle Anjer took a deep puff from his cigar. Not long after, white clouds starts gushing out from his nose.

"I know it is sudden, but I hope that you can consider this seriously." This time, he spoke as if he was speaking to another adult.

Garen nodded.

"If this is your wish, Uncle." Garen narrowed his eyes before continuing, "It’s just that would you mind telling me why are you in such a hurry in arranging this? You are still well in your middle age. Won’t it be too soon for you to worry about this?"

Uncle Anjer seemed less tense having known that his nephew did not reject him immediately. He took out a small scissor and clipped the cigar before holding it in his mouth. Then, he pointed at the old man.

"Naturally, I have my own reasons. Come, let me introduce you. This is my old friend, Adonis. He has been the guest of my house lately, and the one sleeping on the couch outside is his disciple, Winnie. You both practice martial arts, so I suppose you guys must have tons of common topics."

Garen frowned. "Uncle, you still haven’t told me the reason, maybe..." Before he could even finish his sentence, a loud thump echoed out as the study’s door was flung wide open.

The three turned their attention toward the door, only to find Lombarth breathing heavily at the side, staring at Garen ferociously.

"Garen! It’s you! It’s you again!"

Garen frowned again. He wanted to speak, yet he was interrupted once again.

"Get out!" Uncle Anjer shouted. He stood up as he pointed a finger to outside the door. "Can’t you see that we are having a conversation? Get out!"

Lombarth was about to speak, but after seeing the expression of his father, he unwillingly slammed the door and left.

While panting, Uncle Anjer sat down and angrily shoved the cigar into the ashtray.

"This Lombarth is getting out of hand! Please excuse me, I have to teach him a lesson. In the meantime, why don’t you two have a talk? You two should have some common topics since the both of you are martial artists. I am sure Adonis won’t mind giving you some advice, Garen."

He then stood up, coughed heavily, before going out from the study.

A click sound reverberated as the door was slowly closed.

Garen sat at his seat as he silently stared at the old man sitting opposite him. This old man had been eyeing him with a troubled expression since the moment he set foot in this room.

Their eyes met, yet not a single word was let out.

"Young man, your art has drifted from the right path." Finally, Adonis spoke.

"The right path?" Garen was dazed. Originally, he thought that this old man would tell him his relationship with his uncle, yet he actually decided to evaluate his art instead.

"To practice martial art is to practice mastering the heart. Your heart has been affected by your own strength," Adonis murmured. "When the convenience of the strength becomes more apparent, you will be more accustomed to it, to a point where you can never get rid of it. And, when you base your art with it, you will only find yourself being a puppet to it! Forever living only to practice martial arts to get stronger!"

The old man stood up, walked to the window and looked down.

"Did you think that you can get a sense of security just by increasing your strength?"

Garen shivered. He raised his head to the old man and asked, "What do you mean?"

"Don’t let your mind be distracted by strength. The strong will always be strong, and the weak will always be weak." Adonis shook his head and turned his direction toward to door. The door opened and closed, yet no sound was produced.

Garen sat at his seat, his expression uncertain.

Hoo-la!

He abruptly stood up, with his hands gently touching his chest. His muscles were as strong and as hard as a rock, yet the strength he had never gave him a peace of mind.

********************

Thump!

The blocker Garen held in his hand was being kicked hard. From where he stood, a cloud of dust spread out in all directions.

A series of blows were furiously struck on the same spot.

Thump! Thump! Thump! Thump! Thump!

In an instant, four sounds overlapped one another. Garen was slowly knocked back, and his hands were almost unable to keep the blocker stabilized.

Senior Sister Darcia slowly pulled in her fists, letting out a deep breath. Each side of her temples was blood red—a sign only a master in the White Cloud Dojo would show. Cooling down while pulling her fists, the color from her temples slowly faded.

"It’s your turn, junior." Darcia took the blocker off Garen’s hand. "It’s now your turn to attack."

"Okay." Garen nodded.

Both of them wore black robes, sparring on the second floor of the White Cloud Martial Colosseum.

Thump! Thump! Puff!

Like two specks of dust, they stood on the middle of the newly retiled brown-red floor. Each blow they traded, wisps of white dust proliferated around them. The sound of their feet screeching against the floor was enough to have someone clench their teeth.

Garen repeatedly jabbed and swung his fists towards Darcia, but each of his blows were precisely blocked by the latter.

Darcia seemed to be at ease, and her steps were as light as feathers. The white tiger tattoo that occasionally appeared while sparring seemed as if it was alive during vigorous movements. Her blood red temple, with the sharp eyes that seemed to be smiling, gave off an unusually attractive vibe.

After continuously sparring for two hundred times, Garen was finally out of breath. He stopped what he was doing, took a few steps back, and breathed heavily.

"Huff… Senior Sister, can I ask you a question?"

"It seems that you have something troubling you?" Darcia smirked while walking towards Garen.

Thump!

She landed a hard kick on Garen’s chest, sending him to stumble across the room.

"What you must do now is none other than sparring!" Darcia stood while looking at Garen in disdain. "Confusion, hesitation, indecisiveness, cowardice… Get it out of your head! You’re wasting your time if you still live in your past."

She raised her leg high off her chest—her posture was similar to a crazed elephant—and mercilessly landed it on Garen’s head.

Chapter 44: Direction (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Crack!

The wooden board snapped without effort.

Garen was finally able to roll to the side at the critical moment. He stood back up and solemnly stared at Rosetta.

"How can one strengthen one's mental fortitude, so he can act and achieve his goals subconsciously?"

Rosetta was surprised, then she started laughing as she shrugged her shoulders. "Don’t let the pursue of power blind your eyes and fool your heart. If you are strong, you are strong. If you are weak, then you are weak. Someone must have told you this theory, right?"

"How did you know?" Garen was stunned again.

"What kind of bullshit theory is that?" Rosetta sneered. "I can’t even count how many people I killed who believed it! So ignorant and so rigid! People who train using this trash theory will be trash afterward!"

She stretched her neck and flexed her lower body.

"Power is power! The more power you have, the stronger you are, and your mind and heart will be in turn cultivated by it! Invincible confidence is always the byproduct of invincible power!

"The strong minds were all created by the repetitive self-confirmation."

Garen paused a little. "So in other words, if I don’t doubt myself and believe that I’m always right, then my mind and heart shall behave the same way, right?"

"That’s right." The smile disappeared on Rosetta’s face. Her temples were getting so red that it looked like she was bleeding. "Next, I will add some more power so you can really understand the meaning of it."

"Damn!"

Garen felt a chill. He knew that his senior sister was about to lose it on him. If he countered her attack directly, he wouldn’t feel good afterward. Last time, if it hadn’t been for his second brother, he would have gotten his ass kicked so hard by her that he would have ended up in a hospital.

Without hesitation, Garen turned around and rushed away. It was his most practiced martial art style in the White Cloud Combat Arts, after all.

Bam!

He stomped his left foot and in two steps leaped toward the staircase. He then jumped down it without looking back.

He suddenly heard a subtle air-piercing sound. A hand slowly touched him on the left shoulder. Its movement didn’t make any sound. The hand seemed like it belonged to his lover, the movement very soft and gentle.

Garen, on the other hand, was very anxious. He struck his elbow backward, and his arm shot out like an arrow, the elbow being the sharp arrowhead.

This Shot Form was the form in the Four Forms that caused the most damage to the body, and it was the form that had the fastest speed and the highest burst power. With the help of special strength utilization techniques, any part of the body could be trained to burst out with power akin to a released arrow.

At this point, Garen was only able to train one part of his body - his right elbow.

Pia!

His elbow strike was easily blocked.

Garen stomped his feet, and his body continued dropping toward the bottom of the staircase. His speed was a bit faster than usual. He was using his hidden strength, after all.

The White Cloud Secret Arts that he was mastering were slowly increasing his strength on a daily basis. Although he was at the peak of an adult’s strength’s threshold, his strength was still increasing at a steady pace. It had no sign of slowing down.

With this small differential in speed, Garen finally escaped the death chase by his senior sister. He firmly landed on the stairway on the first floor.

In the morning, there were quite a few disciples who were coming and going from the grand hall on the first floor. They all recognized Garen as the Dojo Master’s new disciple, who just joined the Dojo not long ago, when they saw him jumping off the second floor.

"Senior sister goes by the rule of zero combat under the second floor. I’m lucky that I got down in time." Garen wiped the sweat from his forehand as he calmed himself down. "The senior sister is the most dangerous practice opponent, but she did train my reflexes and reaction time. If I don’t stay cautious all the time, I will for sure be going to the hospital."

By now, he had realized the mysteriousness of White Cloud Dojo. His master Fei Baiyun wasn’t around most of the time, and Garen had no idea what he was doing. Besides that, from the way his senior sister spoke and her self-told stories, he could tell that she was a horror figure who’d killed a lot of people.

His second brother was actually a senior member at the Confederation’s Combat Association, and he was one of the examiners for the advancement in the Hobbyist Levels. Garen heard that he also ran some underground businesses. So he was definitely a successful man by all appearances.

In terms of his third brother, he was the very definition of a kid from a wealthy and politically influential family. His father was the Chief Inspector at Huaishan City. This position was created by the Confederation to inspect all the government officials of the municipal level. It was on the same level as the Mayor, which made his third brother’s father one of the two most influential people at Huaishan City. On top of that, his mother was the daughter of a Count, who was very well off.

A few days ago, during practice, Garen’s third brother somehow irritated senior sister and got beaten so hard that he had to go home to rest.

Garen thought his own defense was tough and agreed to practice with senior sister without doing any research. But unexpectedly, after only getting hit a few times by her palms, he noticed that the injured places on his body had already swollen up.

After fixing up his clothes, Garen called two people working at the Dojo. He asked them where his master and second brother had gone. But as expected, they didn’t know at all.

Garen drank some hot water and cleaned the sweat off of his body. He decided to wander around the Dojo, wanting to rest a little bit since he had the time.

His body was getting stronger and stronger. The shape of his muscles was getting harder to cover up by his uniform.

When he was walking around the field and such, other disciples of the Dojo greeted and saluted him.

"Ha! He!"

In the middle of the field, there were three groups of disciples who were practicing White Cloud Combat Arts together. These were the core disciples who were picked from the individual branches. They were all in white uniforms and were very focused on the training.

Garen was relaxing his body wandering around as he checked his Potential Meter, 155%.

"It has been more than a week since I went to the uncle’s place. Now I have another potential point that I can utilize. I have to decide carefully on where I want to allocate it."

He wasn’t planning to use it on any technique. It would be a huge waste to squander it on an ordinary one. It would only make sense if the technique was very hard to master. But at the moment, he couldn’t add the point to White Cloud Secret Arts nor the Explosive Fist Arts. Thus, the potential point was better spent on his own attributes.

Since White Cloud Combat Arts were the most essential foundation, Garen planned to completely understand and practice it form by form, and not use any potential points to jack the level up. He wanted to see if there were any differences between the techniques that he practiced to level and the techniques that he used the potential points to level up.

He quickly skimmed through his attribute pane.

Strength 2.12, Agility 1.10, Vitality 1.35, Intelligence 1.5

"Long term exercises have increased my vitality by 0.01. My strength has also increased under the effect of White Cloud Secret Arts. However, I feel like 2.2 is the absolute maximum amount of strength that I can reach."

Garen had a feeling. An intuition sent to his brain by his body.

It was reaching the ultimate strength threshold, and even White Cloud Secret Arts couldn’t increase it anymore. This ultimate threshold was the congenital physical limit; everyone had their own.

"Looks like 2.2 strength is my limit. I’m a bit weaker compared to second brother. Second brother’s strength is about 450 pounds, which is an equivalent of 2.25 in terms of attribute points. His congenital physical limit might be higher than mine, but I heard that his strength has not increased in a long time. Could it be that 450 pounds is the peak strength for all humans?"

Garen thought to himself.

"I should do some research on my own."

And he did exactly that. He turned around and went to the library in the Dojo.

The strong, bald elder was still sitting in front of it. His eyes were closed as he sat cross-legged.

Garen thought of something and walked up to the elder. "Big master Bai, can I ask you a question?"

After a solid four to five minutes, the elder opened his eyes. "Go ahead."

"What’s the peak strength for humans?" Garen asked quietly.

"Peak strength?" The elder thought about it and said, "In terms of measuring we use here, it should be around 480 pounds. This is the best record in the industry. But since each person has a different potential, we all stop at our own limit despite how hard we train."

"Then, where do you think my limit lies?" Garen asked, pointing at himself.

"You?" Big Master Bai carefully observed Garen. "I think your peak strength is somewhere between 430 pounds and 450 pounds."

"So accurate!" Garen was surprised. It was fortunate that his body grew a lot since he mastered White Cloud Secret Arts, and he was able to hide some of his strength well. Otherwise, this elder might have seen through him.

After his body changed, his strength instantly reached the limit, and his skin’s defense got a lot better as well. It was one time better than the elementary Explosive Fist Arts. Without hundreds of pounds of strength, no one would able to pierce through his skin with a knife.

"Thank you for your time." Garen bowed and showed his respect. He turned around and left after he saw the elder close his eyes.

"Then looks like 2.40 is my absolute peak for strength. If I add the potential points to it, it should increase by 0.3, which is like 60 pounds of strength. But I’m not sure if my limit will be stretched after it is reached."

Garen was very unsure. If he wasn’t able to stretch out his limits, then it will put a hard cap on his future potential.

But if his limit was stretched and topped, then his future potential would be limitless!

"Maybe I should try."

His eyes landed on the strength attribute.

The attribute slowly jumped up. It went from 2.12 directly to 2.20. Suddenly, Garen’s whole body became numb. It was if all the muscles in his body begun beating in a rhythm, one identical to the rhythm of the beating of his heart.

He felt that his temples were beating the fastest, as if some things were about to jump out of them.

This condition only lasted for about a dozen seconds. Garen looked at his attibute pane after it stopped, and his strength had increased to 2.20. It didn’t go above it, but a new symbol appeared behind it.

He knew what it was by just looking at it once.

"So my vitality couldn’t handle too much strength? Looks like I have to increase my vitality at the same time."

The remaining 0.22 of the potential point that were left after the majority of it was used for increasing strength were allocated to vitality.

The attribute for vitality instantly jumped from 1.35 to 1.57.

After adding the potential points to vitality, Garen felt something warm inside his body, as if there was a furnace that continuously baked his internal organs. He could even vaguely hear the ‘Ziz’ sound that his flesh and blood made.

The flow of the blood, the beat of the heart—Garen felt an additional feeling on top of those feelings including the compressing of his lungs due to breathing. It was an unprecedented control over his own body.

Pia!

After a light noise, Garen was surprised to see the Explosive Fist Arts that were on the elementary level jump to the intermediate level in his technique pane. Another aggressive swelling started within his body.

Garen almost couldn’t stand and walk normally. He could barely keep himself from falling by leaning against the wall. It was fortunate that no one was around to see him like this.

He felt that a layer of invisible liquid was slowly secreting within his body. It came from his internal organs, travelled through the bones, muscles, skin and covered the entire surface of his body.

Chapter 45: Encounter (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen fisted his hands as he leaned against the wall. He felt that his skin was getting thicker, as if a layer of hard substance was put over his body, just like when he first reached the elementary level on the Explosive Fist Arts.

"Such a strong change."

He stood up straight and felt that his body was much heavier. No, a better word for it would be firmer.

"The elementary level of Explosive Fist Arts only offered increased defense, but if I remember correctly, the intermediate level should offer the vibration effect. I have to carefully test it."

He didn’t stop and went directly to the test rooms at the back of the field. He looked around and picked one without anyone inside. He carefully locked it from the inside just to be sure no one would be looking.

He walked up to the wooden weapon rack and picked up a curved knife.

Thud!

He stabbed the knife into his left arm. It didn’t pierce through the skin, stopping at the surface as if it had hit a very hard wooden surface.

Garen slowly applied more and more force onto the knife. The strength applied to the knife instantly went over 50 pounds, then slowly 100, 150, 160, 170…

Psiii!

After a slight noise, the tip of the knife went through his skin, and Garen immediately stopped applying the force. He looked at the point on his skin that the knife had pierced.

There was a very little red dot on his skin, and a tiny bit of blood was slowly flowing out of it. However, it quickly solidified, as if it was an injury that a needle left behind.

After placing the knife back in the weapon rack, Garen pinched the part of his left arm that got stabbed.

"170 pounds of endurance and defense. That means that as long as my opponent’s strike with a sharp weapon has less impact than this, I won’t get injured. But if the weapon is dull, then it’ll be much easier to defend against. I think even 200 pounds of strength with such a weapon won’t injure me at all."

He rubbed his hands together, and they made a vague rustling noise, as if his hands were two rough metal plates.

"The martial arts at the White Cloud Dojo are very impressive. They must be on the same level as the Shaolin technique: Golden Bell Cover and Iron Shirt.

"I will specifically test my punches next."

Garen slowly walked up to a black sand punch bag that was hanging off of a rack. He lowered his back and swung his arm, throwing out a side punch.

Bam!

The punch bag swung around, not flying out too much. However, both the punch bag and the rack holding it up shook violently like there was an earthquake. For a time they vibrated aggressively, making buzzing noises.

Garen drew back his arm and punched straight this time. The fist shot out like an arrow and hit the punch bag right in the center.

Boom!

Bang!

The punch bag swung backward and fell to the ground with the rack. The dust on the floor was sent into the air, and Garen quickly covered his mouth and nose as he coughed.

After a while, the dust gradually calmed and settled back on the ground. Garen squatted down and made some careful observations.

The rack was made of metal. It was painted black and was nailed to the ground by long iron nails. Its bottom formed an shape to secure it against impacts from all angles.

Right now, all the hard iron nails were perfectly pulled out of the floor without any sign of damage on them.

Garen picked up an iron nail that was about the length of the index finger and looked at the others as well.

"Is it because of vibration? Apparently, it has this effect on nails, I wonder what kind of effect it would have on humans?"

He stood up as he thought about it and stretched out his arms and chest by swinging his arms horizontally backward. The jacked muscles on his back were compressed and bumped against each other as he moved his arms. It felt like there were strands of iron chains twisting and intervening with each other under his skin.

Si…

Hu...

He took a deep breath as he closed his eyes and recalled the moment when he punched out.

"It’s a vibration… A strong vibration."

He threw out a punch into the air, using the Shot Form.

After he punched out, there was a vague whistling sound.

"The strength would cause vibrations after it’s used, and transfer a huge vibration in the opponent. This type of attack would deal a great amount of damage to living creatures’ internal organs. I have to find an opportunity to test it out since I’m still not sure where exactly I stand in terms of combat abilities."

Garen drew back his fist and stood up straight. He stretched his neck and looked at his well built upper body. It was at that moment that he realized that he had turned from a weak teenager to a tough, muscled man.

"This change is really significant when considering that only a few months have passed by." He pulled on the button of his shirt, trying to cover up his chest muscles.ł However, it was impossible. He helplessly resigned the effort.

"I can’t really use my full strength when I’m practicing with senior sister and brothers in the Dojo. It seems like I’ll have to find other alternatives if I really want to test my real combat abilities. Now, that the situation at the Golden Hoop, Silversilk Castle, and with uncle are all mixed together, it’s very chaotic.

"I don’t have to worry too much about the situation with uncle. However, the Golden Hoop will soon find out that I had killed that Number 102, and they will certainly come for me again. It will be a great time to see what I'm made of." Garen bumped his fists together as he thought, "Next, I will just have to keep a close eye on Grace."

Garen shook his head after looking at the sand punch bag on the floor again. He turned around and walked out.

************************

Four days later…

Back at his home on Bluetree Street.

"Brother, I’m going with my classmates to Jaderipple Lake tomorrow. Do you want to come?" Ying Er’s voice came from next door.

"Jaderipple Lake again? Who’s going?"

Garen was thinking about the progression on Dale Quicksilver’s case. He was surprised by his sister’s sudden question.

"After doing so much and thinking about so much external work, I almost forgot that I’m only a high school student…" he thought to himself.

"Just my classmates, and a few of my best friends from junior high school. We are planning to have a grand barbecue at the lake," Ying Er answered as she combed her hair in the bathroom.

"What about dad and mom?"

"They said that they’re going to a dinner party, a celebration party put on by their company. They told us to solve our own problems and eat by ourselves."

"Again…" Garen shook his head. He had nothing to say. It was something that was no surprise to him.

He sat in front of his desk and started to work on the math questions that he had from school for the break. Temporarily, he threw everything that wasn't related to his student career to the back of his mind and focused on solving the math problems.

"Brother, are you going or not?" Ying Er peeked her head into Garen’s room.

"It’s ok. You guys have fun, I’m not going to go," Garen answered casually. "I’m busy with stuff."

"Suit yourself then. Peel your own almonds that are on the table in the living room. I’m going out. I have to prepare all the stuff that I need." Ying Er humphed at Garen as she left his room. She also intentionally stomped heavily with her feet on the floor and made loud stepping noises.

Bam!

Soon, Garen heard the sound of the closing door. Ying Er had intentionally slammed the door, too.

Garen shook his head as he sat in front of his desk. "So childish at that kind of age. She is still like an elementary school kid," he thought. Then he immediately went back to doing his homework. After a full hour and a half, he sighed as he raised his head.

"Although math is easy, there are just way too many questions. Looks like I have to spend some more time on it if I want to finish everything in one sitting."

Garen closed his practice question booklet that he completed and stood up to rub his lower back. He looked at the clock on the wall, and it was 9:43 AM.

"It’s about time to go."

After quickly changing into a T-shirt and a pair of jeans, he grabbed some money and a handful of almonds from the living room table, and walked out of his home.

He quickly went down the stairs. But as he was about to get to the end of the staircase, he saw a white-haired elder slowly walking down the stairs in front of him. Garen slowed down and didn’t pass him.

The elder was wearing a delicate, clean black suit along with a black round hat, and held a reddish brown cane in his hand. He was walking down the stairs one stair at a time. He seemed to hear the noise coming from his back and turned around to look at Garen with an apologetic smile on his face.

"After you."

Garen recognized this elder as the one who lived in this building. He saw him on a regular basis when using the stairs.

He smiled back and politely said, "Please be careful, and watch your steps. Don’t injure yourself."

"I’m in no hurry, just coming out to exercise a little." The elder smiled as he watched Garen walk past him. The smile on his face got brighter and brighter. "I’ve seen this little guy many times. He is polite every time I see him. This is rare to see nowadays."

Garen felt like the way the elder was looking at him was very strange. He paced himself as he felt a little uncomfortable. After he left the residential area, he walked down Bluetree Street toward the downtown.

He saw ox carts passing regularly on the road. All were carrying bricks and wood. He could see piles of black ox feces on the corner of the road, and they smelled really bad.

The human and car traffic on the streets was getting denser and denser as he got closer to downtown. Some of the perfume fragrance coming from off from passing girls and wealthy women who walked past Garen at the cross section covered up the smell of the oxes’ feces.

When he walked past a street that was full of stores selling clothes and accessories for women, he saw two familiar figures walking out of a jewelry shop on his left. It was Kalidor and Ai Fei.

They were holding onto each other’s hands, and Ai Fei leaned against Kalidor like a little bird resting on its owner. Both of them were wearing their school uniforms. Ai Fei’s was a dark purple dress, the bottom of which barely covered up her thighs. She also had some makeup on and looked even prettier than usual.

Both of them saw Garen, who was walking by as well, and were surprised.

"Garen, it’s you! Such a coincidence to meet on this street," Kalidor greeted with a smile. He subconsciously coiled his arm around Ai Fei’s waist as he saw Garen who was stronger, bigger and more handsome than him.

Garen smiled back and nodded as he glanced at Ai Fei. "You guys are out shopping? Yeah, it is such coincidence. Did you guys just get here?"

"We’ve been here for a while already." Kalidor chatted with Garen casually, but his arm subconsciously tightened its grip on Ai Fei’s waist.

Ai Fei looked at Garen who had changed a lot in the last couple of months. Although she had a slight smile on her face, she felt a little miserable. This great boy in front of her had shown interest in her, hinted that he did like her.

But after comparing Kalidor with Garen right now, Kalidor was no match with Garen in terms of appearance. In terms of height, Garen was literally looking down at Kalidor. There were also looks, figure, style, and temperament differences.

"Ai Fei, say hi to Garen."

She heard Kalidor’s voice, and that brought her back to reality. She quickly nodded at Garen and said, "Long time no see, Garen. How are you doing?" Looking at the tall and handsome man in front of her, the scene of them being deskmates appeared in her head.

But as she finished asking the question, Kalidor, who was beside her, suddenly reached his hand under her dress and started rubbing.

Ai Fei kept on smiling innocently, but her body stiffened as she felt Kalidor’s hand. She knew that Garen must have seen it. One of Kalidor’s hands was recklessly rubbing her bottom, and the other one reached out for her chest. It was formed into different shapes under Kalidor’s forceful fingers.

Ai Fei instantly felt like her body was getting hot, and her face burned. She saw Garen’s slight frown. At that moment, she felt like she was degraded.

This was in public, on a street with a lot of foot traffic in downtown. Kalidor had recklessly reached into her dress and dared to make it obvious!

She didn’t dare to resist. She knew what Kalidor was like. He was doing such a thing to directly tell Garen that she belonged to him. His temper wasn’t that good if emotions were involved.

If she resisted, she knew that it would be over between Kalidor and her.

At that moment, she felt like a whore. She had been trying to maintain her image one second, but was completely exposed the next. She could feel Garen’s stare, and the looks of other pedestrians on the street. She could feel them clearly! This unprecedented shame and embarrassment made her body shiver uncontrollably.

Chapter 46: Encounter (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen scrunched his eyebrows. Kalidor was not trying to hide anything from him, and Garen knew he put a lot of pressure on Kalidor. Ai Fei lowered her head, and she was scared to face Garen. Many thoughts ran through Garen’s mind, but he knew their relationship had ended.

"I still have something to take care of. Have fun, " Garen said.

"Garen, you’re alone, right? Why don’t you join us?" Kalidor got what he wanted, and he stared at Garen with a slight smile on his face. He patted Ai Fei’s butt with his hand, and it looked like he was trying to show his dominance.

"Sorry, I have to go. I will talk to you later." Garen was a bit annoyed, and he hurriedly left the place.

Leaving the two behind, he turned to a street, and a red car slowly stopped before Garen. From inside, Grace opened the door and got off the driving seat.

"Garen, sorry for being late," she said. Grace wore a black suit with a white shirt inside. Her skinny legs were covered with a pair of black stockings, and her long brown hair was silky smooth. She looked cool and pretty with her hair trailed over her shoulders. Grace stood beside Garen, and with both of them having red pupils, they looked unusually like a couple.

"No worries, I’ve also just arrived." Garen looked around, and he barely saw any pedestrians. There were several children playing at the side of the street, and it looked like they were playing hide-and-seek.

"How’s the recent situation?" Garen asked.

"Nothing happened." Grace lowered her head and respectfully answered. She looked like a secretary standing beside her boss.

"They probably knew who I was working for. It’s probably not a wise idea for us to meet in public like this. They will notice," she continued.

"It’s fine. They will eventually know sooner or later. Actually, I wanted them to notice. I wanted to communicate with the Golden Hoop anyways," Garen said with a light tone as he rested his back on the car door.

"I am not alone," he added.

"Also, once they try to communicate with us, I can use ‘Kelly’ as a cover to get in touch with Quicksilver. If they are not trying to avenge their members, they are probably trying to cooperate with me. Don’t worry, even if they come to us, we will not be in danger. The Golden Hoop has been around for a while, and they should know how to approach an unknown opponent. Just carry a gun in case you have to fight," Garen said.

"Got it."

Grace felt like the words he spoke were not from a 16 years old high school student. She thought she was talking to a 30 or 40 years old man, and she had mixed feeling about this.

"Am I talking to a genius?" Grace thought. She was an ordinary girl, and she trained very hard since she was young. Working for a gifted 16 years old teenager left a bitter taste in her mouth.

"What? Get on the car and drive me to the antique shop. Pick me up at 4 p.m. and take me to the dojo after. Don’t screw around, okay?" Garen said.

"I know!" Grace was a bit speechless; she felt like she was the teenager, and Garen was the adult here.

"I have a gun!" she added.

"I know. I know." Garen brushed her off and got into the car. Grace did not know what else she could say, but she remembered how useless her pistol was when Garen jumped on her like a violent leopard, and she felt secured when she was with Garen.

"You should change your expression from time to time. You are young and cute, so why don’t you at least try to smile?" Garen asked. He sat on the passenger seat and relaxed.

"Now try it, smile," Garen said.

Grace tried her best to smile, but she was not even sure if she was actually smiling.

"Never mind. My bad." Garen buried his face into one of his hands.

Grace took a deep breath and told herself not to get angry, but she really wanted to kick Garen in the face. She started the car, and they disappeared by the corner.

Kalidor and Ai Fei walked out of a fast food restaurant by the side, and he pouted his lips towards the direction where Garen disappeared.

"You saw that? Garen never shows anything off. No one knew he had such a pretty lady with him, and he also had a nice car. Damn… That’s a million-dollar car," Kalidor said. He was a bit jealous; his parents would never give him money to buy such a car. He also saw how the cool beauty followed all of Garen’s orders.

Kalidor turned back and looked at Ai Fei. She wasn’t as pretty as the lady that was with Garen, causing anger to boil inside him.

PA!

Kalidor slapped Ai Fei’s behind.

"Hurry up! Let’s go home!" He was almost yelling.

Ai Fei did not say anything. She just followed Kalidor from behind. Kalidor’s temper was getting worse and worse after he argued with his friends. Ai Fei thought she was attractive enough to Kalidor, but she was not sure about that anymore.

Ai Fei watched Garen and the lady leaving as she felt a lost. She was unsure whether she made the right choice, and she was also unsure whether all her efforts were worth it. She followed Kalidor down the street and disappeared by the corner.

********************

It was night.

Garen sat in the car and Grace was driving. Silence filled the air, and the light from the streetlights brushed their faces in light. Their pace was slow, and even the carriages were faster than they.

As they drove into a relatively quiet street, someone suddenly appeared in the middle of the way and blocked their path.

"Someone is in front of us!" Grace said in a deep tone.

"It’s one of them…" Garen opened his eyes and looked ahead through the window. There was a man standing in the middle of the road, and he looked thin. The man was wearing a grey-white coat, and his hair was short; he looked like a private detective. Grace stopped the car three meters before hitting him.

Garen opened the door and got off the car. After asking Grace to stay put inside the car, he walked straight towards the man. He noticed the golden earring on the man’s right ear, and it looked the same as the one No.102 had, but the man covered the number with a piece of white cloth.

"Were you the one that killed No.102?" The man spoke first.

"I am here to represent the Golden Hoop, and I hope we can have a chat," he said. His voice was dry, and it sounded like he had not drank water for a long time.

"What? I killed one of your members and you are just trying to have a chat with me?" Garen asked; he was surprised the man did not try to start a fight.

"Well, you can compensate us in a different way, I believe. We have no intention of making our relationship worse, and we already investigated the incident that happened in the Dolphin Antiques. It was our mistake." He raised his hand and apologized.

"Also, we believe that you and the detective are not good friends, since he left you behind at the Silversilk Castle," the man continued.

"True. There’s no point in fighting each other," Garen said as he nodded.

"I come in peace. We don’t really care about what happened before." The man straightened his back and clapped.

PAPA!

Several strong men walked out of the alley after hearing the signal. All of them had daggers or swords in their hands, and they were all laughing. Those men quickly surrounded Garen and his car.

"You can call me No.101. Although the organization asked me not to hurt you, No.102 was my best friend, and I decided to do a private test on you. I want to check if you are good enough for us to cooperate with you. Also, I want to know how you killed No.102." The man in coat smiled.

"Ah!" Garen heard Grace’s scream from the car.

Garen saw that Grace was seized by two strong men, and they were moving towards the river. The other side of the river was apartment buildings, and the embankment was grey.

"What do you want?" Garen said in a cold tone as his eyes narrowed.

"I told you already. It’s just a test," No.101 said while smiling.

"I don’t like being tested like this," Garen turned around as he spoke in a light tone.

Grace screamed again as she reached the edge of the embankment; she was just one step away from falling to the river. Garen turned back and rushed towards Grace, but No.101 blocked his path.

"Move aside," Garen said.

"We will kill your girl if you fail the test, but you have to hurry. I am not sure how long they will keep her by the edge. A weak girl like her won’t be able to handle the pressure for too long,"

No.101 smiled and said. He clapped again, and one of the men walked towards Grace with a dagger in his hand. He put down the dagger by a Sand Gull and slashed the air with his hand while laughing cruelly.

"Do what I say, otherwise, we will have to kill your beautiful girlfriend." No.101 laughed.

"I take it that the Golden Hoop doesn’t really care about me," Garen said and laughed.

"I thought you guys were smarter than this. I guess I am too naive," he continued.

"Don’t worry, Grace. I will avenge you if they decided to kill you," Garen said as he looked at Grace with eyes half-opened.

PONG!

Once these words were spoken, Garen suddenly attempted to seize No.101. His arm size doubled as he used the Strike Stance; it sounded like the air was slashed open. The veins on his hands were visible, and they seemed as big as an adult’s head.

"Die!" The muscles on Garen’s back moved towards his right arm like waves.

Chapter 47: White Eagle (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The ferocious force brought up a burst of wind. Before Garen’s arm connected, the strong pressure from the move already squeezed the air out of No.101.

Garen’s right arm seemingly grew a few inches as it swelled up. Like a mace, it crashed past.

Chi!

His claw slid past No.101’s face.

No.101 snickered. He easily avoided this attack with a side movement.

"An attack with this speed, are you joking around with a kid?"

Garen withdrew his hand as his arm returned back to its original form. He stayed put and calmly stared past No.101.

On the edge of the embankment, the man who was holding a small blade slumped to the ground. Fresh blood slowly flowed out of his forehead, and a pendant in the shape of a book fell on top of his clothes.

"You bastard...!!" No.101’s face darkened as he retracted his vision. "I guess I have no choice but to break the rules this time…"

He abruptly teared off his trench coat and threw it away, exposing the black vest underneath as well as his well-defined muscle lines.

With one hand vertically in front, and with the other hand’s palm facing outwards, he slouched his back. He exhibited a strange style of combat pose.

"Oh? You practice martial arts too?" Garen expressed his surprise as he watched his opponent position himself. He noticed that his vertically erect right hand had an abnormal skin color—a faint copper red.

Bang! Bang!!

Suddenly, the sound of two gunshots came from the neighboring road. It was especially piercing to the ears on this quiet street at night.

No.101, after hearing the gunshot, peeked at his right. The expression on his face immediately changed, and he quickly relaxed his combat pose.

"Something’s happening! Everyone, retreat!!"

The other strong men who surrounded Garen became nervous as well. One by one, they put back their knives and other weapons as they ran towards the neighboring road. They quickly disappeared in the little alleys.

No.101 coldly glared at Garen for one last time.

"I will come back for you."

He tipped his toes, picked up his trench coat, and swiftly disappeared into the alley like a shadowless grey bat.

Frowning, Garen watched the group of people depart before proceeding to relax his muscles.

"It’s a shame that my speed is too slow. I could have gotten an opportunity to make a person stay this time."

He pulled up his collar and quickly walked to the edge of the embankment.

Clap.

He grabbed Grace’s right hand, slowly lifted her up, then gently placed her onto the ground.

"Are you okay?"

"I’m fine. Thankfully, you scared off that group of people, or else we really would’ve gotten in big trouble." Grace was still shaken up. She glanced at the dead Golden Hoop member on the ground.

"I cannot believe that the Golden Hoop would try to make a move on me! I am my company’s upper management! Master Garen, please excuse me for a minute. I have to go back and report this incident to the headquarters!" Grace’s face turned cold.

"Even though Manuyllton Corporation is not as great as the Golden Hoop, but we are not pushovers either!"

"Alright, you should go." Garen nodded. "I have to go see what is actually going on. Just now, something lured them away. Be careful by yourself. It would be best if you arrange some people to protect you. What happened to your gun?"

Grace blushed. "Before I could get it out, I was attacked and grabbed from the back…"

"Be careful, I’ll go find out what's going on." Garen couldn’t help but laugh a little. "What happened to that aggressiveness from when we first met?" As if she was a child, Garen stroked her hair and pinched her cheeks. Then, he picked up the pendant and walked towards the dark alley.

Even without the transformation of his body, Garen was already more than 170 cm; his natural height made him taller than Grace by a little bit. The way he treated Grace seemed very natural, and both of them completely forgot about their actual ages.

Grace stood still and bit her lips as her cheeks turned even redder.

"I told you! Don’t treat me like I’m a child!" She quickly squeezed into her car and took out her gun from her purse. She then turned on the engine and drove towards the company.

****************

Garen walked along the sidewalk into the alley. Very soon, he heard sounds of fists pounding. Between each punch, someone whimpered and moaned.

"Catch him! Don’t let him get away!"

"Carlo passed out! Goddammit, this guy’s punches are strong!"

"Be careful of the gap! Don’t give him any opportunity!"

A group of men shouted at each other; it seemed like they were trying to attack someone.

Garen stood in the shadows at end of the alley and looked in.

On the muddy road, a group of men from the Golden Hoop Organization surrounded two skinny youths. No.101 stood outside of the circle and watched the fight with a cold expression on his face. He remained alert of any noises around him.

On the ground were three to four adult men, all of whom seemed to have passed out from being punched in the head.

Garen gasped as he estimated the extent of the injuries these members received.

"This level of strength is similar to the amount I used when I first killed someone! Could it be that all these casualties were caused by these two children?"

He moved his gaze onto the two youths.

One was a boy, and the other was a girl. The boy was handsome, and the girl appeared innocent. They were only around 15 to 16 years old, similar to Garen. However, from the looks on their face, it was obvious that this was not the first dangerous situation they ran into.

The two of them wore white sportswear. Their backs were against each other, and their stances in proper boxing stance.

"My father will be here to save me soon!" The boy sneered out of his teeth. "He won't let you off easy!"

"Don’t talk too much! Save some strength!" the girl said in a quiet tone. On her waist, a black gun was tucked away.

No.101 chuckled and speedily walked forward.

"Let me do the rest. You guys make sure he doesn’t run away. This fella here is the White Eagle’s son. We finally captured him after much work; we cannot let our effort go to waste."

He marched inside the circle and stood still. One hand vertically shot up as the other hand’s palm faced outside. Then he slouched. He positioned himself in the same stance as before.

Faintly, Garen noticed that his right hand turned even redder than before. It was as if his blood was congested, and his veins would pop at any second.

"Kid, I cannot believe you dare to fight me. You’re courting death! If any part of your body ends up paralyzed, don’t blame me."

"Cut the crap! Make your move!"

The young boy’s body remained straight as he interrupted his opponent.

Before he could finish talking, there was a snipping sound.

A red shadow dashed across his chest. and his white uniform was silently sliced open. A red slash ripped across his wheat-colored skin as blood started to spew.

After the red shadow faded, it reversed back as No.101’s hand knife.

The boy’s face whitened. When the red shadow dashed across just now, he sucked in air to tighten his chest. If he had reacted any slower, the knife would’ve cut open his stomach. However, because he inhaled too much oxygen too fast, he was having some difficulties breathing. His lungs felt like they were tearing apart.

"Silvica! Are you okay?" the girl asked in a panic. "Please be careful! He practices Red Hand Fist!"

"I’m okay. I dodged!" The boy, Silvica, coughed a few times as he intensely stared at No.101.

"I have dragged on long enough." No.101 positioned himself in the same stance again. "What I just did was a warning. Now, I will cripple your right arm!" His black pupils gradually turned cold as murderous intent flashed across his eyes.

Snip! Snip! Snip!

After three soft sounds, Silvica staggered backwards and quickly dodged two slashes from the hand knife. The third snip landed on his right arm, and red blood quickly dyed his white sportswear.

"Nice dodge. Let’s try it again!" No.101 was getting angry. "Die!!"

His right hand violently shook, and, like a chopping knife, he aimed for the young boy’s limbs. Within two seconds, he slashed four times.

With every slash, the speed increased, and only red shadows could be seen.

The two youths backed off even more.

Snip!

A street light made of stone was hit. With a bang, its concrete base was destroyed.

Another series of snips rang out. The boy’s right leg could not dodge fast enough and was slashed open. He stumbled and could no longer stand up straight.

"Silvica!" the girl screamed out of worry.

Garen stood in the shadows; he was planning on stepping out, but he decided to draw his extended leg back.

"The White Eagle? Is that the guy with Dale Quicksilver?"

"If it’s that guy, then it’s a bit troublesome. I cannot let them see my real face."

He observed his surroundings and took a deep breath.

Bang!

Another punch landed on the right-side wall of the alley. A bowl-sized bulge instantly appeared as gigantic pieces of cement were shot off.

Garen grabbed a piece of cement and squeezed it, causing it turn into a handful of dust. He then slabbed it on his face. Immediately after, his dusty face became unrecognizable.

"Who is it!" The party heard noises from the alley and questioned.

Garen slowly walked into the alley and observed the change in the situation.

During the one moment Garen did not pay attention, the young boy’s left arm was hit. He was now supporting his entire body with just one unwounded leg. The young girl was trapped by another group of people, and the situation was unfavorable.

No.101 stood with his back against him.

Hearing the noise, No.101 turned his head and glanced at Garen.

"It’s you. You want to involve yourself with this too?" Without waiting for Garen’s answer, he suddenly laughed. "Since we’re all here today, we might as well take care of all of you together. "

Bang!

The young girl on the side was kicked in her stomach. She wobbled a few steps back and was immediately hit from the back. She fell to the ground hard. Her face turned ashen as she struggled to breathe. The gun tucked in her pants had also shook loose in the process.

"Eve!" Silvica screamed as he kneeled down on the ground with one knee.

No.101 turned around and marched towards Garen, completely ignoring the now weakened and defenseless young boy.

"You had such a good opportunity, yet you did not run away. Should I call you stupid, or should I call you an idiot? I have no idea why our boss sees you as valuable." He pointed at the young boy and girl who were still getting beaten up. "See this? This is what happens when you fight against the Golden Hoop. Even if they are the son and daughter of the White Eagle and Dale Quicksilver, they have to obediently be tortured by us."

Garen loosened his shoulders. Crisp bone cracking noises were emitted out of his body.

"You talk so much useless crap. Just fight me. As a gift for what happened before, I’ll make sure you have a relatively comfortable death."

"That is exactly what I wanted to say." Before No.101’s voice faded, he dashed towards Garen at an incredibly fast pace. The moment he was about to reach Garen, he twirled his foot and turned left for an upper cut.

Snip!

Garen felt a pinch of pain in his left arm, and the sound of his clothes being ripped open echoed out. He looked at the wound in disbelief. There was a red imprint on his skin.

Chapter 48: White Eagle (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Such a sharp hand knife! My body has already reached the second stage of Explosive Fist Arts. From head to toe, my skin is rougher than a bull and is hard to pierce even with a dagger knife, but one move from his hand knife could leave a red imprint on my skin! This means, if he pierced at the same spot again, he could penetrate my defense!"

Garen was in shock. This attack was too fast, he could not react swiftly enough. He was blinded for one second, and the next thing he knew his left arm was hit.

When Garen looked at No.101 again, he already stepped back three meters and was staring at Garen coldly.

"Another speed type?" Garen’s expression fell.

No.101 was actually the one who was really in awe. Unbelievably, his hand knife failed to cut through the opponent’s skin.

"This level of defense! This level of Body-Hardening Technique! I have not encountered this for years! This person has a strong physique! I need to attack his vitals, or else he will not even feel an itch let alone feel pain."

"His speed is definitely not as fast as me. I could run around and test to see which area is his weak spot!"

After making a decision, No.101 again stood in his attack stance. He pushed himself forward with one foot and dashed toward Garen. His right hand, hand knife, instantly turned into a red shadow and disappeared before him.

Snip!

Garen’s right arm was also hit. He extended his arm to grab the opponent, but he only grasped onto air.

A pinch on his back immediately followed. He was deeply stabbed.

"Die!" he bellowed. Both of his arms roused as his muscles expanded.

"Swing form!"

His two arms, like two elephant trunks, flung to the right side and formed into a rotation posture.

Hiss!

Garen circled on the same spot, but the two arms he was swinging failed to land. Below his feet, his boots scratched out a clear black circle.

The agitated air around them from the fight blew in all directions, forming a gentle breeze.

No.101 backed up another two meters. He had taken a short break before he threw himself forward again. The red shadow flashed and ruthlessly stabbed Garen’s lower belly.

"I will find your weakness!!"

The hand knife slashed upward and ripped open Garen’s clothes.

,

Bang!

Garen’s two arms again failed to grasp onto anything. His vision blurred as the red shadow flickered. His lower belly was again pierced by the hand knife, and a wave of dull pain started to emerge.

"I’m hurt!" He could picture the damage on his lower belly. Even though it was not deep, his skin definitely tore.

"I must find a way to stop his speed! Or else it will be hard for me to win no matter how good I am at defense."

His thoughts were interrupted suddenly. His lower left arm felt a pinch of pain. He was hit again.

"F*ck!" Garen was getting angry, "If only I had practiced my Shot Form to a point where I could utilize it however I wish… you bastard, kill yourself!!!"

He viciously threw a punch.

Crack!

No.101 dodged. His fist hit a wooden board instead.

The wooden door from a closed shop on the side of the road was punched through. Yellow wooden dust spattered

everything.

Bam!!

Another loud noise, Garen missed again and instead smashed a rock wall. A bowl sized crack bulged in.

"Is running away like a bug the only thing you can do!! You goddamn monkey!" Garen yelled angry as he threw another punch at No. 101. He dodged easily by lowering his head.

Pain shot up his right wrist, Garen was getting even angrier.

"You goddamn gray fur monkey!"

Boom!

He missed a step and landed on the concrete, and instantly, a little hole formed. He swung both of his arms and hit the lamp post No. 101 was hiding behind.

Crack!

The thigh-ticked concrete lamp post shook after the Swing Form punch. From its center, thin cracks began to form and spread. Small chunks of concrete flung off the post.

Everyone around them was silenced. More than 10 of the Golden Hoop members were shivering like cicadas. Looking at Garen’s bear like destructive behaviors, their legs felt weak.

A few of them were already hidden in obscure spots, ready to run away from this place.

The two youths who were still circled watched the fight between Garen and No.101 in awe.

"This person’s physical abilities are too strong..." Silvica mumbled, "His muscle defense is horrifying. His body is completely fine after hitting a concrete post! This is terrifying!"

The girl Eve had secretly sat down beside the boy when the others were too busy being shocked.

"This person seems to be the rival of the Golden hoop. His strength and defense attributes are way too strong. He probably practiced some sort of Body Hardening Technique or other forms of Arts. Too bad his speed is slow, he cannot move fast enough to catch up with his opponent. We better hide for a while then run away when we see a chance."

Boom!

Another shop’s metal iron door was hit and bulged in a round shape.

No.101 stepped back at lightning speed and distanced himself by two meters. His face was full of sweat, and blood was seeping out of the tip of his nose. It was scratched by a splattered cement piece.

His chest was violently moving up and down, and his lung was gasping for oxygen. His sweat was rolling into his eyes, but he was too afraid to wipe it off. He gazed at Garen in a deadly stare, terrified that the opponent would find a chance to attack.

"One punch!" His heart was pumping intensely, a reaction to his need of blood, "If he hits me with one punch!"

"I will die!"

No.101 concluded.

"What’s wrong? Gray-furred monkey?"

Garen inhaled deeply and walked forward with a cold smile.

"Are you done already? But I haven’t used up all my strength!"

His two fists bumped each other, creating a clashing sound similar to two pieces of wood hitting each other. It was as if his fists weren’t made out of skin and bones.

Bang!

Suddenly, a gunshot reverberated through the night sky.

Everyone fell silent.

The boy and the girl covered their own mouths as they watched the situation unfold before them.

Members of the Golden Hoop were also observing the scene with a dumbfounded face.

No.101 had a cold expression on his face. He slowly let go of the silver gun in his hand. White smoke was still dancing around the muzzle.

"Sorry, I’m not merely a Martial Adept."

Garen lowered his head and stared at his chest. There, a clear and charred bullet was stuck in the left side of his chest where his heart was.

Snap!

He covered his wound with his hand, and his fingers buckled around the bullet.

A yellow bronze bullet fell to the ground, creating a soft noise.

Hiss…

Everyone held their breath one by one in astonishment.

"He… He blocked a bullet!" Silvica watched with his eyes and mouth wide open, "Did I see it wrong?!"

"No… No…" The girl Eve was also in shock, she had no idea how to react, "I have heard that Martial Adepts who have reached the peak stage of martial arts were not scared of guns. But…"

"You mean his martial arts skills have reached the peak!?"

"No, that’s not it. This person’s Body Hardening Technique is too horrifyingly strong!" Eve swallowed her saliva. Her voice was shaking because of how surprised she was.

"You… you bastard!!!" No.101’s whole body was shuddering. His expression became twisted as he staggered back even more.

Bang, bang, bang, bang!

Then it was just the clicks of an empty gun. There were no more bullets.

No. 101’s face was pale. He still crazily pulled the trigger.

Garen looked down at the five holes in his chest. He flexed his muscles, and the four other bullets were squeezed out and fell to the ground.

"This is it."

He fiercely marched forward. After a dull sound, he flung forward, and with one punch, his fist landed on No.101, who was still pulling the trigger continuously.

Bam!

No.101’s head exploded like a watermelon. His brains splattered out and formed a perfect fan shape behind him.

Because of that one second of distraction, No.101 wasn’t able to utilize his speed. On top of that, he was already exhausted from the fight before, he did not have enough explosiveness and was therefore knocked out with one punch.

"He… he exploded!"

A member of the Golden Hoop was shaking from head to toe. He stepped backward.

"Ah!!!" everyone screamed.

Every member of the Golden Hoop scattered and ran away.

The girl and boy watched every moment of the fight. They were in complete disturbance from the bloody scene before them.

"Don’t look."

A giant hand gently covered their eyes.

Garen withdrew his fist and calmly looked at No.101 who was on the ground.

"I killed someone again."

This was not his first time killing someone.

After his first accidental kill, he felt like his view on life became foggier and foggier.

"Every time I see those around me with soft necks and other weak body parts, I realized that if I’m not careful, I can gently squeeze, and a life will fade away. Humans have been living so peacefully in such weak shells. Just like ants, even though they are weak, they still have a division of labor."

He could feel that there was something strange happening to him.

"Young man, that was not true martial arts!"

A deep voice appeared from the side.

Garen turned his face and saw a pair of clear black eyes.

"Your fist techniques, they have entered the demonic path ."

It was a healthy looking young man with golden locks. His short hair was like a burning gold flame, prancing in the night wind.

The young man was wearing all white. His two hands covered the children’s eyes, and he was staring at Garen intensely and calmly.

"Demonic path?" Garen froze.

He looked at No.101’s headless corpse.

"Someone did once say to me that my martial arts have diverged from the righteous path. But what is the righteous path? What is the demonic path? Who draws the line between them?"

"To pursue strength unscrupulously is the representation of demonic." The blonde man turned the children around and stood up, "Martial arts were a terrifying murder technique created so humans could fight against creatures that were stronger!"

"It was not meant to be used between the same species! It was not meant to hurt and kill species of your own!"

"I was defending myself," Garen composed himself and said softly.

"But you had no need to kill him! You could’ve just wounded him so you could control him!" The girl Eve suddenly turned around and screamed.

"Eve! Don’t anger him!" Silvica shakily grabbed the girl’s arm out of fear.

"The martial art you used was created purely with the intention of murdering others. Who is your teacher?" the blonde man asked.

Garen did not answer. He simply stared at the three of them then walked into the alleyway he came from before disappearing into the darkness.

The blonde man observed the scene around him. Suddenly, his gaze froze when he saw the concrete lamp post that was almost broken into two.

"This fist art… Behemoth Gate!"

An image appeared in his mind. He suddenly remembered the silhouette of the devious and horrifying woman he encountered a couple years back. The woman’s naked back had white tiger tattoos that seemed to be roaring. The tattoo was so vivid it was as if the white tiger was going to lunge in his face.

"In the future, don’t provoke that person!" the young man returned to reality and whispered to the two children.

Chapter 49: The Fundamentals (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Dawn.

Garen was strolling alongside the street next to the river wearing his black coat.

On his left, sounds of river colliding against the bank could be heard. The midnight wind blended itself with the gloomy surroundings; one cannot help but to feel as if winter was just around the corner.

Garen had his hands inside the pockets of his pants while strolling; the coat masking the torn shirt that he was wearing inside. He unbuttoned his shirt and looked down on his chest, only to find the red mark on his exposed skin slowly fading away.

His hands reached to his stomach. Still can’t shake off the pain.

At the corner in front of the street, an old lady appeared in her gray gown, gently pushing her cart. On her cart stood a cylinder-shaped black container, and on the container’s surface were the words: 2 yuan milk.

A girl in a thick white fur coat rushed over to the cart. She took out some money and gave it to the old lady. In exchange, she left with warm milk in between her palms.

Garen tightened his shirt due to the decreasing temperature around him. He too hurried towards the old lady.

"Can I have one please?"

"Of course," The old lady answered. Her face wrinkled with age, so was her skirt, but she looked surprisingly neat. She took a small yellow cup from under her cart and put it under the container. She poured the milk into the cup and passed it to Garen.

He gave the old lady two yuan, carefully holding the cup in his hands, and headed off to the arc just by the corner. The billboards at the each side of the closed shop had coincidentally formed an enclosure that prevented the wind from blowing onto Garen.

Garen laid his back against the wall, looking at the milk cart that was going further away from him. Every now and then, residents came out of their houses to buy milk from the old lady. She handed them their drinks, they handed her the money, and she continued her journey.

The scene of him bursting No. 101 with one blow recurred in his mind.

"I’ve murdered again…" Garen closed his eyes, seemingly stuck in recollecting his thoughts. "I was born with a talent that none others have: the ability to swiftly cross the gap others spent years to build. But is it a blessing or a curse? Because of this, I have no progress in sculpting my heart and soul."

"Abruptly increasing strength, causing my desires to be set loose and spiral out of control… Is this what I’m facing? Am I going down the righteous path or the demonic path?"

Coming back from his senses, he immediately discontinued his thoughts. He took a sip of the warm milk, the vapor from the drink steamed onto his face. The rich aroma of the milk seeped itself into his nostrils and left him feeling oddly satisfied.

"The fight with Golden Hoop 101… It was obvious that my speed could not match him, but my strength and defenses were enough to endure his hits. It didn’t matter how many blows he laid on me, one blow from me was enough to seal the deal… Which was also one of the perks of strength-based fighters. Even then, my combat techniques are still not up to class. If my techniques were at a certain level, I’m confident that I’m able to strike first no matter how swiftly he moves. Until I’m certain I’m able to face these types of opponents with ease.. " Garen concluded while taking another sip from his milk.

"It seems as though the choice I made to strengthen my body first was right. No matter how fast a person is, a bullet is all that’s needed to end a battle. This type of approach is safer, to say the least. Too bad I’m still fighting at the basic level. I still need to focus on solidifying a general move set before moving on."

He crumpled the cup and threw it into a nearby trash bin after finishing his milk.

"Now, I’m simply strengthening my body and throwing it onto my opponent to see what happens. Things will be different, though, when my combat skills mature."

Garen walked out from his hiding spot and headed towards the stone bridge. After crossing it, it took another ten minutes for Garen to reach his house at Bluetree Street.

From this point on towards the whole area within Bluetree Street was considered as the suburbs.

Ding-a-ling…

A bell rang from afar, signaling that the clock had struck ten.

"It’s ten already?" Knowing this, Garen hastened his pace. The hills were especially empty during the night, except for the occasional carriage and cars along the road. It looked as though no one had ever set foot around here during the night.

After coming out from an intense battle, Garen was exceptionally relaxed, having this silent night to accompany him.

He walked without a worry along the main street, knowing that no one knew who he was and, naturally, will not have any intentions towards him. If it weren't a scheme specifically set against him, normal people would be just like chicks on his palm if they went up against him.

Over at the stone bridge, a few drunkards sat on the floor boasting about their stories. A sharp smell of alcohol ran up to Garen’s nostrils as he passed by.

Garen had one of his hands on the stone bridge’s rail. The cool rough surface of the cement that he felt from his touch transmitted into an image that was projected in his mind. Suddenly, he felt some pain surging from his chest to his abs.

Garen was surprisingly calm because he knew it was the impact from the bullet that caused the internal pain.

He tore off his tattered shirt effortlessly and threw it into the trash bin at the side. He only wore his coat cover his body as he made haste towards the direction of his house.

Garen didn’t even get far before a white carriage appeared coming towards his direction. The carriage made a sharp U-turn on the main street and followed him slowly. The carriage window slowly wound down, exposing Grace with her tired, yet emotionless face.

"I have gotten the permission for the application. Now, regardless if it’s the Golden Hoop, if they set foot in our territory, they must follow the rules. They must give a clear explanation on why they ambushed us now," she whispered.

Garen jogged along beside the carriage. "101 died," he said calmly.

"Died?" Grace glanced Garen for a second and notice that he was showing no emotion. She immediately understood when she saw the cement powder on his face. "I understand. I will handle it."

"I received some intelligence this time when I went back to the company. The Golden Hoop dared to order some of their henchmen to kidnap the son and daughter of Dale Quicksilver and the White Eagle. The current status of their children is still unknown. It is obvious there are some motives behind this action."

Garen regained his breath before speaking, "I’ve already saved the two children. Too bad they weren't grateful."

Grace was stunned by his reply. She did not expect so much to have happened when she was not around.

"Is it… Did they see your face?" Her eyes fixated on the cement powder on Garen’s face.

"Supposedly no… But still, she is the daughter of Dale Quicksilver. She can easily see through the disguise. She is indeed a tough one." Garen recalled the moment the little girl stood up out of nowhere and questioned his expression.

"Right, do you know how the factions divide themselves in the martial arts community?" he added.

"The division of the sects?" Grace was puzzled. "I’m not particularly sure about that, but from what I’ve heard it is separated into two groups: the official ones that train accordingly to build their physique and mentality; and the unofficial ones who train people to morph themselves into a human weapon to take lives."

"Is that true?" Garen’s eyes light up suddenly. "Then, do you know anyone well-known sects that train using the unofficial way?"

"Give me a sec…" Grace frowned. She went silent for a moment before continuing, "Your master is one of them. There are a few martial artists inside the province that follows this philosophy. It has quite an impact on the underground community there."

"It seems that they are quite accepted. What about the martial artists that trained formally?" Garen asked.

"Almost similar, besides the fact that they don’t dwell in the underground community, they are quite in common with the unofficial ones. Didn’t your master or senior mention anything about this?"

"I’m heading back first. Be careful when going back, Grace."

"Relax, I’ve gathered enough human resources to deal with this situation." A killing intent could be seen in Grace’s eyes as she continued, "I even have the police department on my side. This time I will give the Golden Hoops an unforgettable lesson!"

Garen saw the determination from Grace’s eyes so he didn’t bother to continue. Garen passed by the village’s main gate and saw the old guard watching him. The guard then scribbled on a piece of paper, faced down.

Before going up the stairway, he heard sounds of children crying coming from above, as well as a hoarse male voice coming from the record player.

Garen skipped a few stairs and got to his floor in no time. The hallway was dark and almost pitch black, so Garen had to move slowly to avoid bumping into anything or anyone. He reached the door, took out the key, and inserted it into the keyhole.

Ka-chak

The doorknob unlocked. The inside was dark and silent.

Garen closed the door softly and changed his shoes before entering the living room. From the corner of his eyes, he spotted a shadow sitting on the couch. He could barely make out the shape of a human under the low lighting

Garen paused, before slowly realizing the shadow was of his sister.

"Ying Er? What are you doing sitting here?"

Ying Er sat silently on the couch facing down; her expression shrouded in the dark. The only light source was the faint light coming from the opposite building, shining through the window onto her.

Garen noticed that her sister wore a black high-waist skirt with a dark colored bow on her head. She even wore a pair of thick stockings underneath her skirt. She sat unmoved on the couch, without replying.

Ever since he came to this world, Garen has always cared for his sister. Judging from his sister’s personality, he knew something was up.

He then shifted himself and sat beside his sister on the couch.

"What’s up? What happened today? Aren’t you going to the Jaderipple Lake with your friends tomorrow?"

Grace only replied after what looks like an eternity.

"I’m not going tomorrow."

"What happened?" Garen frowned. For Garen, he always thought that the world was different inside and outside the house. To him, home was a place where he could free himself from all his worries. He could only be himself when he was with his innocent sister who only knew how to treat him well.

Plus, Ying Er was the last one he wished to hurt.

"It’s nothing, stay out of it!" Ying Er turned her head away. "I’m just a little bit tired that’s all."

Garen grinned, stretched his hands out to both sides of his sister’s cheek, and pulled.

"Ah… Owh. What are you doing!?" Ying Er erupted. She tried to pull Garen’s hands away from her cheeks but despite her best efforts, her struggles were ineffective.

"Don’t worry so much when you’re inside the house. Take some rest. I’m sure after a good night’s rest you’ll be fine." Garen let go of his hands. "Don’t forget you still have me, Pa, and Ma in the house."

"Do you want me to kill you!?" Ying Er stood, punching and kicking Garen in a completely arbitrary manner. Nonetheless, she didn’t exert too much force to prevent hurting Garen by accident.

"You shouldn’t look down on your brother," Garen smirked, steadying his body to let Ying Er hit him. "Are you tickling me by any chance?"

"Gahhhh!!!" Ying Er was truly angered now. "It seems as though you won’t know wrath if I don’t use my true power!"

Thump

She threw a heavy punch at Garen’s face.

"Hey! Not the face!" Garen was caught off guard by his sister. He quickly avoided his sister’s incoming punches, dug his head in between his arm, and hid somewhere in the living room.

Ying Er followed closely behind him, chasing and trying to beat him. Both of them made a fuss in the living room.

After quarreling for a while, Ying Er was finally exhausted. She then dropped bum first onto the couch.

"Huff… It has only been months and already your body has grown bigger. What do you eat every day? It’s absurd!" She caressed her fists. Garen felt nothing, yet her fists were red with bruises

"I told you I’m practicing martial arts. I’m even a formal disciple of a master. I’m different from amateurs like you." Garen purposely showed off his proud face to his sister.

"You… are really getting on my nerves!" Ying Er felt a sudden urge to give her brother more beatings. She inhaled deeply, suppressing her urges. "Speaking of which, you had been gone all day for weeks now. What have you been doing outside? Did you found a job outside because it’s the holidays now?"

Garen scooted over to his sister’s side. "Nothing much, I usually jog around evening, right? Plus, I need to train some of my basic techniques at the dojo. It’s normal if I came home late."

"It’s not good if you come home too late." Ying Er said, pouting her lips, "And I heard a rumor about you and Ai Fei in school…"

"I swear I’m innocent…" Garen was obviously in a predicament. He then started giving a detailed explanation to his sister about what had happened.

Both of them cuddled up on the couch, chatting away. By the time they came to their senses, it had been two hours past midnight.

Ying Er sat still on the couch, without any intention of going into her room. It could be seen from her face that she was tired. She sneaked a yawn when Garen wasn’t paying attention.

Chapter 50: The Fundamentals (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Are you sleepy? You can go to bed if you want," Garen said. He wanted to go sleep, but his sister was not tired at all. Garen rarely saw Ying Er under the weather, so he decided to stay with her.

"I am not sleepy at all, I will go to bed later. Are you sleepy?" Ying Er said. She sat beside Garen and put her head on Garen’s shoulder. She could feel Garen’s muscles against her arm, and she felt safe staying beside him.

"Do you have other plans if you are not going tomorrow?" Garen asked. It was rare for them to sit beside each other and talk for so long.

"Can’t I just stay at home?" Ying Er said. After thinking for a moment, she then asked, "Or take me to your dojo, I want to watch you guys practicing the skills! Am I welcome there?"

"Nope." Garen answered without thinking.

"You…!" Ying Er looked irritated again.

"Don’t! It’s not my rule, and you know I can’t show you the Secret Arts." Garen explained quickly, and he did not want Ying Er to get angry again.

"That’s true, but how about after the practice? I went to the dojo once and I heard there was a pretty lady driving you there every day. Is that true?" Ying Er asked, and she had a forced smile on her face.

"Well…" Garen did not expect to go to the White Cloud Dojo alone, and she even asked someone there about him. It looked like she already knew about Grace, and it gave him a bit of headache. He knew Ying Er liked him, but it wasn’t due to them being siblings; it was because of something else.

"Fine. I am tired now. I’m going to sleep." Ying Er stood up and walked towards her bedroom.

Garen was not sure how to best explain this, because his relationship with Grace was all about underground business. He did not want Ying Er to get involved and wanted his sister to live a normal life.

Ying Er stood by the door of her bedroom, turned back around, and said, "You are old enough to make decisions by yourself. I think I put too many restrictions on you."

She did not wait for Garen to respond and just slammed the door shut. Garen shook his head and felt a bit speechless. He decided he would go to bed after brushing his teeth.

*******************

*PA*

"Straighten your fists! If your stance is wrong, you will lose your balance. If you keep going without correcting your stance, your knees won’t be able to handle all the pressure, and they could be damaged permanently," Farak said.

Senior Brother Farak was standing beside Garen in the Martial Colosseum, and he was correcting Garen’s basic stances. The two looked like an adult and a kid standing beside each other.

Garen grew taller and stronger recently, but he still looked small comparing to Farak.

Farak was half-naked, his skin was tanned by the sun, and his muscles were hard like rock. Garen could see the veins on Farak’s skin, with a white tiger tattoo just like the one Senior Sister had, but around his chest where Senior Sister’s was around her back and arms.

"Besides all the basic attack and defense techniques in Martial Arts, there are also basic training techniques. I’ve told you that these training techniques were developed by the masters, and with these training techniques, you will learn how to use your force without hurting your muscles or bones, how to maximize the potential of your skills, and how to minimize the damage you take. Countless senior members improved the training techniques based on their own experiences, and those techniques are the secret of building your body." Farak’s gray hair was all over his shoulders, and he looked wild but gentle with his white pants.

"Garen, remember, you must perfect this form. You should make sure your center and your stance are stable. Don’t make any mistakes. You need to be steady, and solid, like a mountain!" Farak patted Garen’s back as Garen was practicing the forms of White Cloud Combat Arts.

"If your form is not perfect, your knees and shoulders will be damaged by the stress." Farak added.

"Yes! Senior Brother!" Garen nodded.

"Some beginners focus too much on the core theories thought they would be able to create their own skills. They thought that their own creations were much better than the traditional techniques, some even said the skills the beginners created were not effective at all without the fundamentals, but that's only half-correct." Farak watched Garen practicing the form, and Garen looked like an elephant that had lifted its feet.

"In a real fight, the free-style combat is actually very effective, but using those skills will damage their bodies. If you want to hurt others with those skills, you will have to hurt yourself first. Martial Artists like these won’t live long, though they are good at fighting others," Farak said, and he started to practice the Elephant Form as well.

"Forms will change with the development of Martial Arts. The forms from the Mammoth Secret Technique and Behemoth Gate you are practicing are new. The Master already improved them, and you need to find the most comfortable stance by yourself while not making any mistakes. You should not let others break your stance easily."

Farak crossed his arms, and raised them in front of his chest. He leaned forward a bit and bent his knees a little. One of his feet was out in front, and the other was places behind. Farak’s stance looked unbreakable.

"Human bodies are different from one another, and you need to figure out what suits you the most, then you will have your own perfect stance," Farak said. Garen nodded, and his eyes were half closed. He imagined himself as a mammoth lifting its forefeet in the air, but he realized he was still not steady enough.

"Keep making minor corrections. Don’t just imitate others. Their stances are developed for themselves, and you still need to find the stance that suits your own body." Garen heard Farak’s voice again.

"Understood!" Garen started to adjust his stance again.

"Gates with long histories all have their own stances," Farak said, and he moved to the front of Garen.

"Besides building your body and helping you reach your optimum state, the stances also have another central role: to fight and to kill." Farak said.

"Fight and kill?" Garen asked.

"Yes. All the stances were created for the same purpose. To help you use your combat techniques faster and easier."

"Every Gate has their own combat techniques, and that’s the reason why the stances are different from one Gate to another. With proper stancing, you will be able to use your skills easier, and your opponent will have a harder time trying to figure out your combos, so you need a stance that can help you unleash skill combos that will fit into any combat situation.

"Alright," Farak said as he patted Garen’s shoulders, "let’s give the stance a test."

"Your Four Forms are pretty good already, and you should be able to use them well. Come here," Farak said. Garen nodded and opened his eyes. He then followed Farak to a wider space.

Using his Mammoth Stance, he said with a light tone, "Attack me. Use any skill you want."

"Sure." Garen did some preparation and stared at Farak calmly.

"Ha!" Garen yelled, and he used an overhand punch.

*PA*

Farak waved his left hand, and redirected Garen’s attack towards the side. Garen was going for Farak’s waist, but missed his punch after it was deflected.

Garen did not give up. He kicked out towards the front and used a third of his strength, aiming at the gap between Farak’s arms. He suddenly felt his ankle ache, and his right leg was caught by Farak’s arms.

"Yoink!" Farak imitated the sound of bone breaking, and he moved his arms a bit. He sounded a little cruel.

"There goes your right foot. It will be broken in half," Farak said and released Garen’s leg. He returned to the Mammoth Stance again.

"With this stance, I will be able to defend attacks from most of the angles, the only problem is attacks from the rear, but most Martial Artists have this problem. Remember, never show your enemies your back!

"A good Martial Artist will never show his back to the enemy no matter what happens!" he added.

"Understood." Garen nodded. He knew Farak was speaking from his own experience.

Farak stood straight, smiled, and said, "Most of the time, you have to try it yourself after you know the theory. If you don’t try it yourself, you won't be able to understand it well, and you won't be able to use in real fights. I suggest you try it when it’s safe, and help your body memorize it."

"Senior Brother, what do you mean ‘try it’?" Garen asked.

"Go to the Stage Exam. You will see many different styles in the Amateur Stage Exam, and you can practice what you learned there." Farak blinked his eyes and asked, "Your Explosive Fist Arts is good enough for defending, right?"

"You… know about that?" Garen was surprised and asked.

"Yeah. You don’t need to hide it. We all know, otherwise the Master wouldn't have let you do whatever you want. Your talent is the best among us, and we wonder how strong you will become in the future." Farak smiled and patted Garen’s shoulders.

Farak, Senior Sister, and Junior Brother all knew Garen was extremely talented, and they were willing to see him improve. They never hid anything from him, and they tried to teach all the things they knew to Garen.

The stronger Garen was, the stronger the Mammoth Gate would be. Though Farak did not really like Senior Sister, they were in a competing relationship and they sometimes argued. However, they would never engage in a real fight. They learned from the same Master so there was no point in them fighting each other. They all wanted the Mammoth Gate to be better, and they would never show weaknesses to the true enemies.

Chapter 51: The Beginning of Misfortune (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

For almost 20 days, Garen practiced the White Cloud Combat Arts under Second Senior Brother Farak’s supervision. Farak corrected all of the mistakes that might cause Garen injury before Farak could spend time on his own training.

Since Farak’s supervised him in person, Garen could not use the two Attribute Points he had accumulated from all these training days. The abrupt enhancement of power would alert Farak and expose his special ability.

Boom! Boom!

In a bright training room, two arm-sized dark iron sticks were mercilessly hitting Garen’s back and chest as beads of sweat splashed all over the cement floor.

The two strong students wielding the sticks were panting and had no strength left to continue striking.

"Okay, thank you. Get some rest."

Garen stood up straight, relaxing the muscles of his upper body.

"Yes, Brother Garen," said the two students, as if they were just absolved of a severe punishment. They put away the iron sticks and left the room hastily.

Standing alone in the center of the room, Garen felt the bright sunlight shining through the window and onto his naked upper body, reflecting the glossy sweat.

Whoo…

Garen let out a long exhale as his muscle gradually relaxed.

It was lively outside as the indistinct sounds of an accordion drifted from the street, along with loud roars.

Garen glanced at the window.

"Looks like the government holding a celebration for completing the central sculpture. It’s surprising that it lasted so many days."

Garen paced to the window and looked down.

A group of kids with red shirts, black hats, and small black-and-white striped Federation flags were passing by the dojo in lines. They were looking around aimlessly, and the lines were a mess, but with their cute faces and young skin, they had attracted a lot of people on the street. There were also parents and relatives following them, cheering them on. The scene was chaotic, yet rhythmic.

There were several long tables placed by the streets, covered with white tablecloths. People were busy setting out fruit plates and cakes on them, but some, including a group of beautiful girls, had already sat down and start tasting. The two students who helped Garen practice were also there, smiling and chit-chatting with two girls.

Garen couldn’t help laughing.

"No wonder they were so reluctant."

"Of course they were. You couldn’t possibly forget which holiday it is today?" Third Senior Brother Joshua spoke from behind.

Garen turned around and found that Joshua had shaved all the white hair from his head. Now his head was covered with bandages and he was wearing a white suit, which presented a weird scene, since he looked like a monk in a tuxedo.

"What holiday? Isn’t for the completion of the central sculpture?" asked Garen puzzled.

"It’s the Carnival! The Carnival!" said Joshua speechlessly while rubbing his bald head. "Have you practiced too much and lost your mind? Hiding indoors to train on your own on Carnival day? This is a once a year event."

"1230"

"Carnival…" Garen suddenly understood and said, "Every December 30th, I almost forgot…"

He pulled his jacket from the hanger and put it on slowly, covering his powerful muscles.

"Brother, how do you have time to come back to the dojo? Shouldn’t you enjoy yourself during the holidays?"

"If only First Senior Sister didn’t beat me into pieces, then you wouldn’t even have the chance to tell me to enjoy myself," said Joshua sourly. "Okay, okay, hurry up. You must have someone you want to see, right?"

"Yeah…" Garen smiled, dressed himself up, and grabbed his key from the shelves. "So excuse me for leaving first. Thank you, brother, for reminding me or I would have missed something really important."

"That’s more like it! Bring me something nice to eat when you come back," said Joshua, waving his hand.

Garen stepped out of the training room. He washed off the sweat from his face with tap water and left.

A noisy and sweltering turbulence blew directly on his face as soon as he stepped outside. Everyone was crowded on both sides of the street while watching the slowly marching parade. A circus troupe passed by as pigeons burst out from magic tricks and soared up into the sky.

Garen followed the street and went toward Pennington Street. He made a few turns, bought some tarts and two glasses of tomato juice, then he headed to the Dolphin Antiques store.

It was noon and the store door was open. Old Man Gregor sat on a wooden stool by the door, smiling and staring at some young girls passing by.

They were dressed in refreshing short red skirts and white stockings. From time to time, while holding up their fluffy pom-poms, these girls shouted out the slogan:

"Aria School! Forever the best!"

They were only around 16 years old and passed by the antiques store in a very neat queue, shining with youthful vitality.

Garen looked at the Old Man on the other side of the street across from the girls. He smiled and held up his food to him.

Garen really stood out with his tall figure, handsome face, dark-purple short hair, and maroon eyes. He had not stopped exercising and was becoming more robust. Like a heating furance, his Spirit outshined others. Some girls flirted with him, showing great interest.

"Hello, handsome!"

A blonde left the queue and nudged Garen a bit. She had her dark blue eyes on him and looked coy. She flicked a note to Garen without anyone noticing and Garen caught it.

"You are beautiful, but…" said Garen. He pinched the note in his fingers, shrugged and shook his head.

Disappointment flashed in the blonde’s eyes.

The girls moved away and shouts of slogans would sound out occasionally. It was so packed that Garen had to push through the crowd as he went directly to the antiques store.

"How are you, Old Man? I mean for the Carnival," asked Garen. He sat down on the stairs beside Old Man Gregor, disregarding the dirt. He passed the tomato juice and tarts to him.

"Same-old, same-old. Ain’t the girls from Aria School beautiful? You feel tempted? I saw someone gave you a note just now!" said Old Man Gregor with an obscene laugh.

"Such an old age, yet still a pervert," said Garen speechlessly.

"Mom!" A little boy ran past Garen and lost his balance. He fell over in front of Garen.

Garen lifted the boy up. The boy didn’t even shed a tear and continued to rush forward to a beautiful woman’s embrace. The woman gave Garen a gentle smile to thank him and left with the boy.

"My grandson should be that age if he were still alive…"

Garen could hear the sorrow in the Old Man’s words. He did not reply and simply sipped on his tomato juice. He stared at the lively street, waiting for the Old Man to continue.

"It was my fault for getting my son and daughter involved. How regrettable…" Gregor sipped his juice and murmured, "It’s a pity… but there is no medicine for regret in this world…

"Is there even any sense in regretting?" asked Garen lightly. "Looking back, the only point is to learn from your lessons and grow up."

"You are still young. You don’t understand," said the Old Man with a smile. He exhaled deeply and said, "When memories of the past occupy half of your life, you will know."

"Maybe." Garen didn’t pursue the topic further. His face showed no expression.

"Garen, lad," said the Old Man who suddenly became formal, "Have you been curious why I would open an antique store here?

"Curious? Why would I be curious? Isn’t it nice living and ordinary life like that?" Garen gave the Old Man an odd look. "Right, do we continue our lessons today?

"Of course, learning is something you must stick to every day. No breaks," said the Old Man who eventually collected his thoughts and stood up. "Come on in. Today is the Carnival, so I have a special treat for you."

Mystified, Garen followed him into the Antique store. The Old Man closed the front door. Light came in through the small window above the door and illuminated the room.

Gregor carried two thick books from the back room and sat at the desk. Pointing at the books and he said, "These two are the textbooks that I will spend most of the time to guiding you through. You can go through them yourself now. There are hardly any errors in them, I’m sure. I proofread them myself very carefully so don’t worry."

"Thanks." Garen randomly picked one book on the side. The pages were full of red marks and notes, which covered the entire 2,000-page book.

He switched to the next one. It was the same.

"I annotated those two books a long time ago. All errors have been corrected. I meant to prepare it for my grandson. Well, who would have known that you’d get to use it first?" said the Old Man.

Garen smiled. He knew that the Old Man prepared these books specifically for him since the notes were still new. Old Man Gregor only told him that the textbooks were prepared for someone else out of the fear of pushing Garen too much.. Previously, Garen unintentionally mentioned that he wished to have more systematic textbooks. To his astonishment, Gregor actually took out two heavy dictionaries.

Garen was honestly touched seeing all those densely marked pages. God knew how long it took for the Old Man to complete everything.

"So these two books are all the rudiments I need to know?" he asked as he closed the book.

"More or less. The next step is to learn appraisal by hand. To enhance your level, you must feel the object in your hands. Plus, you have to know every detail and the history of all kinds of objects," said the Old Man, who took out a pair of glasses and started polishing.

Garen nodded. He moved a stool to the Old Man’s side and sat on it with his back straight.

"Where do we start today?"

Chapter 52: The Beginning of Misfortune (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Regarding theory, you’ve mostly understood the basics. You will become an appraiser after understanding these two books and experiencing some practical application. Your mission for today is to start reading these two books. You can even take them back with you if you want. The things that I’ve told you are all in these books. You can come find me again if you have any more questions," the Old Man replied calmly.

Garen nodded, flipped open the first page, and began reading the book attentively.

Two hours went by without a notice. Garen let out a long and deep breath, remembering the page number he had last read before closing the book.

"Old man, it’s already 3 o’clock. I need to go back and celebrate the holiday with my family."

"Take the books with you. I will be meeting some of my old friends soon anyway. It’ll be better if you’re not around then." The Old Man’s eyes never left the book he was reading. He waved at Garen impatiently, as if wanting him to be gone at once.

Garen grinned and picked up the two books.

"Then I’m heading out now. I’ll be back tomorrow."

"Mmm, hurry up! Seeing you taking your time annoys me." The Old Man didn’t even bother to look up. "Remember to write down the questions you want to ask on a paper."

"Got it."

Garen walked out of the shop playfully swinging the books. He turned his head to look at the old man before letting out a smile.

"Stubborn Old Man, I know you’re celebrating the holiday alone. If you truly have friends, they sure took their time visiting you."

The streets were filled with flowers and paper confetti. There was also some dove feathers and smashed cupcakes lying around.

Garen had not even gone far before noticing Grace standing with a stern look beside a car near the entrance of Pennington Street. She seemed to be waiting for him.

Garen hurried himself over.

"Did something happen?"

"Dale Quicksilver is here. He wants my company to help him identify something!" Grace whispered, "Let’s talk in the car."

Garen frowned. He was a bit startled when he heard that Dale Quicksilver was looking for Grace.

The two of them sat side by side in the front seats. They cranked the windows closed to dampen the sound of the marching band passing by.

Grace took a photo from her purse and passed it to Garen.

"Dale Quicksilver approached us out of nowhere this morning. He took this along with him and asked me to identify it."

Garen received the photo from Grace. He was clearly shaken by what he saw.

The photo showed the Bronze Cross Emblem he left at the Silversilk Castle.

"Is this…" He observed the emblem in the photo carefully. The black and white photo was shot at a very close distance. Everything was shown very distinctly.

"Hasn’t Dale Quicksilver investigated the Silversilk Castle incident thoroughly? Doesn’t he know where this emblem came from?" Garen asked softly.

"Of course he knows! What he wants to know has nothing to do with the information about the Silversilk Castle." The look on Grace’s face was exceptionally serious. "He wants to know the origins of the emblem – from before the Silversilk Castle incident!"

"Before!?" Garen felt goosebumps recalling the strange events he encountered during his time at the castle. He almost broke both of his arms back then and he had tried to forget about fleeing with his tail between his legs.

"Looks like they’re facing the same problem as us…" He glanced out of the car window at the marching band. He spotted a kid wearing fake armor and dancing delightfully with a balloon and a badminton racket in each hand.

Garen closed his eyes. His eyes reflected with a bit more seriousness when he reopened them.

"So where is our ‘Detective’ now?"

"At our company."

"Let’s go and find him then," Garen replied heavy-heartedly. "If it is as predicted, we could even lend a hand to our detective to know more about what happened to me last time at the castle…" he murmured, looking out the window.

He had a hunch that everything started at the Silversilk Castle.

"Ok," Grace replied as she started her car and drove slowly toward the crowd.

****************

The scene shifted to a small room in a motel.

"Hahaha… Mr. Quicksilver, it’s been a while." Garen gave Dale Quicksilver a big hug with a big smile on his face.

"Indeed it has been a while." Quicksilver had happiness shown all over his face. "Did that Golden Hoop guy bring you any trouble, Mr. Kelly? I had asked some of my men to find you after the incident but to no avail. After all that effort, I can’t believe that you are here, standing in front of me. Such fate we have."

The detective still carried a smoking pipe with him, along with his black coat.

Standing beside Dale was a beautiful lady in a white gown with a feather hat. Her arms crossed delicately at her waist, showing off her elegance.

"This is?"

"This is my wife, Marianne," Quicksilver introduced.

"Nice to meet you, Mrs. Quicksilver," Garen nodded while smiling.

"Oh please, Mr. Kelly, you’re being too formal," Marianne answered sheepishly.

All three of them sat on the couches, facing each other.

Garen then took out the photo showing the Bronze Cross Emblem.

"Mr.Quicksilver, I’m actually a professional appraiser from the Manuyllton Corporation. When I heard that you wished for this item to be identified, I immediately took this matter into my own hands. Time went by so quickly my friend and it has been two months since the last time we met. "

"Indeed my friend. Such a coincidence, I admit I did not expect that you were working for the Manuyllton Corporation.." Dale smiled before continuing, "Do you by any chance know where this thing came from?"

Garen frowned after hearing this. He sat silently, looking as if he was recalling something.

Regardless, the couple was not in a rush. They sat there quietly, waiting for Garen to speak.

Garen only let out a word after a few minutes of silence.

"Truthfully speaking, I’m afraid that this emblem is an ancient artifact left by a kingdom from 1,000 years ago."

"1,000 year artifact?!" The couple jolted from what they had heard.

"Indeed. 1,000 years ago, there was an ancient kingdom called Natama, located where our federal state is now. There’s very little information left regarding this kingdom. Thus, I based my judgement on the characteristics of this emblem. As for the origins... I’m afraid that I cannot help you with that."

Garen let out a sigh. The information given was not from Garen, but from real appraisers from the Manuyllton Corporation. He was just pretending like he knew the details.

"If that’s the case then…" The couple exchanged eye contact, both looking worried.

"But…" Hesitation could be heard from Garen’s tone. "I’m not sure if I should tell you this."

Dale’s eyes sparkled with hope, so he immediately asked, "Mr. Kelly please do not hold back on us. We’ve been through so much together that there’s nothing that you should hide."

Garen glanced at him and saw the determination from his eyes. He showed a face of determination in return.

"If that’s so, regardless of whether you guys believe me, I will be telling you two about the other data that we collected."

He hesitated before continuing, "No, it is not categorized as a ‘data,’ but more of a hunch that I have." He eyed them before saying, "I think that this emblem is a cursed antique."

"A cursed antique!?" Dale Quicksilver staggered. He regained his posture before mumbling, "I should’ve known! I should’ve known…"

Mrs Quicksilver was still seated at the side. Sweat could be seen dripping down from her forehead. She was worried about her husband’s reaction.

"Indeed, this is an antique that brings misfortune." There was some firmness in Garen’s tone. "I have a natural talent for recognizing antiques that are cursed and I’m confident in identifying anything that falls into this category. However… would you mind letting me have a look at the emblem? Before I even came back to the company, the other appraisers had already returned the emblem to you two. I didn’t have the chance to examine it for myself."

"This won’t be a problem." Dale took out a small black box from his coat, clearly worried.

Garen received the box and immediately opened it. What rested inside was a burgundy emblem surrounded by black swan feathers. The exact same emblem he had left at the Silversilk Castle.

Garen placed the box carefully on the coffee table, cautiously picking up the emblem.

His expression immediately changed the moment the emblem fell into his hands.

Without a doubt, the Potential residing inside the emblem had grown since the last time he made contact with it. A cold piercing sensation slowly seeped from the emblem into Garen’s body. With the emblem in his hands, it felt as if he was holding ice itself. This emblem definitely had at least a fraction of the Black Jade Disk’s Potential residing in it. Judging by what he felt now, this power had grown at least twofold.

"Could it be?!" Garen seem to remember a possibility. He raised his head and look at Dale Quicksilver, who sat across from him. "Mr. Quicksilver, you have to answer me this. Did anyone meet any accidents before you two got a hold of this emblem!?"

"How did you know?!" Dale’s eyes opened wide. He stood up, breathing heavily.

"Please! Stay calm!" Mrs. Quicksilver ran over to comfort her husband, trying her best to make him sit back down. "Please listen to what Mr. Kelly has to say."

Huff…

Dale Quicksilver let out a long breath.

"I apologize for my rudeness Mr. Kelly."

"It’s alright. Please, call me Kelly. We are friends, right?" Garen nodded.

"Sure, Kelly. Would you mind telling me how you knew that there were people involved in accidents with this object?" Though Dale Quicksilver sat down, he did not break eye contact with Garen. "This is very important to me!"

"Did someone close to you have an accident?" Garen did not wait for him to answer before continuing, "I apologize, this is also one of my natural talents. I can properly identify the status of these cursed antiques. It may be related to the fact that I’m fascinated by items like this. It’s an instinct, an indescribable one."

"Instinct? Good, your instincts are indeed very accurate. Aside from this fascination, I think you were born to become an expert in identifying cursed antiques. Right now I need your help." Dale Quicksilver spoke in a serious tone, "Do you know how to break the curse from this emblem? My friend, the White Eagle’s son is in danger!"

"In danger?! What happened?!" Garen asked worriedly.

He owed Dale Quicksilver a debt due to the case involving the Black Jade Disk, but Garen thought he had repaid Dale last time after the rescue. Though he was not particularly fond of Quicksilver’s daughter, Garen still held respect for Dale. Regardless, the Black Jade Disk had helped him through a lot. He still felt that he was progressing from time to time.

Chapter 53: Companion (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Dale Quicksilver picked up the coffee on the table and had a sip to calm his nerves before speaking.

"Since the Golden Hoop incident, things have been happening consecutively. Silvica, my old friend the White Eagle’s son, unexpectedly received this emblem by chance. He subsequently got himself into trouble during his time at the Silversilk Castle."

"What happened?" Garen asked.

"He fell from the top of the castle." Dale took a breath in and continued, "Fortunately, there was stuff below him that helped to disperse the impact. But after the incident, he fell into a coma and we don’t know which region of his brain was injured."

Lady Marianne continued from where her husband had stopped and said, "What’s strange is that the doctor performed a full body examination on Silvica and found no damage to his brain. Yet, he still lies unconscious in a hospital bed." She also had a worried look on her face. "If it is possible, we will be glad if Mr. Kelly can lend us a hand."

Garen frowned, looking at Dale Quicksilver and Lady Marianne. It was obvious that both of them thought of Garen as someone who had extraordinary ability. No doubt they hoped that his "ability" could help him resolve Silvica’s situation.

"I’m afraid I’m going to disappoint you…" Garen had all of his fingers crossed, with a weary look on his face. "I gave a judgment on the cursed antique based on my hunch. It’s not like what you guys have in mind… I’m just a normal person with a natural born talent… but still a normal person."

"But… What about Silvica…"

"Stop mentioning it, Marianne."

Dale Quicksilver prevented his wife from finishing her sentence. "I can very clearly see that Kelly can’t help us in any way. He isn’t lying."

The detective scowled, then slowly returned to being calm and logical.

"From the looks of things, we still need to know about the origins of this emblem. I have stayed at the Silversilk Castle for so long, yet nothing has ever happened to me. Why did Silvica encounter danger so quickly?"

"Indeed, this matter needs to be analyzed thoroughly," Garen nodded in agreement. "How about this? I’m quite free during this time of the month, so maybe I can check things out with you guys and give you a heads up if I find anything relevant to the cursed antique."

"I’ve always thought curses were a myth, but after witnessing how you deduced the situation so accurately, maybe there are some secrets hidden inside this emblem. Screw it!" Dale Quicksilver stood up. "If this cursed antique is really useful and if it’s the root of Silvica’s condition, then we have to take this emblem and experiment on our own to fully understand the situation."

"Please, let me be the one to do it."

A male voice came through the window. A white shadow came into the light and a man with a white coat and blonde hair can be seen from the half-open window. He took a seat on a corner of the couch.

"I’m sure the Golden Hoops are the ones behind my son’s situation! Curses are just some folklore made to frighten kids. This world is full of people trying to deceive others by making up myths and fairytales."

Garen raised his head and discovered that this guy was the one that showed up beside the kids that night. He still remembered being criticized by this guy for being too violent and that his martial arts swayed onto the demonic path.

"This is….?"

"He is the White Eagle, who is also my best friend," Dale Quicksilver introduced him while standing up. In the meantime he reintroduced Garen to his friend, but this time as Kelly.

The White Eagle used his sharp vision to scan Garen and nodded, "I’m afraid we might need to depend on you this time." He did not recognize Garen as the look-alike disciple of the Behemoth Gate from that night.

"It’s no big deal. I have endured hardships with Dale before and it is only right if friends help each other out. Plus, this incident involves the cursed antique, which pretty much suits my interests." Garen dismissed the formality and said, "Okay, let’s not waste any time. When are we going to the castle?"

"How about tomorrow? We gather here at Manuyllton Corporation in the morning and then head off to the Silversilk Castle," Dale suggested.

"No problem."

"Sure."

"Then it’s settled." Dale then reached for the emblem on the table. "I got this emblem from Silvica’s body. I thought that it was suspicious, so I brought it here to be identified. Who would’ve known that things would turn out like this?"

"My friend, don’t worry too much. Everything will be alright." Garen let out a sigh, while one of his hands patted Dale’s shoulder. There were two reasons why Garen was being so nice to them: one, he sincerely wanted to repay Dale Quicksilver’s kindness and two, he was genuinely interested in knowing the secrets hidden inside the cursed antiques – especially after being affected by it at the Silversilk Castle.

"If there’s nothing else, then I need to go back home to celebrate the holiday with my family." Garen stood up. "Please excuse me."

"Please."

"Please do."

The Quicksilvers immediately stood up formally.

"Please make yourself at home you three. I’ll be going now." Garen turned and left the room. The moment before the door fully closed, his eyes were focused on the White Eagle. He couldn’t help but have a weary look on his face.

"That guy stayed hidden outside the window throughout the conversation and I didn’t even manage to notice him. This guy is definitely not an average joe…"

Grace awaited him at the door and they both headed downstairs.

"This here is one of the divisions that I’m in charge of. Basically, everything here is at my disposal. The results regarding the situation you want us to check on are already here."

She handed Garen a copy of the results.

Garen looked at the results and was thrown deeper into confusion.

"No obvious scars, the first judgment is a cardiac arrest?"

"Yes, it is possible that it’s related to poisoning. In a manner of speaking, the suspect has already taken action and, judging by the looks of things, he is very determined this time around. I can’t believe he will strike at this crucial moment, but I’m afraid I cannot assist you this time," Grace said disappointedly.

"It’s alright. I will investigate this matter with the help of the detective and his friend. It helps that this is according to what we initially intended," Garen replied, winking.

Grace had no idea what his initial intention was, but she nodded along. "Any preparation needed?"

"If it is possible, please prepare me a gun." Garen grinned.

*************************

Garen reached his home before dawn and spent his evening celebrating the festival with his family. They only had a simple meal and some conversation about each other’s recent situations. He went to bed after washing up. The next morning, he went to the Manuyllton Corporation’s division after applying his makeup. Surprisingly, Dale Quicksilver and the White Eagle were already there waiting for him.

"You guys are early. Are we driving there?"

Dale stood beside the White Eagle in front of the building. Marianne and Dale’s pretty assistant were nowhere to be found. Parked beside them was a black sedan with two car lights as big as goldfish eyes – dead goldfish eyes to be exact.

"I’m driving straight to the Silversilk Castle. Is everything prepared?" Dale Quicksilver opened the door and sat inside.

The White Eagle and Garen followed suit.

After the doors were closed, the White Eagle took out some cigarettes from his pocket and handed one to Garen.

"Thanks, but I don’t smoke."

"Mr. Kelly, I’m sorry we have to drag you out this time." The White Eagle lit his cigarette and took a puff from it. He lets out the white smoke before continuing, "Regardless of this case being solved or not, I owe you one."

"You’re Dale’s friend, which makes you my friend as well. There’s no need for such formality between friends. Plus, I volunteered to do this myself." Garren grinned. "I can see that you’re a righteous man and worthy of being a friend."

"Likewise." The White Eagle smiled in return.

The car engine slowly warmed up, then they drove onto the streets into traffic.

After 10 minutes or so, the car slowly drove out of Huaishan City onto a mountain road. The car sped through the withered grass and through the wilderness.

Inside the car, Garen toyed with his black revolver. Flipping it from front to back and then from left to right, as if he wanted to try it out soon.

"Kelly is this the first time you’ve handled a gun?" Dale noticed Garen’s actions from the reflection of the rearview mirror.

"Yes, there’s practically no use for guns within the city, but since we are going out in the open, Grace gave me one for protection purposes." Garen seemed to be fond of his mini revolver. In this world, a revolver can only hold up to six bullets at a time and after a bullet was shot, it reloaded automatically. It can be regarded as a semi-automatic.

"We should spend some time at the shooting range when we’re free." The White Eagle chewed on the remains of his cigarette and suggested half-heartedly. He took out a white revolver from his waist. "For now, let’s take care of those filthy pests behind us."

Before he even finished his sentence, he forced open the door and jumped out.

Bam Bam!

Two consecutive shots were fired, then the sound of a car skidding as it suddenly braked was heard.

Screech….

Dale Quicksilver instinctively stopped the car. He immediately got out from the car.

Garen, not wanting to be seen as a weakling, also pointed his gun behind him. From the car window, he saw the White Eagle had gunned down one tough henchman, rolled forward, and executed two other henchmen who were hiding behind.

There were two additional black cars following behind the first car. Six other henchmen came out from their cars and four of them were instantly shot dead by the White Eagle. The remaining two tried to escape by driving off with one of the cars at the back.

The White Eagle smirked and fired two more shots from his gun.

Boom!

The car exploded while trying to make a turn and burst into flames. The smell of petrol mixed with burning rubber wafted over the air.

The battle was over before Garen even exited the car.

"Such rapid movement, such precise aiming!" Garen could not help but be impressed by the White Eagle’s killing efficiency.

Their three faces were red from the glow of the burning flames.

Dale Quicksilver bent over to examine the corpses.

"They’re from the Golden Hoop."

"Filthy pests!" White Eagle spat and swung his white coat to shake off the dirt he picked up from his actions earlier. He noticed Garen getting out of the car and was impressed by how Garen handled the situation calmly.

"Looks like Mr.Kelly has been through situations like this. I’ve heard that you took care of the man from the Golden Hoop last time right? Care to spar with me some time?"

"I can’t compete against professionals like you! I’m just interested in ancient antiques and I’m sure you understand we can’t be in this field if we can’t adapt," Garen shrugged bitterly.

"True. Okay gentlemen, let’s head back to the car. Leave the killing for professionals like me." White Eagle kicked away the corpse at his feet and turned toward the car.

The other two followed.

Igniting the car, the three of them drove faster to make up for lost time.

Nobody said anything inside the car.

Garen snuck a peek at the White Eagle. The White Eagle may look like a relaxed person, but he was actually always on high alert. Rumor was that he had certainly learned a lesson after they were injured by the explosive trap set by the Golden Hoops. Since then, he did not let his guard down like he used to.

Dale Quicksilver was focused on driving. From his eyes, it could be seen that he was thinking of something.

"Since White Eagle is always on high alert, I might as well take a nap."

Garen decided to rest in his seat. He then slowly drifted away into slumber.

Chapter 54: Companion (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After what felt like an eternity, the car slowly came to a halt.

"We are here." Dale Quicksilver’s voice transmitted from not too far away.

Garen slowly opened his eyes as his gaze extended beyond the car window. On a simple yet beautiful hill, Canoe Town’s two story buildings hid among the mists and decorated the hill. A boy riding in a cow-drawn carriage curiously looked at the black car while passing by.

"Are we here?" Garen stretched.

"Yes, after a couple hours of driving we have arrived at Canoe Town. We still have some ragged distance before we reach the Silversilk Castle, but we can’t get there by car." Dale Quicksilver exited the car and stared into the sky. "The weather doesn’t look too pleasant, so we should make our way there as soon as possible."

Garen followed him out of the car and gazed at the gloomy gray clouds in the sky.

The wind was picking up in speed as a hint of rain flourished.

"It is noon, but the sky looks murky. I think heavy rain is inevitable today."

"Then let’s get there before the rain." The White Eagle switched to the driver seat. "I’ll go park the car. You guys go find a carriage."

"No problem."

Collectively, the three tasked with different duties managed to find a driver who was willing to go to the Silversilk Castle at twice the regular fare.

The carriage hit the road again. It took the group of three another two hours to finally reach the small hill they visited before.

They gazed at the distant Silversilk castle as they stood on the grassy, dark green hill.

The castle and its grounds were still shrouded by white ashes. . Some black charcoal was mixed in, which made it look like coffee mixed with baby formula.

The triangular castle was quiet, casting an uneasy silence. The sound of tree leaves rustling from the forest dispersed to the surroundings.

Roar…

The booming thunder spread from the dark, overcast sky. It rumbled from the distance, passed over them, , and finally resounded into the horizon.

"Oh... Is this the Silversilk Castle? It’s got a pretty nice atmosphere." The White Eagle laughed sarcastically. However, his eyes rapidly scanned the area.

"We are going to live here for the next few days. The police department initially left two people to watch this place, but I told them to leave yesterday. The scene is the exact same as when Silvica was injured." With a serious face, Dale Quicksilver said, "Let’s go. It’s going to rain."

He took the first step to walk down the hill. The White Eagle followed.

Garen carefully examined the far left window on the second floor of the castle, where he had fallen after being pushed, then followed them.

The group of three tread on the dark green hill as if they were three small ants on a giant green carpet. They looked insignificant.

There was not another soul within the vast tract of grass and forest surrounding the castle. Only three figures approached the Silversilk Castle.

Kacha!

Blue lightning broke the sky as thunder roared.

The three of them sped up to the castle fence. They quickly came through the front gate.

Dale Quicksilver took out the key to open the door. The White Eagle was examining the surroundings with his eyebrows raised.

Garen gazed at the castle in front of him with a hint of gloom pervading in his mind.

Last time, he was pushed and fell out of the second floor window without a clue of what happened. He had not seen a figure when he turned around, but heard a chuckling noise. Now that he was in front of the castle again, the Silversilk Castle was masked by a layer of mystery.

"If possible, I want to go back to that room again." In the previous life, Garen was not a fearful person. Although goosebumps covered his skin and his head tingled, it made him even more excited.

[The more I feel afraid and frightened, the more it exposes the weakness in my heart. This world is much more entertaining than the previous one.] The thought crossed his mind.

Crack!

The door opened.

The three of them strolled past the door. Dale Quicksilver slowly closed the door behind him.

The hall was pitch black. Dale Quicksilver took a torch from the wall and lit it.

"Should we go separately or together?"

"Together. It would be problematic if we encounter the Golden Hoop." The White Eagle said with a stern face.

"True," Garen agreed.

"Then let’s go the crime scene first. The place where Silvica found the emblem," Dale Quicksilver suggested.

Garen and The White Eagle didn’t disagree. The three of them followed the curved stairs to the second floor.

Crisp footsteps echoed in the hollow, yet frightening, castle .

The three of them hastily entered the room where Garen was pushed.

With a squeak, the door was forced open. A layer of white dust fell from the doorframe.

"I thought Kelly settled here last time, but it looks like you didn’t stay in this room." Dale Quicksilver smiled. "Why is it so dusty?"

He didn’t walk into the room but squatted in front of the door.

The room looked run down.

The floor was covered with a thick layer of white dust. There was nothing in the room besides a giant bed, a box, and a chair.

In the middle of the dusty floor, there was a faint trail of footprints.

"Those are Silivca’s footprints. It appears that he found the emblem on the bed or on the box and then for some strange reason decided to jump out of the window," Dale Quicksilver said in a deep voice. "I didn’t let anyone touch the crime scene."

The White Eagle nodded as he also examined the placement within the room.

Only Garen felt a tingling sensation on his scalp and goosebumps the moment the door opened.

He vividly remembered that he had entered this room before. Everything in the room was arranged the exact same way as before.

Yet, there is no way there would be this much dust in the room after a period of just two months.

The key point was that Dale Quicksilver had rested on this bed before! They even changed the bed sheets for a brand new set.

Now, the bed looked like no one had used in years and was covered in dust and cobwebs. The bed sheets were a faded yellow color. "Dale, the last time you came with me, didn’t you live in this room?"

Throat dry, Garen squatted down.

"How come?" Dale Quicksilver glanced at Garen with a puzzled look. "Only Silivica came in this room before. The dust on the floor is at least a few years old."

Garen remembered the last time he came into this room and a peculiar feeling that could no longer be suppressed overwhelmed him.

[Then, which room is the one that I came to last time?] Garen was no longer calm. [Could it be Dale that purposely fabricated this place?]

He carefully inspected the room as he looked from outside the door.

Everything was identical. The only difference was that the place was dustier and worn down.

"What should we do?" He lowered his voice but didn’t tell them the story about last time.

"Tidy this place up again. We’ll live in the two rooms beside it. I want to see how strange this Silversilk Castle is," Dale Quicksilver said with conviction.

"How should we organize the room?" The White Eagle looked at Garen. "Why don’t we move a bed and all live in a room together. There is no way I can keep both of you safe at the same time otherwise."

Garen took a moment to think before he shook his hand. "Don’t worry about me. I’ll sleep in a room by myself. You guys can share a room. The White Eagle can protect Dale. Don’t forget I am not a powerless ordinary person." He showed a slight smile.

"Okay this works, I want to see the truth behind the Antique of Tragedy!" Dale Quicksilver nodded.

Kacha!

Another lightning bolt flashed across the sky. The bright light cast a pale white on their faces. The thunder continued to roar in the distance.

Splash…Splash!

Giant raindrops hit the windows of the castle and cascaded into a continuous wave of impacts.

"Who is it!!"

Dale Quicksilver’s vision sudden focused as he immediately pulled out his pistol and aimed directly behind Garen. The two of them were facing each other and the pistol pointed toward the hallway behind Garen.

The White Eagle slightly frowned as he didn’t feel anyone behind him. He, like Garen, was also facing Dale. He turned around and asked in a puzzled voice, "What happened? I didn’t feel anyone behind me."

Garen also turned his head around to see an empty hall.

"No. I saw a black shadow flash down the hall. It was clearly spying on us," Dale said with a stern face.

"If it was because of the metal lamp on the right side of the hall, I would not be able to see the person’s shadow."

"So you are saying you saw a person’s movement through the lamp’s reflection." The White Eagled pondered as he followed Dale’s vision to the copper mounted lamp on the wall.

Strangely, the bottom of the lamp looked bright without any corrosion.

"Yes. Let’s stay in a room together. It’s probably safer this way," Dale said with his voice lowered.

"I don’t mind," Garen nodded in agreement. He looked at the Bronze Cross Emblem around Dale’s neck as caution flashed across his eyes.

"Perhaps they were from the Golden Hoop. Looks like we have to be cautious now to see what tricks are they up to!" the White Eagle said with a cold voice.

The three of them moved two individual beds into an adjacent room. They tidied the room up a little before it was habitable to sleep with clothes.

Garen knew that Dale Quicksilver and the White Eagle did not believe in the power of the Antiques of Tragedy. As long as someone else had control over the information, anything he said before could be impersonated and faked. They thought that the tragedies related to the Antiques of Tragedy were all caused by people.

Garen wasn’t certain either, but the Silversilk castle was strange.

[This time it isn’t me that carries that bronze cross emblem, but Dale. From another perspective, I want to see what will happen to the owner of the emblem!] When Garen moved to his bed, he secretly watched Dale Quicksilver.

Bang!

A dull thud reverberated through the door as if the wind had pushed the window against the window frame.

The three of them sat separately on a bed or a chair. They didn’t make any noise as they listened silently.

The sound of raindrops rose as they smashed against the window. It felt like someone was pouring water profusely onto the window. The howling wind from the other parts of the castle wailed in the hallway as if ghosts were screaming within the mysterious Silversilk Castle.

Chapter 55: Rainy Night (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The White Eagle held out the pistol and slowly stood up against the wall. He gave the other two a signal.

The two of them immediately understood and stood up. They grabbed the guns from their waists and opened the safeties.

Kacha!

Another lightning flashed across the sky, and the light blinded the entire room.

The White Eagle pressed his ear against the wall. He was listening to something.

"Someone is outside." He lowered his voice. "There is more than one person!"

When his ear left the wall, mists of white dust dropped from the wall with a constant brushing sound.

"Who is there!" The White Eagle let out a deep roar as he rolled forward. Two bullet holes appeared from the wall he originally stood against. Someone had shot through the wall.

The White Eagle rushed to the door. He slammed the door open and dashed out.

Garen and Dale Quicksilver cautiously remained in the room without moving.

Garen held the gun in his hand and leaned beside the window while staring cautiously at the door. All of the sudden he felt his collar get pulled.

He turned around to discover the window was open. There was no one that could be seen outside. Rain continued to pour down, blurring the vision as close as a few meters away.

"What’s going on Garen?"

"Someone was grabbing my collar," Garen said in a bewildered voice. "Maybe I am just too nervous and got my clothes caught."

Dale approached the window and peeked outside. "This is the second floor and high above the ground. The window probably caught it. Be careful and don’t stand in front of the window. Even if you can’t see anything in this weather, it’s still dangerous."

"Got it," Garen responded.

Bang!

A gunshot rang in the adjacent room.

"Let’s go!" Dale dashed out of the door, and Garen followed.

The two of them rushed to the adjacent room. It was the same room from which Garen had been pushed out. It was empty.

"White Eagle!" Dale yelled.

No response. Only the door behind him creaked.

He turned around only to discover that Kelly, who had followed him, had disappeared as well.

"Kelly?" He raised his voice. He tightened his grip on the pistol in his hand, and his expression tensed up.

"The White Eagle! Kelly! Are you guys here?"

The wind suddenly blew on the half-open door as it gradually opened.

Creak!

The noise was oddly disturbing in the quiet hallway among the sounds of rain. Outside the door was a pitch black emptiness, there was nothing visible there.

Dale felt his hand holding the pistol begin to tremble. He realized something was strange.

He scanned the room.

The room was abnormally clean. The spider webs on the bed were gone and replaced with a clean white bedsheet. Multidimensionally shaped tiles covered the floor without a trace of dust.

The box at the end of the wall was spotless as well.

"This place is strange." Gloom covered Dale’s face as he deliberately opened the gun’s safety.

*******************

Bang!

Garen followed. He saw Dale dash into the adjacent room. The wind pushed against the door and closed it for a moment before he opened it again.

"Hmm?"

The peculiar thing was that he couldn’t see a trace of Dale who was just one step ahead of him.

"Dale!?" Garen slowly opened his safety and walked into the room.

The room was littered with dust. Water spilled on the floor in front of the window. Someone stood in front of it with his back turned.

Garen looked carefully. The person’s clothes resembled the White Eagle’s.

"Dale?" He questioned with his voice lowered.

Tatata.

He heard footsteps behind him.

Garen turned his head and saw the White Eagle run into the room.

"Where’s Dale?" The White Eagle asked breathlessly. "Someone was in the room beside us. I didn’t manage to catch them."

"Dale was beside the window?" Garen pointed at the window as he turned around. He was shocked to discover that the figure had disappeared. It was as if it had vanished into thin air.

"What happened? I just saw someone at the window!" he said in a deep voice.

"Could you have made a mistake?" The White Eagled walked over, frowning. He examined the floor by the window. "There are no footprints. There’s no way that someone was standing there."

"That’s impossible," Garen said firmly. "I am confident that someone did stand in front of the window. Oh right, where is Dale?"

"Isn’t he with you?" The White Eagled asked with agitation.

"I just saw him rush into this room, then all of the sudden he vanished! My vision got blocked by the door for less than two seconds, and he was no longer here!" Garen said with seriousness.

Kacha!

Lightning painted their face pale white.

"This is going to be a problem." The White Eagle’s face became sober. He took out a match to light up a torch he’d brought with him. The bright yellow light slowly lit up a small portion of the room.

All of the sudden, he thought of something. His expression changed as he leaped beside the window and looked down. The dark grass field was empty. He let out a sigh of relief.

"Dale only came in one step before me!"

"Are you certain?" The White Eagle’s face was calm as the way he looked at Garen turned vicious. "There is no way he could have left in such a short time."

"I’m certain!" Garen answered with conviction.

The White Eagle stared at him without blinking. He tightened the grip on his pistol when he remembered something. He slowly backed away from facing Garen. He retreated to the door and squatted down. The White Eagle used his empty hand and gently touched the ground. Suddenly, his body began to loosen up.

"You are right. There are three people’s footprints! But one of the people disappeared as soon as he stepped into the room."

Garen felt a terrified feeling edge into his mind. He took a few steps to check. There were three sets of footprints with one set vanishing as soon as it entered the room. Due to the humidity, the other two sets were still visible.

Bang!

A sudden furious wind gusted into the room and slammed the door close. It almost hit Garen’s nose.

"The wind is picking up its speed." The White Eagle stood up. "I am sorry I didn’t trust you." He apologized as he pushed against the door, it didn’t open.

"Not a big deal. The door must have locked itself, use the key to open," Garen suggested with a grave expression. He kept alert for any movement in the surroundings. "We need to find Dale now. He may be in dire danger right now."

"I got it!" The White Eagle nodded and his expression became grim. He took out a set of keys and examined the labels. He picked out one to insert into the lock.

Creak, creak.

The key turned a few times in the keyhole. The door didn’t move. The White Eagle pushed again but couldn’t move it in the slightest.

"Hmm?" The White Eagled paused. "This is not right!"

"Kick it open!" Garen also saw the problem.

The White Eagled agreed. He took a step back and kicked the door with full force.

Bang!

The door didn’t even shake. Only a flurry of dust fell to the ground.

"There is something wrong with this room!" Garen stepped back to give his companion more space.

"Go grab the stuff. I’ll kick open the door. We’ll leave this place as soon as we find Dale!" The White Eagle yelled out, feeling the absurdity of this as well.

"Ok!"

Garen sprinted back to the room they’d stayed in before and packed everything together. Just as he was about to leave the door, another sound rocked the place.

Bang!

A gunshot was heard from the hallway. Then the sound of the door cracking followed.

Garen took their belongings and rushed out. The hallway was empty, and silence returned.

The room beside them was still locked without any signs of damage.

"Then how did I hear the noise?" His head felt numb as he was certain he’d heard gunshots and the sound of door breaking. But now even the White Eagle was gone.

"Could it be because of the emblem?" He caught a trace of the cause.

He stared at the closed door. He knew that if he didn’t do anything, Dale could die in there.

"Although I have repaid your favor already, but..." He took out his pistol and aimed at the lock.

Bang Bang Bang!

Three gunshots and lock was destroyed.

He tackled the door with full force and opened it.

There was no one in the room, but the bed was moved out of its position. There was a flight of stairs leading to the first floor hidden on the ground.

Garen took a deep breath as he walked to the hidden exit and peaked down. From this angle it directly faced the first-floor ground. Dale Quicksilver lay there, motionless on the ground.

"Dale!" Without any consideration, Garen jumped down. He used a couple of rails to break his fall and landed firmly beside Dale.

"Dale! Are you okay?" He helped the detective up and checked if he was still breathing. He was.

The detective gradually opened his eyes, mumbling in drowsiness,"Below me, below me."

Garen noticed that there was a bronze cross emblem in the place where the detective had lain. It had a visible white scratch mark, most likely done by the detective himself.

Dale begun regaining his consciousness. He sat up straight and gasped for air.

"That was dangerous! Just before, you guys disappeared all of a sudden! I managed to find an enormous secret in that room!"

"Don’t worry about that now. The White Eagle is gone!" Garen said in a stern tone. "I just heard him break into the room, but when I got there, the door was completely fine!"

"The White Eagle is gone?" Dale looked rather calm. "Don’t worry, he is stronger than both of us. If we are okay, then he should be all right too."

"What do we do now?" Garen helped Dale to get up. Both of them unanimously agreed not to pick up that emblem.

"No wonder The Antique of Tragedy is known by its name. I finally witnessed it today." Dale Quicksilver had a perplexed look as he gazed at the emblem.

He took out a gun and aimed up.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Three straight shots.

The gunshots sounded oddly unbearable. The noise even supressed the sound of rain outside.

Quickly, a white shadow sprinted from the second-floor stairs and landed in front of them.

"Are you okay?" The White Eagle asked.

"I am okay!" Dale nodded. "I just saw the Golden Loops! They definitely have something to do with this!"

"Me too! I saw a figure jump from the window and pursued him," The White Eagle said solemnly, "but unfortunately I didn’t manage to catch him. Follow me."

The White Eagle took both of them out through the gate. They walked to the left side of the castle and into a small hut.

A dead body covered in black lay lifeless inside the hut. Blood dripped from its chest and rolled onto the grass field before being diluted by the pouring rain.

"Golden Loop Number 114."

The White Eagle threw the golden loop at Dale.

"Golden Loops’ hundred numbered member. Of course they’re the ones causing headaches!" He walked beside the body to examine it. He asked The White Eagle for some specific details before he starting to analyze based on logic and deduction.

Chapter 56: Rainy Night (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was not listening to their analysis. He was standing slightly behind, alertly surveying his surroundings.

The two of them were talking at the front, while Garen was paying attention to the rear. Standing at the back, he could see the two of them through the rain—one of them was standing, while the other was squatting—in the pavilion. Their voices were carried to him intermittently by the wind. Garen lifted his head and looked toward the room that they had just come from.

He could actually faintly see a person standing at the window, but was unable to clearly see the person’s face. The room was pitch black and even the contours of the figure could not be made out.

Garen was quietly looking at the figure.

"Let's go! I found the key to the problem!" Dale Quicksilver and White Eagle walked over and tapped Garen's shoulder, then headed towards the entrance of the castle.

Garen quickly followed after them, but when he looked up at the second floor window once more, the figure was gone.

The three of them walked into the lobby and reached the place where Dale Quicksilver had jumped down previously.

The detective squatted on the ground, inspecting something. Then he looked at the Bronze Cross Emblem that was still on the floor, as if he was calculating something.

After a while, he stood up again.

"Follow me."

Garen knew that Dale definitely found something. He followed the detective together with White Eagle and the three of them walked toward the back of a staircase on the first floor.

Dale examined the floor in the corner, then suddenly lifted up a black piece of floorboard, to reveal an underground entrance.

As the dark, rectangular entrance was uncovered, the thick smell of blood instantly gushed out.

The three exchanged looks as their expressions changed. Then White Eagle took out a matchstick and lit it.

Chi.

Under the dim light of the matchstick, the three finally saw the scene under the entrance.

The interior of this small cellar was filled almost to the brim with corpses.

The corpses were all wearing black clothes and golden earrings.

Even though they were mentally prepared, the three of them were still shocked by the amount of corpses and drew in breaths of cold air. For a while, they did not manage to recover from the shock.

Afterward, White Eagle was the first to react.

"They're all from the Golden Hoop! What's going on?" He carried out a corpse that was closest to the entrance. "I can't believe so many people died here! No.89, a two-digit from the Golden Hoop is not that easy to kill!"

Dale knitted his eyebrows and said, "I only accidentally found the clue. I didn't think that following it would give me a result like this. It looks like this castle may be more mysterious than we imagined..."

"He died within a day." White Eagle inspected the corpse and sullenly said, "What should we do now Dale?"

"There's still some things that I haven't understood! Let's get out of here first!" Dale Quicksilver looked around the surroundings, as if he was checking for the presence of enemies. "This place isn't safe any more, so we shouldn't stay here. We'll go back and contact the police department, then mobilize some men here."

"What about the emblem?" Garen jokingly said with a low voice. "Don't tell me that it grew legs and ran back to the room?" He forced himself to laugh due to the slightly heavy the atmosphere.

However, when Dale Quicksilver heard his words, he became startled. He stood there absentmindedly, as if he thought of something.

"That's right!! The position of the emblem! I actually forgot about it! How did I not think of it just now!" he muttered to himself.

"You guys, follow me!" He suddenly turned around and started to run. As he ran, he looked at the carved reliefs on the walls.

Garen and White Eagle were baffled, but still followed after him. They moved from the back of the staircase to a room that was like a study.

Dale moved an empty bookcase aside and knocked on the floor. He soon found a ring and firmly pulled it.

A large wooden board was lifted up and the pitch black entrance underneath was revealed.

Dale took a lit matchstick from White Eagle and held it towards the entrance. There was a dark, metallic staircase connected to the entrance that extended all the way down.

Garen leaned over and looked in. The black metallic staircase extended downward into a very wide chamber.

Dale Quicksilver did not say anything further and just placed the wooden floorboard to one side, allowing the subterranean entrance to be permanently accessible. Then he tucked his shirt into his pants and went down the stairs.

White Eagle immediately followed after him, while Garen changed positions and looked down from the entrance.

The spiral staircase continued all the way down, extending to the bottomless darkness below. It was like a spiral funnel.

"We'll go down and take a look first. Please stand guard at the top. Fire your gun if something happens," Dale said softly after turning back.

Garen nodded. As he looked down at the anticlockwise spiral staircase that extended downwards to a bottomless depths, he felt slightly terrified deep in his heart.

The other two descended after lighting up a torch, yet the glow that it gave off seemed oddly weak on the spiral staircase.

Garen thought for a while, then picked up a rotting piece of wood from the bookcase. After weighing it in his hand, he threw it down the central gap of the spiral staircase.

The piece of wood rolled as it hurtled down, then, there was no sound at all.

The two that just went down—and had not yet gotten far—stopped. Dale found something, then lit it up and threw it down from the center as well.

The blazing red object rolled as it hurtled down, illuminating its surroundings as it fell.

They could only see section after section of stairs as the ball of light fell. The light from the fire became smaller and smaller and traveled further and further. It soon became a tiny dot and completely merged with the darkness. Then nothing could be seen.

Dale and White Eagle immediately turned around when they saw the result. They soon returned to the entrance and came out.

"From my estimation, this staircase is at least five hundred meters deep! It might even be deeper!" Dale Quicksilver sullenly said, "The secret of the Silversilk Castle might be inside here and this might be the final goal of the Golden Hoop."

Even though the two of them only went down for a short time, a thick moldy smell radiated from their body. They were shivering as well and their faces were slightly pale. Garen was only standing next to them, but was able to feel the cold air emanating from their bodies.

"Let's get someone to survey it tomorrow! I don't think the Golden Hoop would be able to properly explore it within such a short time," White Eagle suggested.

"By the way, I found this thing in my room earlier. Kelly, do you know what it is?" Dale Quicksilver passed over an exquisite ring with a black gem. The ring was silvery but there was some rust on it.

Garen received the ring and carefully inspected it.

"It's nothing. It's just an ordinary metallic ring, not an Antique of Tragedy. I am not sure what the black gem in the middle is, but it might be a black crystal." Garen had picked up a lot of antique and jewelry appraisal knowledge, so he was able to recognize most materials.

"It's something from 50 to 60 years ago," he added.

"Really? But I feel that this thing might have an important function..." Dale took back the ring and muttered to himself.

"One more thing," White Eagle suddenly said. "I found that guy from the Golden Hoop hanging on by a thread. The strange thing was that he actually accused us of killing a lot of their guys." He frowned and continued, "But we did not even encounter the people that he mentioned and what's going with the corpses in the cellar?"

"It looks like this castle isn't an ordinary place after all… I didn't think that there's actually someone—other than us—who could cause such a huge loss for the Golden Hoop..." Dale Quicksilver closed his eyes, as if he was thinking.

"Let's leave this place first. We need to carefully examine the information on this place..." he calmly said after opening his eyes.

"Even though I want the Golden Hoop to completely disappear, it doesn't feel good to be framed like this." White Eagle shrugged his shoulders.

"There's nothing we can do for now. We can't stay here tonight any more," Garen agreed with a nod.

The three of them returned the bookshelf to its original position and silently left the castle. They jogged in the direction of Canoe Town under the rain.

In the middle of the night, under the heavy rain, the three figure swiftly disappeared into the darkness.

The rain drops continued to intensively smash onto the surface of the castle, creating a pitter-patter sound as they collided.

After two hours, the night deepened and the rain subsided a little.

A human figure swiftly returned from the same direction the three of them had headed toward. It was Garen in a black outfit.

His eyes were calm as he changed his clothes and put on a black mask. He jogged back along the original route and circled around the right side of the castle. There was a french window missing its glass panes. Propped by his hand, he easily vaulted through the window.

He nimbly exited the room and walked to the lobby.

When he reached the lobby, he spotted a black figure standing at the staircase. The figure was faced away from him, looking in the direction of the cellar with the corpses.

Garen's expression went cold, but he could not prevent the sound of his footsteps.

"Who is it!"

The figure suddenly turned around and looked towards him.

Boom!

A flash of lightning illuminated the earring on her left ear. A large number ten was displayed on it.

Garen's gaze went cold and he slowly approached.

"Since you're someone from the Golden Hoop, hand that thing over and I can let you leave here alive," he said with a hoarse tone after deliberately altering his voice.

The figure who turned around was a tall woman with faint purple eyes and her hair tied into a high ponytail. With a frigid expression and tight black clothing, she gave off a cold and pure aura.

"You'll let me leave here alive? Ridiculous." The woman icily said, "Are you here for that thing as well?"

"What do you think?" Garen laughed bitterly as his right arm suddenly swung to his back.

Bang!!

A man in black behind Garen was sent flying. After hitting the ground, the mane rolled a few times before crashing into the wall, then ceased moving.

"I already said, hand that thing over and I can let you leave here alive." He did not even look at the attacker behind him and slowly walked towards the purple-eyed woman. The closer he got to her, the more he could feel the aura of potential exuding from her.

The purple-eyed woman sneered.

"Very well, you are qualified to make me fight you."

She slightly bent over.

Ssss...

A long hiss of breathing slowly sounded out. The woman raised her hands and grabbed her own collar.

With a tearing sound, her upper clothing was completely torn off and revealed her fair, naked skin.

"I will sacrifice your head to my dead brother…!"

The woman did not mind in the slightest that her naked chest was completely exposed. Her purple eyes faintly became deeper and her hands were clenched together with one above the other—as if she was holding something at her chest—while an oval space was left between them.

"Polaris… Fierce Arts!!!"

The woman suddenly breathed in once more, then her body rapidly inflated and thick muscles—covered with blue veins—appeared all over her body.

Her breathing sounded like a large airbag swallowing and spitting out air.

Within mere seconds, the cold, slim woman transformed into a muscular warrior who was as large as Garen.

The muscles throughout her entire body were twisted together, like steel ropes bouncing under her skin. A gigantic airstream slowly expanded from her body as a torrent of scorching air heated up the surroundings.

"Is that a Secret Martial Art?" Garen's eyes became more focused. The muscles of his body slowly tightened.

Huff...

He took a deep breath and slowly assumed the starting pose of the Mammoth Secret Technique.

No matter how he saw it, he needed to go through a hard fight in order to obtain this new, accidentally discovered Antique of Tragedy.

Chapter 57: Fight (1)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The woman's eyes were a deep purple, as if a purple liquid was about to seep out of them.

Bang!

The ground slightly shook as she stepped forward and charged towards Garen, like an arrow shot from a bow. If seen from above, a straight line was gouged into the floor of the lobby.

Both of their arms connected with each other as their fists and palms collided, sprinkling tiny drops of sweat onto the ground.

Bang!

Garen maintained his blocking pose and was forcefully pushed a few meters back, almost touching the wall.

Without a word, the woman swung both of her fists forward once more. A series of fierce impacts sounded out. Both of them did not shift positions and exchanged blows while standing in the same spot. The huge force caused the surrounding windows in the lobby to slowly begin to shake and even the sound of the rain was gradually overwhelmed.

Every time their fists collided, both of their bodies slightly trembled and the faint sound of bones cracking could be heard.

"Break!!"

As the woman shouted, a burst of warm air gushed out of her nostrils and her right fist instantly disappeared.

Garen could not react in time and her fist reappeared directly in front of his chest. With a loud boom, his chest visibly caved in as he flew backwards and crashed into the wall.

The walls of the lobby abruptly shook and huge amounts of fine dust fell onto both of them.

The woman sneered.

"You're not bad considering the fact that you were able to face me head on for this long while I used my Polaris Fierce Arts."

With a loud click, the chandelier from the ceiling suddenly fell straight down onto her head. This black chandelier was over a hundred pounds, was entirely made of metal, and the ceiling was over ten meters tall. It would easily kill a grown man if it landed on him.

The woman looked up toward the chandelier and swung her right fist at it. With a loud bang, it broke in two and smashed into opposite walls.

She shook out her right hand, though her skin was not damaged in the slightest.

Garen took the opportunity to stand up and stabilize his body. He sullenly looked at the woman, desperately thinking of a solution.

[I only discovered the Antique of Tragedy when the cellar with the corpses was opened. I didn't think that they would be looking for that thing as well. This lady is quite strong...]

[However, when it comes to the Antique of Tragedy, the more the merrier. Now that I finally came across one, I can't let it go. Even though she is strong, my Explosive Fist Arts isn't weak either!]

He felt his chest was still slightly painful. He took a deep breath and stabilized his body.

[White Cloud Secret Art!] he shouted in his mind.

All of the muscles in his body slowly expanded, as if a human shaped balloon was slowly inflated, and he grew from 1.7 meters tall to 1.9 meters. His head seemed a lot smaller compared to his current body.

"It looks like I've underestimated you." He calmly walked back to his original position, facing the woman. The distance between them was only a few meters. "However, I think you're mistaken. I wasn't the one who killed your men."

"You're not the one who killed them?" the woman sneered. "In a rural place like this, are you telling me that there's another Martial Adept hanging around?" Her eyes were constantly scanning Garen's body. As a martial artist who had reached the human limit, her insight had naturally reached the corresponding level. She could easily tell that the man in front of her had already reached the human limit as well.

"I don't care where you're from. Since you've messed with the Golden Hoop, you shall experience our endless vengeance!"

Before she even finished speaking, the woman roared and suddenly charged forward. She moved silently like a gigantic white python, drawing out a fine arc.

Her fists were like the top and bottom fangs of a python—opening and closing—constantly changing their position as they bit down toward Garen.

"Python Stab!!"

As her fists overlapped, a faintly audible sound due to the air resistance could be heard.

This was her true killer move: her fists appeared to be the attack, but the true attack was from the metal blades hidden in the soles of her shoes. Even though it was obvious that her opponent was an expert at the Body Hardening Technique, her legs had slaughtered a countless amount of such experts. As long as this attack connected, even the hardest muscles and bones would be pierced through.

She had previously used this move to puncture through a wooden board that was thicker than her fingers.

’

[I will kill you with one move!] She focused most of her energy into the tips of her toes. Silently, a silvery-white object slowly emerged from the bottom of her shoes.

Garen sullenly looked at the female figure charging towards him. It was not that fast, but the immense heat blowing towards him was as if a gigantic white python was really pouncing at him. He could even hear its hissing as its jaws opened and closed.

He slowly rotated his body, facing his opponent with the right side of his body.

Bang!

The two of them viciously collided and tightly stuck to one another; neither of them took a step back. As their arms intersected, they were only inches apart and could even hear each other's breathing.

Chi chi!!

The clear sound of cloth tearing sounded out twice and a triumphant look appeared in the woman's eyes.

Her legs were viciously wrapped around Garen's waist and her entire body was coiled around him as well, forming an abnormally amorous position. If she still had her previous beautiful appearance, someone might have the wrong idea. However, as she was tall and brawny at the moment, it looked like two muscular men were wrestling.

The woman was topless and had fair skin. Garen was wearing a large black shirt and even though his muscles had expanded at the moment, it was still mostly black. That was why the differences between their bodies were exceptionally clear.

The woman clung onto Garen's body as the blades of her shoes stabbed into the lower back of Garen's torso, at the position of his kidneys.

"Goodbye..." she whispered and laughed.

Garen suddenly grinned.

"That's my line!"

His right elbow instantly moved forward—like a black baton—and viciously smashed into the woman's face.

Bang!

The two of them instantly separated, while droplets of blood sprinkled all over the place.

The woman stumbled backwards. She could not keep her balance and knelt down on one knee.

"You… You're actually alright?!" She lifted her head and stared at Garen in astonishment. Blood was coming out of her eyes, ears, nose, and mouth. After receiving the elbow strike, her entire body was still violently shaking. Her ears were ringing as if she was standing inside a large bell that was being sounded.

"This is Vibration! Damn it! He's actually an expert that has grasped Vibration!" She could not believe it as she stared at Garen.

Garen touched the back of his waist and found two light wounds that were faintly bleeding.

"Too bad… If it was someone else, this move might be able to cut them into them. It's too bad that your opponent is me."

He slowly walked toward the woman.

"Hahaha..." the woman suddenly laughed. "What a terrifying Body Hardening Technique!" As she stood up, her right hand swiftly reached to her back and a silver pistol appeared in her hand.

"It's too bad that your opponent is me."

Her body seemed to have shrunk a little after the close combat just now. Even her muscles were softer than before.

Noticing this, the woman made a circle with her hands once more.

"Polaris Fierce Arts!!"

After fiercely inhaling, her body returned to the previous state.

"Combat Gun Arts!"

She charged towards Garen once more, like a white line.

Garen raised his right elbow again to use his most familiar stance: Shooting Form. Suddenly, he felt a numb sensation at the back of his waist.

"Damn! There's poison!"

With his waist suddenly losing strength, he could not even maintain the basic stance.

It was too late for him to do anything about it, so he could only use all of his strength to block with his arms raised.

Bang bang bang!

A series of gunshots rang out and Garen violently smashed into the wall behind him. Three brass bullets were lodged in both of his arms, the right side of his face, and his abdomen. He could feel a metallic taste in his mouth.

"Damn it! The handgun was too close, I am shocked!"

An ordinary bullet would need to stay within a human's body to maximize the lethality. When fired from such a close range, the penetrating strength was too high. If it was someone else, they would not be too injured and would only suffer a penetrating trauma at most. However, as Garen's Body Hardening Technique was too strong, the penetrating strength of the bullet only served to pierce his skin and the bullet successfully entered his body.

The bullet in the right side of his face was originally aimed towards his forehead, but was timely avoided. However, the other two positions were on target. Both of his arms were struck by a punch as well, but it was weak. However, it was just enough to break his stance and allow the bullet to hit his face.

Leaning on the wall, Garen did not even have time to catch his breath. He saw a white figure viciously pouncing at him as, the silvery blades on her feet drew an arc in the air as they aimed for his abdomen.

With the poison on the blade, he would definitely die if he was struck a few more times.

"Damn it!!"

Garen roared. Though his opponent was slower than No.101, she was still extremely quick and faster than him. At that moment, he could already feel the cold blade touching his abdomen.

"Since I can't avoid it, then we'll see who's tougher!!"

"Ah!!!"

With a roar, his abdominal muscles tightened to trap the blade, his left hand grabbed onto her leg to prevent her from escaping, and he viciously swung his right fist at the purple-eyed woman's head.

Bang!!

"Umph!" The woman was struck in the head by the punch and she reeled back from the blow, splattering blood everywhere."

The two of them separated, breathing heavily.

Even though the fight between them did not last long, the situation was abnormally severe. Both of them were heavily injured.

The woman's right eye was completely destroyed, her entire body was shaking, and she was bleeding even more from her facial orifices.

Garen was poisoned, his lower back was getting number, and his abdomen was starting to get numb as well. If the woman was not too weak and the blade was longer, the attack might have directly penetrated his gut.

Garen was leaning on the wall. It was the first time that he met his match. Even though his opponent's defense was lower and she had not grasped the Vibration Technique, her power was comparable and her blade could easily pierce his skin and muscles with enough strength behind it. The high defense of the Explosive Fist Arts was nothing for his opponent. With the addition of the gun and poison combination, Garen knew that he would not be able to get that mysterious Antique of Tragedy on this day.

"I've taken a huge loss this time!!" he muttered to himself. Lifting up his head, he saw the woman struggling to stand up. She was holding the silver handgun and was slowly aiming at him.

Bang bang bang!

Out of the three shots, only one managed to hit Garen's right shoulder. The bullet did not even managed to pierce through the skin and only left a red mark before it ricocheted. It made a clear sound as it fell to the floor.

"Your eyes are finished, hehe… You should have just handed that thing over. You were asking for it." Garen gloatingly laughed.

"You… Very well!!" The purple-eyed woman took two steps backward, then sagged onto the ground. "Unfortunately, you're poisoned. So you'll only... die earlier than me. To be able to die… by the hands of the No.10 Golden Hoop, your death isn't wasted."

It seemed that the two punches—using the Vibration technique—to her head had made her slightly sluggish.

Chapter 58: Battle (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen knew that the vibration was taking effect. The lady standing across from him must have had her insides injured by the power of vibration. His version of the second level of the Explosive Fists Art was unlike that of others. The lady might even have internal bleeding from it. Garen was confident in his actual strength and, if he were to use his it, he might even surpass his third senior brother. A simple gun would not pose any threat to him now. Originally, he planned to sneak out once he had finished searching for the antiques, but he had not expected this purple-eyed lady to discover her henchmen’s corpses.

Everything was smooth up until this point. Garen had not expected his opponent to be so vicious. The lady did not hold back on him using guns, fists, and even poison.

"I have to leave here now!" He felt that the numbness in his back had intensified.

Garen sneered and then closed his mouth. He focused on the upper bracket of the attribute panel.

The potential bracket was already at 233%, so he still had two attribute points remaining.

"Physique influences the recovery rate. It might prove to be useful now against poisonous effects."

In this emergency situation, Garen was running out of ideas. He needed to recover and escape to prevent unforeseen accidents from happening. The enemy body count of men from the Golden Hoop was no joke.

He fixated his attention and added one skill point to his Physique attribute .

The Physique attribute increased from 1.57 to 1.87.

The moment the point was applied to his Physique, Garen felt nothing but tingling all over his body. It only took one second for him to return to normal. He felt the numbness around his back and his lower abdomen start to fade away. He even recovered enough strength to stand up.

"Effective indeed!"

He was pleased by what happened.

"It is not worth becoming like this for a cursed antique! I even started a feud with one of the masters of the Golden Hoop. If I don’t take care of it now, I’ll be in even more trouble in the future!"

He was determined to finish his opponent to prevent any inconvenience in the future.

He stood up and began slowly walking toward the purple-eyed lady.

"How can you still stand?!" The purple-eyed lady covered her right eye with on of her hands. The remaining eye stared at Garen in shock. "How can you still move after taking hits from the Roman Flower King’s poison?!"

Her whole body was deadened and without strength due to blood loss. Though she could still aim her gun, her effort seemed meaningless against her opponent. She could not even reload and shoot in time due to the short distance from her opponent.

"This is the end!" An ugly smile could be seen on Garen’s face. He felt his body recovering rapidly. The 0.3 increase to his Physique attribute that he applied earlier had really helped his body. He sensed the numbness almost disappearing from his back and the feeling of pain returned from the injuries to his abdomen area.

"Hurry! Master has been waiting for a while now!" Hurried steps were heard coming from the outside.

Garen’s facial expression changed and he had one last look at the lady before deciding to escape. He jumped out from the same window he had snuck in from, turned the corner, and disappeared into the rain.

The lady had her head down and only let out her breath after confirming that Garen had left the hall. Blood and tears seeped through the fingers of the hand she held over her eye and dripped onto the black tile floor.

She picked up the clothing that she threw on the floor from earlier and covered her naked chest . Her body began slowly shrinking down, like a deflating balloon. In no time, she returned to her original form – a pretty lady with a petite figure.

The living room door swung open widely. A man and a woman dressed in suits swiftly came through the door. They were startled by the mess that was left behind and the purple-eyed lady who sat on the floor.

"Boss! Are you okay!" The tall man rushed over and bowed beside the lady on the floor.

"Go away!" Thump!

A muffled sound was heard. The man stumbled backward with his face looking pale. His eyes stared at the sword marks left on his chest. A line was neatly cut across his shirt, with his skin almost injured.

The woman in a black suit, who was smaller in size than the man, stood aside and laughed at what the man had been through.

The purple-eyed lady sat up on the floor.

"Any updates on the tasks I’ve ordered you to complete?"

"Master, I’ve been to Dale Quicksilver’s house and some of the White Eagle’s hiding spots. Both of them are nowhere to be found. We suspect that they’ve been hiding in some new place ." The woman in the suit bowed before answering.

The man’s eyes focused on the purple-eyed lady as she wrapped up the injuries to her eye region. He tidied his suit before speaking respectively.

"I, on the other hand, found both of them! Unfortunately, White Eagle’s friend Black Panther showed up unexpectedly during the search and took both of them with him."

"A bunch of useless pricks!" the purple-eyed lady roared while rising from the floor. Her right eye had stopped bleeding with the bandage wrapped around it. "You can’t even capture one little White Eagle! I think it’s time for me to ask for new henchmen to assist me. After I finish recovering I, will take care of the White Eagle on my own!"

She subconsciously glared at where Garen had stood. With hatred in her eyes, she said,

"If this skilled fighter had not shown up and weakened me, I’m certain that tomorrow would be the death of Lily!"

"Master 10" The tiny women spoke softly, "your plan is to force Lily into a corner and take care of her. However, Lily’s personal disciple, the White Eagle, was able to escape from Canary’s hands in the previous encounters. This has proven to be a hindrance to the organization’s plan. I personally think that things couldn’t be so coincidental every time. What if…"

"Are you implying that…" The expression of the purple-eyed lady dimmed. She glanced over toward the man in black suit. "Canary, do you have anything to say?"

"Are you suspecting that I let them go intentionally?" the man replied in disbelief. "I have no reason to do so!"

"I will see things through. Dale Quicksilver and the White Eagle are just secondary. Either of you can go to take care of them. The main mission now is to take care of Lily. She has been an obstacle for the organization for years now. Everything will be easier once we get rid of that old lady. Without her, the puny detective won’t dare to stand against us." Number 10 of the Golden Hoop said coldly, "Be gone now you two! Have the brothers outside take care of the corpses. We leave now!"

The two did not dare say a word and left the living room immediately.

Standing in the rain, the man named Canary stared at the sword mark on his chest in dismay. He was not affected by the fact that he was suspected by the woman in the black suit.

"Lola, Master 10’s Body Hardening Technique has reached the point that not even a bullet can pierce through. What monster did she meet that can be on par with her level?"

"Who knows?" The tiny woman seemed to be chewing something in her mouth. She answered half- heartedly, "Senior Sister 10 hasn’t been in a situation this bad for a few years now. Things are getting more and more interesting."

A group of henchmen in black suits moved rapidly toward where the duo were standing. The woman walked forward and started assigning them their tasks. Those who went in the lobby to move the corpses lying on the ground each wore a golden ring on their ear. Their movements were swift and tidy, yet silent.

*********************

Garen jogged slowly under the rain. The mist from the rain only allowed him to see within a range of 10 meters of his surroundings.

He followed the shortcut in the forest that led directly toward Canoe Town. He felt the numbness fading away, yet there was still some left in his body that he could not seem to cleanse.

Raindrops kept falling on his body. The atmosphere was oddly cold and quiet. The air that he breathed in slowly reduced the heat within his body.

Vapors emerged from his body, signifying that his body temperature was overheating.

He wiped his face and smeared makeup all over his hand.

"The makeup is gone and I did not get the antique either. I should just go straight to the dojo and clean up before heading home."

He left a note for Dale Quicksilver and the White Eagle before leaving. He decided to head back first and then return to the Silversilk Castle with them tomorrow. This decision proved to be useful in the long run.

"Lying with the note will definitely raise Dale’s suspicion." Garen jogged while formulating a plan in his mind. "Screw worrying, he will discover my identity sooner or later. Still, who is that lady that I’ve just met? If it wasn’t for the remaining attribute points, I’m afraid I would be crawling my way home now. I can’t believe that there is such a vicious lady within the Golden Hoop. How did the White Eagle face off against them previously?"

He suddenly recalled the Bronze Cross Emblem he had left in the room on the second floor.

"Hopefully the Golden Hoop will have a taste of the Silversilk Castle. Hehe." he sneered, before holding his hand over the abdominal injuries and coughing vigorously.

Ever since he began training, his body strength had been growing more potent. Simultaneously, he perceived that the desire residing in his body was building up like a volcano. It felt as if he could erupt at anytime. The effort put in training combined with his extraordinary ability had provided him tremendous power, yet this power had never got the chance to show itself. It was as if there was a time-bomb planted inside Garen’s heart, waiting to explode.

Though the injuries he had suffered this battle were unlike any before, it helped to relieve the suppressed force within Garen’s body.

"I will definitely defeat you the next time I meet you!" Garen shrugged when he recalled the purple-eyed lady. He clearly understood his current condition and was plainly not relieved.

The moment he tried to laugh he felt the pain surging through his abdomen, killing his mood.

"Damn it!" He punched the tree beside him to release his anger.

Crack!

A tree large enough for a person to hug now had a hole in its body. The insides could be seen covered in whitish-yellow tree sap. Some of it gushed out from the trunk, but was immediately washed away by the rain.

Garen did not waste his time looking at the tree. Instead he sped up his pace and ran toward Canoe Town.

After this battle, he could measure his current Potential level.

With his total strength, he should be on par with the purple-eyed lady, stronger than Third Senior Brother, but far weaker than Second Senior Brother and First Senior Sister. As for the Grandmaster, his strength should not exceed First Senior Sister since he had aged and his power should be waning.

Garen was excited to find out how his strength would be ranked according to the standard criteria. He decided that he would take the ranking exam to see which rank he can reach after concluding the Silversilk Castle exploration with Dale and the White Eagle.l.

"E"

[First Senior Sister and Grandmaster are said to be at Rank E. Anyone who reaches a letter rank is above the normal standard. Judging by this, I think I can be ranked by the amateur standard? I suppose I am not even at lowest letter rank.]

Garen had some doubt in his heart. He had the impression that First Senior Sister and Grandmaster were beyond what they showed on the surface. They should be at a higher level.

Chapter 59: Bodyguard 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"It’s you again…"

In the plain colored emergency room, Dr. Ash from Canoe Town was sitting besides Garen. He was carefully taking out the brass bullet head from his arm, and slowly putting it in the metal plate on the table.

Cling!

The bullet landed in the plate, making a crisp sound.

"Tsk tsk, the bullet head had gotten bent. You were very fortunate that it went through something else before hitting you, otherwise you’d be dead for sure," Dr. Ash exclaimed. "Last time your arm was dislocated, but this time you got hit by a bullet. Did you meet some bandits?"

"Yes." Garen nodded. "If I wasn’t this lucky, I’d be done for. All of those bandits were wearing golden earrings. They stole all my antiques as well. If I hadn’t trained in martial arts, I’d be dead for sure… Ouch!"

He moaned as the bullet in his stomach was removed. Dr. Ash dropped it in the metal plate.

"Those cursed bandits! The residents of our town also get robbed by them frequently, and we end up having to pay them every time." Dr. Ash shook his head hopelessly. "You should report this to the Huaishan City Police department, a case like this isn’t solved in one or two days."

He dabbed the cotton ball with alcohol and started cleaning Garen’s wounds. As the alcohol touched his injuries, Garen gritted his teeth to endure the pain.

After cleaning, Dr. Ash took out a small bottle from his bag. He dipped a cotton swab inside, and a purple colored liquid soaked it, emitting a strong smell like that of a disinfectant.

Garen endured the pain, watching Dr. Ash anoint his wounds with the medicine.

His face was bruised white and yellow while his eyes differed in size. One was small and the other big. It was so because of his makeup not getting fully washed off. But at least it was still good enough to cover up his face.

"Oh and Dr. Ash, I’ve heard that detective Dale Quicksilver has come to Canoe Town. Do you know if he’s still here?"

"Ah, Detective Dale…" Dr. Ash paused to think. "I’m not too sure either, but I did see him and two other people getting on a carriage headed to Silversillk Castle. I don’t know if they’re back."

Garen nodded in silence.

After ten minutes or so, Dr. Ash finished dealing with Garen’s wounds. Garen paid the doctor and put on his soggy jacket, ready to leave.

"Wait!" Dr. Ash stopped him from behind. "You are going back like this? Although it’s not raining outside, your jacket is still wet, you will infect the wounds!"

"No problem, I have a strong body, I’ll be fine." Garen chuckled indifferently.

"You don’t care but I care, this is my work!" Dr. Ash mumbled as he treaded inside, shorly after he came out with a grayish suit jacket. "Take this and put it on, don’t wet the wounds! Think about all the time and effort I put into binding them. Don’t forget to return my jacket!"

Garen smiled and took off his wet jacket and put on the grey one.

"Thanks, I’ll return it in a few days!"

"Hurry up and leave, don’t let them see you." Dr. Ash waved his hands impatiently. "Be careful and don’t let the wounds become infected."

Garen nodded and walked out the door with his soggy jacket in hand.

It was already dark outside. It must’ve been late in the night. Garen stood infront of the small clinic and gazed outside, listening but hearing no sound of anyone nearby.

"Woof woof."

A faint dog bark came from a distance, making the night even more lonesome and quiet.

The houses on the sides were dark, without any lights. The moonlight shone from above, showering the road with a faint light.

Garen closed the door behind him and suddenly felt exhausted.

"After that battle, I rushed here on foot, and then spent half an hour in the clinic. My body seems to be overloaded." He fixed the grey suit and strode along the road out of town.

The pitch-dark town seemed empty, the houses on all four sides standing like indistinct silhouettes. In the complete silence, Garen could only hear his own footsteps.

He stepped into a small puddle, and the muddy water splashed all over his pants.

Cursing under his breath, he continued walking along the street.

While walking down the road, Garen decided to check his attribute pane.

"I have one more attribute point, so I have to carefully consider everything before using it this time."

He reached into his pockets and touched the black jade disk, a stream of cool qi flowed into his skin. Even though it was slow, the value was in its stableness.

"The enhancement of attributes needs time to precipitate, but the improvements in techniques are immediate. My techniques right now are …"

Garen’s eyes moved up to the techniques pane.

His eyes swept past the unimportant skills such as basic archery and swordsmanship and landed on the few special techniques he had learned.

White Cloud Secret Arts: Max(level 4) Explosive Fist Arts: Intermediate. White Cloud Combat Arts: Elementary.

The option for White Cloud Secret Arts was in grey, meaning it couldn’t be improved further. Garen had reached a level of mastery that no one had achieved in the history of White Cloud Gate. Currently, only his talented second senior brother could compare to his strength.

The Explosive Fist Arts were at an intermediate level, the power of this technique was astonishing. During his combat with the purple eyed woman, he had only hit her twice, but these two contacts had severely injured her. Those hits had completely ignored her Body Hardening Technique, going through the surface and directly hitting her insides.

"People who achieve the level of Vibration are scary. It really is the counter to martial artists like me who are well trained in Body Hardening Technique. I have to be extra careful from now on," Garen warned himself.

He tried to see if he could enhance the level of Explosive Fist Arts again, but was unable to do so. There were some other requirements before he could enhance it. To level it up from elementary level to intermediate, he had had to take the body enhancing pills from the White Cloud Gate.

White Cloud Combat Arts, Garen thought about the fight just now.

"If my body wasn’t strong enough, I wouldn’t have been able to trade with her blow for blow. My combat techniques were too weak, so she could effortlessly block my attacks. If she had been more careful, I couldn’t have hurt her at all.

"If I had better combat techniques, I could use a completely different fighting style. My resilience is better than her’s, my strength is higher, so I could easily kill her," he thought to himself.

"My White Cloud Secret Arts have reached mastery, and because of it my muscles got enhanced, and I could double my defensive stats. I could fight blow for blow with second senior brother. My Explosive Fist Art is at intermediate level, only a few in the Gate being able reach this level. I also have exceptional physique and vitality. With these conditions, I still almost lost to her. If I had had the combat skills of senior sister, it wouldn’t have been like this."

Garen’s eyes gleamed. "The problem is that I have too little combat experience. I could only take the attacks from the enemy and fight back after. If she was another cautious fighter…"

He pictured a fight in his mind.

The purple eyed woman swiftly circled around him, occasionally dashing forward to promptly slice at his arms and legs. The poisonous blade paralyzing his body in a breeze.

"It seems that I have great strength but could not put it to use." He held in the temptation to enhance Vitality attribute and put his eyes on the White Cloud Combat Arts.

Cling!

The White Cloud Combat Arts jumped from Elementary to Intermediate level.

Garen’s body shivered. His limbs instantly felt more flexible and alive. It became easier to move them in all directions.

"The White Cloud Combat Arts at an Intermediate level enables the effortless use of Four Big Forms during combat. Changing forms during combat feels natural and instinctive. I wonder what the Advanced level would be like." Garen moved his body and limbs, feeling like he had complete control over the area within the radius of one meter around him.

He raised his hand and did a karate chop in front of himself.

Shoo!

He instinctively used the Shot Form. The air snapped and made a crackling sound like a firecracker.

"I could only use Shot Form with my right elbow before, but now I can freely use all Four Big Forms with any part of my body. This intermediate level is indeed stronger." Garen grinned with satisfaction.

After trying out the speed of his Four Big Forms, he was sure he could now beat two of himself from before.

"Now if I meet someone who is faster, I’ll be able handle them with my strength."

He nodded with satisfaction and quickly stepped into the darkness, on the road back to Huaishan City.

*************************

It was past 2:00 am when Garen arrived at Huaishan City. He went back straight to the dojo. He asked one of the students to inform his family and stayed at the dojo for the night. The next morning, he woke up early to put on the makeup and headed right back to Canoe Town.

"Kelly! You’re here early."

The sky at dawn was not yet bright, but grey and gloomy.

At the open-air restaurant, Garen sat at a round table with his silver suit. There was a smile in his red eyes. Grace stood next to him, dressed like a secretary, and holding a black notebook in her hands.

The two silently watched as Dale Quicksilver strolled over with a yawn.

Garen lifted a cup of coffee from the table and took a sip.

Dale fell into the chair in front of Garen. "What happened to your face? Why is it banded in gauze?" He drank a big gulp of coffee and asked. "Didn’t you say you were going back?"

"I accidentally chafed it, no big deal. What about yesterday? Was there any results?" Garen asked.

"We’ll go again today. The White Eagle has already informed Huaishan’s Police Department. I’m guessing someone should be there by noon. This is a big case with lots of casualties, so it’ll be troublesome. If I had to guess, the Golden Ring must have thought we killed their men, so we might run into some trouble at the Silversilk castle today."

Dale Quicksilver frowned with worry.

Garen’s eyebrow flinched as he thought about last night. He was a little surprised about detective Dale’s predictions. His guess on the Golden Ring’s reaction was spot on.

"What? Are they going to find trouble with the police?"

Dale chuckled. "You probably don’t know, Kelly, but this has happened more than once." He took out the smoking pipe that he forgot to bring yesterday, lit it up with a match, and sucked on it with great pleasure.

"Should I get some help?" Grace suddenly suggested.

Chapter 60: Bodyguard 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"That’s not necessary, we have enough hands this time. But Kelly, you really should stay away this time. The White Eagle and I will go with our friend. If something happens, we won’t be able to protect you," Dale Quicksilver told Garen.

"Don’t worry, I can protect myself. Don’t forget about when you gave me the black jade disk." Garen winked at Dale.

"I knew you wouldn’t give up so easily, up to you then. We are going to go down that hole and take a closer look. Oh right, take a look at this." Dale took out an old looking yellow paper from his pocket. Garen spread it out and revealed a colored oil painting.

A man was running forward on a vast grey plateau. The man was headless and facing the opposite direction. A flock of birds were flying out from his neck.

"There is more on the back," Dale Quicksilver reminded Garen.

Garen flipped the paper over, and there was another painting on the back.

A man’s rough and coarse hand reached out from underground. There was a bloody hole in the middle of this hand, and a man in a black robe stood inside this hole.

At the bottom of the painting was a line written in a language Garen did not understand.

"The line at the bottom is written in an ancient language, Archon. It means ‘To bestow goodness of heart upon mankind’." Dale’s face looked serious. "I did some research. You should prepare mentally for this."

Garen nodded mutely. He had a feeling that things at Silversilk castle could be on a whole different level of trouble.

Dale drank some coffee and continued, "We found this piece of paper under that hole yesterday. I left as soon as I found it because I immediately recognized the origin of this writing." He paused. "Archon is a language used by one of the most mysterious people in ancient times."

"Mysterious?" Garen squinted at him.

"They were always on the dark side of the world, and their powers were mysterious and enigmatic. In ancient legends, they were the symbol of the devil, blood and uncanniness, but no one had ever seen their true faces. They were called the Warlocks."

"Warlocks…" It was Garen’s first time hearing this word.

Grace mumbled in surprise.

"Those people in the myths and legends that learned how to use magic?"

Dale nodded. "Correct. It is said that Warlocks learned their magic from the devil and fear itself, that’s why it’s called magic. In the legends, they would mate with mythical creatures and give birth to offspring with powerful bloodlines. They had control of the demon arts. They blended in with common people, becoming nobles, businessmen, or even travelers. But of course, these were just myths," he concluded. "However, there are numerous people worshiping these Warlocks. It was especially common in ancient times, and I suspect that entrance was constructed by some of those people."

Garen was originally shocked by the story, but he calmed down after hearing they were merely myths and legends. He remembered the story of Warlocks from Garen’s memory. "I think I have heard of the Warlocks from stories and legends before, but aren’t those all made up? What could these worshippers possibly do?"

"Ceremonies, bloody sacrifices, making flutes of people’s femurs - these are all actions attributed to them. They’ve formed some kind of cult."

"If that’s the case, I would have even more reason to follow." Garen licked his lips. "After all, these Warlocks and their magic doesn’t really exist. The stuff down there would be nothing but men’s creation."

Dale Quicksilver nodded. "I’ve ran into cases like this before, involving ancient cults. And like you said, these things are all man made, not particularly mysterious. They are, however, gory and cruel. And since this time Golden Hoop has a part in it, the situation is more dangerous. These cults may have leftover tools from sacrificial ceremonies. They could be worth a lot of money as antiques."

"When are we taking action?"

"We are waiting for The White Eagle and his friend. We’ve asked for some reinforcements from the police as well, so we shouldn’t run into too much trouble." Dale Quicksilver looked at his watch. "It’s 6:40 right now, and they will be arriving before 10."

"Are we just going to wait around?" Garen asked.

"It’s nice to have some rest, don’t you think?" Dale Quicksilver laughed. "Don’t worry." He tapped Garen’s shoulder and said, "We have to wait until our expert on ancient traps arrives, or we cannot safely investigate that underground cave. Until then, you can have some free time with your pretty-faced secretary."

Garen chuckled reluctantly and watched Dale Quicksilver leave the restaurant. As he relaxed in the chair, he felt a sudden warmth and suppleness behind his neck.

Grace blushed behind Garen, but she did not dodge and let Garen’s head rest between her breasts.

"In my company’s eyes, I’m now your spokesperson, the key connection between you and the company. If you really want it, I won’t turn you down," she whispered.

"I don’t like to force it." Garen smiled and stood up. "We’ll be going to Silversilk castle in a bit. It’s very dangerous out there, so you have to take care of yourself. I cannot protect you."

"Don’t worry, I have made adequate preparations this time. The company has sent someone to protect us, so I’m getting some benefit by staying with you."

Grace smiled and clapped her hands. "Cynthia, what are you waiting for?"

From behind the bush outside the restaurant walked out a girl with strong and vigorous body. The girl had a girl-next-door look, wearing a low neck tight dress. This black as ink dress contrasted with her clear skin that looked like gelatin. Her lips were shining pink, and her curly brown hair trailed over her shoulders.

Garen was a little shocked by her beauty. "Cynthia, are you eighteen yet?" he asked in astonishment, concurrently glancing around the restaurant. Fortunately, there wasn’t anyone in this early. Besides his table, there was only the chubby owner, who was dozing off at the bar.

The girl’s long and slim legs were especially dazzling. She was wearing a pair of boots that almost covered her entire calves. "The company has sent me to protect you both, and there is another team of men responsible for guarding and security. Don’t you worry, Mr. Kelly, I’m already nineteen years old."

Her brown eyes were bent slightly, like those of a kitten, making it look like she was always smiling. Her ripe and round breasts along with long and firm legs made her look lively and energetic.

The girl came to stand next to Garen. "Mr. Kelly, I was sent to be your bodyguard. I will excel at any task given to me. What Grace can do, I can do better. What she can’t do… I am totally up for it as well…"

While she was finishing the sentence, she purposely straightened her back to show off her full breasts, and gave an aggressive look to Grace.

Grace’s face turned blue. She knew this was the company sending someone to replace her because she could not form a close relationship with Garen. Cynthia was a younger and prettier squad leader. She could fight better and her looks were superior to Grace’. Most importantly, she was trained as a tool to please people with authority.

"Do you think that there can only be one kind of a relationship between men and women?" Grace asked in a cold voice.

"Isn’t that kind of relationship the closest?" Cynthia replied, acting cute. She put her finger on her lips. "I can do anything for Mr. Kelly, or let him do whatever he wants to me…" She held the chair arm and slowly leaned toward Garen.

Garen stood up with a wry smile.

"All right, that’s enough. I appreciate Manuyllton Corporation’s sincerity, but it really isn’t the best time. Cynthia right? How many men did you bring?"

As he started talking business, Cynthia’s smile wavered and disappeared. "The squad has seven members including myself, sir. They have spread out and started patrolling the area. You can put your trust in us, we are professionals trained by the Weisman Trident Corporation. Your safety is our top priority. Also, after this trip, Mr. Adrian would like to have a word with you."

"Adrian?" Garen remembered hearing that name from Grace.

Adrian was the man in control of Manuyllton Corporation. The reason he sent Grace to work for Garen, and had Cynthia be his bodyguard, was to befriend the White Cloud Dojo. Most importantly, Manuyllton Corporation had some conflicts with Garen’s third senior brother, Joshua’s family, who had control of another company in the antiques business. Manuyllton Corporation had been in a disadvantage for a long time, so they might be thinking to ask Garen to ease up their relationships and escape the suppression.

"It’s about my third senior brother, right?" Garen didn’t know if Joshua would be nice enough to help. "Don’t have too many expectations, these kind of things aren’t decided by Joshua alone."

"That’s fair." Cynthia nodded, she had a trace of doubt in her eyes. Before meeting him, she thought Garen was just a sixteen-year-old high school kid, who only came to the corporation’s attention because of his martial arts talent. There was no way he could be tenacious enough to withstand her charm. As long as she finished the job and gave him a few winks in bed, everything could be dealt with easily.

But she didn’t expect Garen to have a completely different personality. His actions and his speech did not look like a high school kid’s, but resembled that of a thirty-year-old man’s. And he was completely oblivious to her seduction.

Garen nodded back to Cynthia. He knew that everything he had was based upon his identity as the disciple of White Cloud Gate. Be it Grace or Cynthia, they were only respecting him because of his position in the White Cloud Gate and not his actual strength. Although, he had never paid much attention to what others think, with his special abilities and talents, he was destined to get noticed.

Chapter 61: Exploring the Entrance 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After Garen waited for a while with Grace and Cynthia in the small restaurant, a motorcade of black cars slowly drove toward them. These cars came from a distance away from town and traveled along the roadway.

There were a total of four cars that gradually stopped by the roadside. Policemen in black uniforms stepped out, each wearing a white-rimmed helmet and black leather gloves. The man in charge wore a scarf around his neck. He had a slender physique and his height was accentuated by his black overcoat.

The man talked in an undertone with Dale Quicksilver and the others who greeted him, then looked toward Garen from afar. After a few glances, he nodded, went back to his car, and slowly headed toward the Silversilk Castle.

It was then that Garen noticed the White Eagle, clad in all black, from among the people who came from the cars. He stood near a dark-skinned, muscular man. Turning around, he and Dale Quicksilver walked toward Garen.

"Their men are here, so let's go together," Garen whispered. Cynthia and Grace didn't say anything, but both agreed.

The three of them headed toward Dale Quicksilver's crowd.

"The people from the police department have arrived. Let's follow them and head over together," Dale Quicksilver said in a deep voice as a brown pipe dangled from his mouth. "This is the Black Panther, the White Eagle's sworn brother," he said as he started introducing the dark-skinned man, who was dressed like a soldier.

"Nice to meet you." Garen extended his hand to the man and gave him a friendly smile.

"Likewise." Black Panther grinned, revealing two rows of pristine white teeth. "Your woman, she's very good."

"Umm, I think you've got it wrong. They are my assistant and my bodyguard," Garen explained, bemused. The two women behind him let out faint chuckles. "This is Cynthia. This is Grace. Cynthia is the head of my security team," he said, acquainting them one by one to the crowd.

Detective Dale's assistant, Miss Si Lan, suddenly appeared after they exchanged a few courtesies. She drove to a stop by the side of the road with a horse carriage that had four rows of seats with two seats per row and waited with a smile for everyone to get on.

"Come on or we won't be able to catch up to Sergeant Rio in the front," Miss Si Lan shouted.

Garen's group of three and the detective's group of four filled up the rest of the seats. A black car started following them when no one was paying attention. It was filled with youths wearing black overcoats and round black helmets that covered their lowered faces.

"Are those your men?" Garen looked to Cynthia on his right. The latter nodded with a smile.

Detective Dale, by merely glancing behind him, managed to figure out their origin based on the way they dressed.

"They're from Manuyllton. Your company really values you."

"Naturally, Mr Kelly is an important figure within the company," Cynthia rushed to answer. To one side, Grace frowned slightly.

"Cynthia, aren't you the bodyguard? Don't you have to be aware of the surroundings?" Grace sneered.

"Okay enough of this, let's travel quietly." Garen shook his head, speechless. Whenever there were signs of sparks like these, he would halt them.

"I am absolutely diligent as a bodyguard!" Cynthia gave a lovely smile, revealing two white canines. "You just wait and watch later."

While the three of them were chatting in the back, Dale Quicksilver, the White Eagle, and the other two in front frowned.

"Does this mean the Golden Hoop's men are in the vicinity?"

"Yes. According to master, it should be the Golden Hoop Number 10 that has come over. That woman is exceptionally powerful. Her tank-like Body Hardening Technique has almost reached the level of bullet resistance and her movements are like the wind. These skills, coupled with accurate marksmanship, make her a very tough assassin. The average person is just like an ant if they fall into her hands. She's obviously targeting the master this time."

"Master Lily should be fine, right?" Black Panther worried.

"It's alright, don't worry. Master was prepared to hide out temporarily, but that crazy woman was seriously injured by a maverick martial arts expert. She's currently still recuperating and won't be active for a few months, so we're safe for now." The White Eagle relaxed and smiled, but his face instantly sank a little. "But we can't let our guard down, the Golden Hoop Number 10 has two powerful lieutenants, Number 11 and Number 13. Both of them are extraordinarily strong and either one is significantly stronger than I am. If it weren't for the Black Panther intervening the other time, I wouldn't have been able to escape safely with the two children."

"It will be good as long as everyone is safe. Regardless of how skilled they are in martial arts, they can't withstand this many guns firing at them. We have more men this time, so safety shouldn't be too big of a concern," the detective consoled everyone. "Fortunately, I let my wife bring the two children to their granddad's, so I have nothing else to worry about."

"Sir, isn’t it risky that we're bringing Mr Kelly along this time? Our investigation probably involves an ancient cult and no one knows what trouble is in store," Si Lan asked in a hushed tone.

"It was him, the White Eagle, and I who discovered the entrance together. I'll ask him about it again later. It's true that there could be unpredictable danger within," the detective nodded.

At this moment, a cool breeze blew over as the morning sun gradually rose with its light shining on the carriage, a few rays fell on everyone's clothes and brought some warmth.

The horse carriage trundled onto a white stone bridge. Ripples constantly formed in the clear green stream under the bridge. Every now and then, red maple leaves from the maple forest by the shore would fall in the water.

Sitting in the carriage, Garen turned to his side and looked out. The grass hills by the road were covered in trees creating a bright mix of red, yellow, and dark green. There were even a few does with their fawns drinking from the stream on the shore near the bridge.

Upon hearing the clattering of the carriage, the animals merely looked up, and then continued drinking as if accustomed to the situation.

Golden ripples formed where the morning sun shined down on the water surface.

"A little past this stone bridge and we're within the sparsely populated boundaries of the Silversilk Castle. In the past, this bridge marked the border between the Silversilk Castle estate and Canoe Town," Detective Dale explained. "Brace yourselves, the Golden Hoop won't give up on the castle's secrets so easily. They've lost a lot of men for this."

The White Eagle frowned, then hesitantly said, "Sir, I don't know if I should tell you this."

"Just say it."

The White Eagle hesitated for a while. "It's not really a big deal, but when I saved the two children, I met someone who was an expert in Body Hardening Techniques. He killed a Golden Hoop leader trained in the Red Hand Fist. Most importantly, I saw from his skills that he was probably trained in the arts of the Behemoth Gate."

"The Behemoth Gate?" The detective frowned. "Even they're involved in this? Other people might have been mistaken, but you, the White Eagle, wouldn't be. You escaped the clutches of death during a duel with a Behemoth Gate master, so you must have a deep impression of it."

"I, on the other hand, think the meeting was pure chance," the Black Panther said in a low voice. "And after all, it didn't seem like he was malicious. He helped you get rid of your opponent."

"That's true," the White Eagle nodded, "but I still don't know why he would do that."

"Don't think too much about it, it was just a coincidence," the Black Panther consoled.

The carriage kept rolling at a moderate pace. Soon, they reached a hill trail which could only be traveled on foot.

Everyone stepped off of the carriage and started walking. They passed the forested hill and arrived at the gates of the Silversilk Castle.

There were policemen scattered all around the castle. By the window of a room on the first floor, the slender sergeant looked out. Beside him was a policewoman andthey seemed to be discussing something.

A police officer stood guard at the main gates. He walked over when he saw the group approaching.

"Sergeant Rio is waiting for you inside. We've secured the perimeter, but we didn't discover the body that the detective mentioned."

"Oh?" Dale Quicksilver frowned. "Looks like someone beat us to it… Come, let's check it out."

He took the lead walking toward the castle gates. Behind him were the White Eagle, the Black Panther, and also Miss Si Lan. Garen was last, surrounded by the black suits of all the bodyguards that Cynthia brought along.

Cynthia received a black shotgun and was checking its sights. Creaks could be heard while she did a firearms check.

"Have you prepared the handguns and brought the grenades? What about the explosives that I asked for?"

Her subordinate hurriedly handed her a piece of white paper which detailed the weapons and equipment they had brought.

Hearing all this, Garen and Grace felt their scalps go numb.

"Grenades… Explosives… Cynthia, are you here to be a bodyguard or go to war?" Grace murmured speechlessly.

"Given that none of us here are martial arts experts, what choice do I have? After all, this is the era of firearms. Martial arts expert? Nothing a few more guns can't solve." Cynthia casually scanned the paper in her hand, nodded in satisfaction, then pointed at a few shorter subordinates.

"Number 8, Number 11, you guys bring some men to set up an ambush around the slopes. Pay attention to the accuracy range and kill the enemy on sight. The assembled sniper rifles are still out back in the cars. Number 6, you get the equipment ready. Prepare to execute special measures at any time. And you, Number 3, how is the preparation for the explosive packets coming along?"

"Enough to blow up the whole site," the man called Number 3 joked indifferently.

"Get everything ready, pay attention to positioning, be more discreet, and avoid being discovered by the police. Even though we have legal gun permits, some troubles are best avoided."

"Yes, boss." With smiles on their faces, a few black suits dispersed while carrying the large and small crates.

Garen stood to the side feeling frustrated.

"If the Golden Hoop Number 10 reappears… Even if someone has the same level of Body Hardening Technique as me and could resist bullets, they would probably be defenseless against explosives and grenades."

He admitted to himself that he would be helpless if he was faced with more than ten guns. If a critical body part was hit — weak spots like the ears or eyes — there would be no escape from death. He also wouldn't be able to dodge bullets at close range.

He shook his head. at that moment, as a martial arts practitioner, he felt a sense of loss from being obsolete.

He kept up with Detective Dale and the group in front.

They entered the gates, and familiarly made their way to the small room that seemed like a study on the ground floor.

Dale Quicksilver and the rest, together with Sergeant Rio, were already gathered around the underground entrance, discussing something.

When they saw Garen come in, Dale and the White Eagle nodded at him and continued the discussion. Dale was talking to a heavily bearded man standing beside the sergeant.

Garen stood by, listening to Dale and the bearded man conversing in a weird dialect. One asked and the other answered, but Garen could not understand any of it. Only the sergeant would occasionally add a couple of sentences to their conversation and all three of them looked tense.

Garen walked to the White Eagle's side and whispered, "What's the situation?"

The White Eagle shook his head. "There's a problem. The expert in ancient traps said that there might be booby traps all over the underground lair. He thinks we should blast the traps with explosives first, rather than sending anyone down. He can't deactivate all of the traps and…"

Chapter 62: Exploring the Entrance 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"And what?"

"When we came over, the entrance to the lair was open. I distinctly remember that it reverted to its original state when we left. Clearly someone discovered this too."

Garen started frowning too. "That is troubling, indeed. It could be the Golden Hoop." Suddenly he smelled a trace of fragrance, like sandalwood, but fainter. "What's that fragrant aroma?"

"Eh? This scent…" Detective Dale paused his conversation with the bearded man. His expression changed. He seemed to recall something.

Suddenly his face turned and he shouted, "Everyone get out! Don't stay here!"

Everyone else wasn't clear what had happened, but out of their trust toward the famous detective, they instantly ran out of the castle.

Garen did the same, but he only managed a few strides before all of a sudden he saw stars.

"Hehe…"

Subtle laughter could vaguely be heard coming from behind him.

His scalp went numb. He instantly remembered the time he was pushed out the window. It was the same laughter.

He quickly turned back, but there was no one behind him.

"Go!" a muffled voice said beside him. Garen felt a force pulling him straight out the castle gates.

He was shocked. He looked at his surroundings, but everyone who had been around him earlier were no longer there. He was the only one left in the castle. An invisible person seemed to be running in front of him, pulling his hand and swiftly running forward.

Bang!

The gates crashed open. Garen felt dizzy and lost his balance, falling on his face onto the grass. In the cool wet grass, a gust of fresh air went into his nostrils, waking him up in an instant.

Suddenly his vision blurred. A group of people appeared on the grass lawn around him all at once. The sergeant from earlier, the expert, a few policemen, Dale Quicksilver, Si Lan, The White Eagle, Black Panther and the others. Cynthia and Grace lay by his side. They looked dizzy.

"That was close!" Detective Dale Quicksilver stood up and wiped the sweat off his forehead. He warily turned to look at Silversilk Castle. "I kept thinking that scent was naturally occurring, but now it seems that someone must have intentionally released it. This time there were more of us, so they increased the concentration. That's how everyone managed to detect it."

"What was that?" Sergeant Rio stood up from the grass lawn, panting. Everyone else followed suit. Their gaze turned to the solemn looking Dale Quicksilver.

"I saw everyone around me disappear earlier. What happened?"

"Me too! I think I heard someone laughing behind me!"

"Keep calm. Let's listen to what the detective has to say." The sergeant gestured his hands and the surroundings quieted. Everyone focused on the detective.

Garen had prepared to ask questions, but hearing what the others had experienced, he suddenly realized that their experiences were identical to his own. He was shocked, and his gaze focused on Detective Dale too.

"This is a really strong hallucinogenic scent." Dale Quicksilver looked somber. "I’ve read its description in the books, but I didn't expect to encounter this almost obsolete thing in real life."

He took a deep breath, looked at everyone around him, and said word by word.

"Mindtwister Vine. This scent is the hallucinogenic poisonous gas naturally released by the Mindtwister Vine after it matures, which is extinct according the books. It can induce hallucinations of loneliness and fear. The toxic gas released by this type of vine is usually extremely mild, imperceptible to humans. Only certain animals sensitive to smell can distinguish it."

"Mindtwister Vine…" Garen's eyes narrowed. He recalled being injured after being pushed out the first floor window when he first visited Silversilk Castle. "Looks like someone probably used the scent of Mindtwister Vine to hypnotize me first, and then took used the advantage to push me out the window when I approached it. And The White Eagle and Dale were probably hallucinating from the scent too, causing us not to see each other after we entered the room together."

"If that's the case, then someone is intentionally trying to stop us from entering the tunnel?" the sergeant asked in a hushed tone.

Dale Quicksilver nodded and started discussing the strategies with the sergeant and the booby trap expert.

On Garen's side, Cynthia and Grace had both regained consciousness. Cynthia was in fact the one who dragged Garen out of the castle earlier.

"If not for my prior training in resisting hallucinogenic poisons, I probably wouldn't have been able to drag you out of there." She smiled at Garen. "Thank me. You would have been in big trouble if not for me."

"Yes, yes. Thank god you were there," Garen said speechlessly. But it was true, Cynthia had played a significant role ever since she came. If not for her, Garen would have presumably been like the policemen who didn't manage to run out of the castle in time—passed out on the ground.

A group of people stood at the gates but didn't dare to enter. They merely looked at the two policemen lying on the ground through the gates. No one dared to rush in there, in case they suffered the same fate as the two of them.

"Quick, look over there!" a policeman suddenly yelled, his finger pointing at the roof of the second and highest floor.

Everyone looked toward where he pointed. In the second floor’s window stood a person clad in black, seemingly a pale-faced woman. She had a strange smile on her face. Her pupils were dark green, and she drooled from the corner of her mouth from time to time.

The moment they got a good look at her, the woman instantly disappeared into the shadows behind the window.

"Use a wet towel to cover your nose and mouth! Water should be able to absorb the hallucinogenic scent!" Dale Quicksilver instructed loudly.

Everyone immediately took out the water bottles they had with them, wet their clothes, and covered their noses and mouths with it.

The sergeant was the first to rush in with a handgun. He ran to the two policemen lying within the castle and started examining them.

"It's no use. They're dead…" the detective said gravely after walking in. "Hallucinogen overdose, especially at such a high concentration, coupled with internal bleeding caused by a hard blow to the back of their heads."

Everyone else followed suit and re-entered the castle.

"We can talk after we've captured that woman! I'll go first!" The White Eagle said coldly. "Black Panther, you look after Mister Quicksilver and Miss Si Lan!"

"Leave it to me!" Black Panther beat his chest. He watched as The White Eagle sprinted toward the top floor, disappearing around a corner.

Cynthia too, was holding a white handgun, shielding Garen.

The sergeant stood up. His face was grim. "Everyone, search! Kill that mad woman on the spot once you discover her!"

Obviously, the deaths of his subordinates had fired him up.

"Yes!" All the policemen gathered and pulled out their handguns, all their faces showed a hint of anger and anxiety.

Everybody was on high alert, and started to spread out across the castle grounds to patrol. More than ten men divided into groups, patrolling every nook and cranny.

Garen led Cynthia and Grace carefully up toward the first floor. A few steps in, they heard two gunshots coming from upstairs.

"Arghhh!" a scream came suddenly.

"Tom!"

"She ran toward the first floor! Quick, finish her!"

"Damn it! This maniac is too fast, I can't aim accurately!"

"She ran to the stairs!"

Garen and the other two were at the corner of the stairs when they saw a dark shadow leap from the top, floating like a black cloth, weightless.

Cynthia's reaction was the fastest. A white handgun was in her right hand in an instance. She aimed at the black shadow and pulled the trigger.

Bang bang bang bang!

She let out four shots in a row. Within a second, all four bullets hit the black shadow.

"Hehe…"

The black shadow gave a high-pitched laugh, stopped moving, then pounced at Cynthia. It seemed that the bullets had had no effect on her, and her speed was even faster than earlier.

A chunk of her black shadow split to grab Cynthia's neck like a black tentacle. It was extremely fast so it couldn't be clearly made out.

Cynthia looked calm, holding her gun and not making a move.

Bang!

This shot made the black shadow's head lurch backwards.

"Arghh!"

The black shadow gave a piercing shriek. It gave up attacking Cynthia and escaped directly down the stairs. It was gone in a flash.

Garen did not move in the back. He didn't want to expose his skills when so many people were watching, The White Eagle particularly.

Even though he really wanted to help, he refrained.

"Are you alright?" He held Cynthia by her shoulders. She started, instantly snapping out of a highly-tense state, and gasped repeatedly to catch her breath.

"So… so powerful! Her speed managed to evade four of my shots!" There were tiny beads of sweat on her nose. "But in the end, wooh… I still got one shot in."

"It's a nightmare once martial arts experts get too close. Even if your marksmanship is excellent, it's no match for a close range martial artist’s skills. Naturally, the reverse is true for long range." Garen nodded. "Come on, let's go down and have a look."

Grace stood to a side, speechless. Her marksmanship was quite good, but if she faced such an opponent, she would definitely not be able to react in time and be strangled to death. She wasn't too impressed with Cynthia's marksmanship initially, but that spontaneous reaction immediately contrasted their true strengths.

Pulled by Garen, the three of them rapidly ran down the stairs.

In the ground floor lobby, five to six policemen had surrounded the woman. They all stood with guns raised and nervously stared at the center.

The black-robed woman lay on the floor, twitching from time to time. There was a small bullet hole on the left side of her forehead. The injury was deep and had apparently injured the brain.

Garen's group, the sergeant and the others all crowded over, including Dale Quicksilver and Black Panther. Everyone was staring at the woman in the middle.

"She was shot in the head, she won't last long," Cynthia said casually as she spun her handgun in her hands. "My bullets are custom-made. Their penetrating power is extremely high, specifically intended to deal with these types of martial arts experts."

Sure enough, after a little while, the woman gave another twitch, then stopped moving completely. Her black hood fell off, exposing a full head of white hair.

"How old is this woman?" Garen was shocked.

"At least 80 or 90. I don't know how she's been living in this castle for so long," the detective said casually, while smoking his pipe. "Very few people with special constitutions are able to withstand poisoning by the toxic gas from Mindtwister Vine. But long term exposure to the hallucinogenic poisonous gas would make them lose their sanity and act like beasts. This person must have been one of those special ones."

"What now?" the sergeant asked, looking at the detective.

"Let's examine the body, see if we can discover anything from it. Then we'll enter the lair according to plan," the detective answered, removing his pipe.

"Alright. We'll follow your plan."

"The White Eagle, you protect the expert then. We'll enter the lair together, and everyone else stand guard at the entrance above." Dale Quicksilver started making arrangements.

"Sergeant, you bring two men and follow us down. We'll leave a lookout at fixed distances and link everyone up with the rope we've brought."

"What about me?" Black Panther stepped forward to ask.

"You stay above ground to protect Si Lan and the entrance."

"I want to go down too," Garen said, stepping forward. "It's such a huge underground passage. There must be a lot inside. I can find the most valuable item and bring it up!" This was his initial purpose anyway. Moreover, with the detective and the expert leading the way, he wouldn't have to worry too much about his safety.

Chapter 63: Exploring the entrance 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

His initial intention for joining this mission was to find more Antiques of Tragedy.

"Among the men here, only I can identify the value of these antiques," Garen said in a low voice.

"It’s not necessary for you to come now. Wait for us to check the surroundings first, then you can join us after we confirm that its safe," Dale Quicksilver replied.

Garen frowned with hesitation. He had a feeling that if he didn’t go down now, he wouldn’t have the chance. This feeling got stronger after he saw the mysterious green-eyed woman die.

"I still feel like I should go down. I can protect myself if I follow you guys."

"Can you really?" Dale Quicksilver turned around and stared at him. "Kelly, you are the antiques expert, your efforts shouldn’t be wasted on the expedition itself. Leave it to the professionals, that’s how this works."

Garen still felt reluctant. He turned to look at Grace and Cynthia. Both shook their heads at him.

"Fine… I’ll listen." He knew he probably wouldn’t be allowed to go down anymore. He shrugged his shoulders and walked aside.

Dale and the sergeant discussed the plan, and the men got ready to go down into the lair.

Garen stood at the door, leaning on its frame, not knowing what to do for now.

"To be honest, seeing a fascinating and mysterious place like this, I would want to go down there by myself and reveal its secrets. But …" Grace said, standing next to him.

"If you were needed, especially for their current mission, I think no one would reject your presence. But I still suggest you do not to explore with them. If this cave has a trapdoor that can seal the only entrance, it would be extremely dangerous."

As she was speaking, she lowered the wet towel covering her nose and mouth. The gas had fully dissipated by now, and everyone had put down their wet towels.

"Right, that emblem!" Garen suddenly remembered the Bronze Cross Emblem. He left the detective and his men, and headed toward the lobby.

A few policemen were still in here, patrolling around while holding their guns. These men were wearing black uniforms with a badge of a silver eagle on the left chest of their jackets. Seeing Garen come back out, they didn’t act surprised. Just casually glanced at him once and moved their eyes off of him.

Garen tried to remember the exact location of the emblem. He vaguely recalled it being at the dead body of the mysterious woman.

He approached the body and squatted down. Lightly, he picked it up and flipped her around.

The body was pushed to the side, revealing the Bronze Cross Emblem that was under it.

Garen grabbed the emblem and checked it, but didn’t see anything different. The potential qi inside was the same. He felt the increase of potential meter, but it had at most one attribute point left in it.

"Better than nothing." Garen shook his head and stood up.

"What are you doing? Who gave you permission to touch the body?" came a voice from a man nearby. The sergeant walked over with a gloomy expression. He was 1.9 meters of height, which was a lot taller than Garen.

"I just wanted to see if I could find any clues," Garen casually explained.

"This is police business, not something a common folk like you could take part in. Go rest on the side! Don’t interfere with us!" Sergeant Rio was impatient and waved his hands.

"Can I watch from the side? I may be able to help," Garen said with a smile. The sergeant’s brusque tone didn’t make upset in the slightest.

"I said this is none of your business, this is not something a private company could take part in! Get out of here and wait for them to come out!" The sergeant got more impatient. "What’s that in your hand? Give me that!"

Garen handed over the Bronze Cross Emblem.

"All right, you can go take some rest." The sergeant took the emblem and breathed deeply. He turned to talk to his policemen in a low voice.

Garen walked to the side with Grace and Cynthia.

"Looks like we are done here," Grace said casually. "If I had known this, we wouldn’t have needed to bring this many men over."

"That’s still to be decided." Cynthia smiled and looked at her wrist watch, then her brown eyes looked toward the hill. She suddenly had a confused expression.

"What’s wrong?" Garen asked.

"Someone is coming, my squad sent a signal. Let’s go check it out." Cynthia’s face turned serious, she led them out of the lobby just as a man in black came in from the gate.

"Captain Cynthia, there are people approaching, quite a few of them! They have lots of weapons," the man whispered.

"What kind of people? Can you hold them off?" Cynthia asked.

"Don’t know, but they’re all wearing golden rings in their ears. The guy leading them is wearing a white trench coat!"

"They’re the men from the Golden Hoop." Garen realized and said, "Did you see the numbers on their earrings?"

The man in black nodded. "They must all be together, the leader is a number 9."

Garen froze for a second. He just fought off a number 10 with a loss-loss result, and immediately comes a number 9. By the looks of it, their numbers were based on strength, so this number 9 had to be a lot stronger than number 10.

"What kind of weapons did they have?" Cynthia asked again.

"From pistols and rifles to daggers and swords. It’s really strange."

"Tell the two guys on the hill to stay alert, don’t let them see us. As long as we have the snipers in the vantage point, there shouldn’t be too many problems." Cynthia nodded. "We have the police on our side this time, I dare them to openly strike against the police."

The others started laughing, but Garen wasn’t convinced. Silversilk castle had to have an important meaning to the Golden Hoop for number 9 to show up so soon after number 10.

His White Cloud Combat Arts got enhanced to intermediate level, so he was confident that he could fight number 10 without trouble now. Even if she was cautious, he could still beat her with his speed and not trade her blow for blow. But this number 9, there was no information on him. Though he was definitely stronger than number 10. Thinking of this, Garen was a little hesitant.

Even if the police were with them, the Golden Hoop’s stance….

"S**t! The signal on the hill is gone!" Cynthia’s face turned cold as she glanced at the hills. "Little Seven, tell the other brothers to get back here! Our enemies might be tough this time!"

"Yes, captain!" The man in black jogged away.

"You think your men can handle them?" Garen asked in a deep voice.

"I’m not sure." Cynthia shook her head. "Our enemy is familiar with sniper tactics! We will cover your retreat."

"We will notify the sergeant." Grace was nervous too.

Garen nodded, he turned around and walked toward Sergeant Rio. The tall police officer was discussing the situation of the dead body.

"Sir, there are people coming, I’m afraid they’re up to no good!" Garen walked up and whispered.

"Our men didn’t see anything. How do you know?" Sergeant Rio frowned.

"My bodyguard accidentally saw them." Garen thought carefully before he spoke. "The Golden Hoop is up to no good, but the detective is still in the lair, right? You have to send me to get them out immediately! This is our safest plan."

"No need, our whole police department is out on this mission. If there really is someone coming, we can handle them without a problem." He waved at a police officer on the side. The man jogged over.

"Sir, what’s the order?"

"What’s going on outside?"

"What? Everything’s normal outside!" the policeman casually replied, chuckling.

"Are you sure?" the sergeant asked again.

"I’m sure, you can see for yourself sir. Our men are still on guard at the top of the hill." The policeman took out a pair of binoculars and handed it to sergeant Rio.

The sergeant took up the binoculars and looked through them at the gate. A policeman on the hill was waving to signal everything was okay.

"Our expert’s bodyguard said there are enemies approaching, what’s up with that?" The sergeant laughed and handed the binoculars to Garen. He turned around and went inside the lobby.

Garen put up the binoculars against his eyes and gazed, the officer on the hill was yawning out of boredom.

"Cynthia, are you sure someone is coming?"

"I’m sure!" Cynthia replied. "They are hiding in the shadows. My men were hiding at vantage points that could see every corner of the surroundings, and they haven’t sent back any signals in two minutes!" Her face was pale. "They are most definitely experts! Trained in assassination and camouflage techniques! Just as we speak, another two of my men went missing!"

"What do we do now?"

"Tell everyone to gather up at a vantage point, such as top floors of this castle! We should be able to hold the castle from the top. I’m already gathering my men!" Cynthia said with ferocity. "We cannot afford to spread out and go outside. Against assassins that are hiding in the dark, we must avoid our shortcomings and suppress their advantages! Otherwise our men will get eaten alive!"

Right as she finished speaking, they heard a loud command coming out of the lobby.

"Everyone! Spread out into the woods outside the castle! Report back immediately if you find anything!"

"F***!" Garen and Cynthia both cursed.

"This idiot!" Cynthia exclaimed.

"These well-armed policemen are our main force right now, we can’t afford to send them out to die!" She looked at Garen. "Sir, you have to tell the sergeant to get his men back to the castle! Otherwise we’ll be in big trouble!"

"I’ll try."

He knew how dangerous the situation was. Cynthia’s men were all well trained and extremely well equipped. If the enemy could silently take them down, then they would have an even easier time dealing with these policemen.

Even with his strength he would barely be able to take down number 10 since his wounds hadn’t fully healed yet. So if sergeant Rio and his men ran into the Golden Hoop’s men…

He turned around and walked up to the sergeant again.

"Golden Hoop?" The sergeant laughed aloud. "You sure?"

"I’m sure, one hundred percent sure!" Garen nodded. "Sergeant you must…"

"Very well, brothers! Let’s get out there and take out these little boys that call themselves the Golden Hoop! I’ve been longing to meet those rampant bastards. This time I’ll show them the might of the top fifty sharp shooters in the entire confederation! Hahaha…."

The sergeant wasn’t finished speaking when he pulled out his pistol and walked out of the lobby.

He obviously sensed something was going on and told his men to spread out just as a precaution.

The policemen answered by flooding out of the lobby, following their sergeant outside. Leaving one man behind to guard the entrance to the lair.

"These idiots!" Cynthia was irritated. "Face to face combat, the Golden Hoop might not be their match, but they are experts trained in assassination! Sir, leave them be, we have to get out of here! The Golden Hoop must be setting up an encirclement!"

Garen was also getting a headache from the sergeant and his men. He watched as they went outside and started patrolling the castle, not taking their opponents seriously.

"Sergeant Rio seems to be confident, maybe he knows a thing or two, let’s just wait and see…"

Peng! Peng! Peng!

Suddenly, the sound of heavy gunfire came from outside, immediately followed by the policemen’s screams.

"RETREAT!!"

"WHERE ARE THEY!"

"PROTECT THE SERGEANT!"

"RETREAT, RETREAT!" Sergeant Rio’s voice shouted with anger. In the continuous gunfire, he staggered as two men covered him and backed into the castle. One of the men quickly closed the half of the gate behind them.

Two more policemen ran in.

"We must retaliate! These Golden Hoop bastards! Hiding behind the shadows like cowards!" Sergeant Rio furiously reloaded his pistol with ammo.

Garen followed the sergeant to hide behind an obstruction. Black Panther came out of the backroom after hearing the gunshots. He pulled out his gun and ran to the door after seeing the sergeant’s situation.

The windows on the first floor were all shattered. Bullets were flying in from the gaps, resulting in chaos in the castle’s lobby. There were four policemen left, bent down behind the door next to sergeant Rio. They all occasionally reached for their guns and made a few blind shots.

Garen hid behind a statue of an angel, the two women behind him. Cynthia was about to charge out, nodding toward two squad members on the opposite side.

Bang!

A bullet hit the edge of the statue, scraping off some rubble from it and barely missing Cynthia.

Chapter 64: Exploring the Entrance 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Damn it! Their firepower is so strong! How many people did they send?" Cynthia's cheek was cut by a shrapnel and blood seeped out from the gash. "Stay under cover. Don't come out!"

She leaped out, did a forward roll, reclined on the ground and fired three consecutive shots upward, creating a large cloud of dust. She then got up and fired another shot.

Bang!

Someone exclaimed outside the door. A black shadow was hit and crashed to the ground. The gunfire seemed to gradually slow down, until it stopped.

Sergeant Rio roared in anger, extended his arms out, and fired a few blind shots.

Three groans could be heard coming from outside the door. More people had been hit.

Garen remained hidden behind the sculpture, listening to the sounds of gunfire steadily becoming scarcer and scarcer. Cynthia and sergeant Rio returned fire while covering each other and were able to gradually suppress the gunfire outside.

After an unknown amount of time had passed - it could’ve been ten minutes, or maybe fifteen - the shooting finally stopped.

"Has it ended?" Garen asked, quietly sticking out his head to look.

The lobby was a mess. Sergeant Rio and his men were all injured. Out of over ten policemen who had come, only two were alive now. The fates of the rest were still unknown.

The sergeant was shot in the shoulder. His coat was wrecked and half of the white shirt inside was dyed red. He was crouching by the door, gasping hard to catch his breath.

When Garen looked over, the sergeant turned his face away in shame.

Black Panther was tending to a gunshot wound on his left shoulder. He held the white bandage with his mouth and was bandaging himself. Cynthia, on the other hand, was with the two remaining men, silently arranging the equipment.

"Is Radin still alive?" Cynthia casually asked.

"No… I don't know. Maybe," one of the men replied absent-mindedly. He took a dagger and gently dug out a bullet from his thigh. There was cold sweat and popped veins all over his forehead.

"This was a heavy loss. But those guys will figure out a way to hide." Cynthia reloaded the handgun in a swift move, then took out a black shotgun from the backpack beside her and loaded a shell into its chamber.

"Now it's up to us."

Garen recovered his line of sight, hunched his back and crept toward the study. Grace wanted to follow but was held by Garen motioning for her to stay.

"I'll be fine going alone, you stay put."

"Okay."

Faced with bullets, which would be troublesome to others, he was not afraid. Even though Golden Hoop Number 10 had shot at him yesterday, it hadn’t caused any real injury. He was more concerned about Golden Hoop’s Number 9. He was sure that the real reason the other side hadn't barged in directly, even though they had an absolute advantage over them, was out of wariness toward him.

He quietly crept along the corner of the wall toward the study. He crossed the corridor and entered the dark room before straightening up.

There were several new footprints at the entrance to the cavern in the study. It was clear that someone had followed them in.

Bang! Bang!

Gunfire burst out in the lobby again.

Garen gently pressed on the bullet hole in his lower abdomen. He could still feel a slight pain. Before his wound fully recovered, he could only apply 80% of his true strength. Facing an oppponent stronger than Golden Hoop Number 9, he didn’t want to confront him directly either.

"Antiques of Tragedy are not a priority now. I need to figure out how to get out of here! I can't believe the Golden Hoop was brazen enough to directly confront the police force." He started to regret this adventure to Silversilk Castle. He was different from Dale Quicksilver and the others. He was here just for the Antiques of Tragedy, not to investigate the case.

"I need to think of a way to escape safely…"

BOOM!

Suddenly, a muffled explosion came from outside. Its force shook the entire castle.

"Go to hell, you bastards!" Cynthia shouted fiercely from the lobby. It was clear that the explosives set up by her men were detonated.

Garen relaxed slightly. With the deterrence of explosives, the people outside wouldn’t dare to simply approach. After all, they had no idea how many explosives were buried around the castle.

"I'll stay here for a while more, waiting for the detective to come out and leave together. There might be some unexpected gains…" He couldn't leave now anyway. He might as well stand guard at the entrance and wait for Detective Dale and the others. This way he might be able to get his hands on an Antique of Tragedy and then still be able to leave safely.

Garen was confident that if he wanted to retreat, neither firearms nor martial arts experts from the Golden Hoop could stop him.

He walked to the entrance. As he was about to sit down for a rest, he felt that the edge of the entrance was a little chilly.

"Could it be?" He suddenly turned serious. "Could it be that there is wind?"

He reached out with his head to the entrance and carefully felt around.

On his palm, he could feel a slight breeze flowing out from the entrance.

"There is wind indeed! There must be an exit on the other side!"

Garen stirred, his face instantly revealing his glee. He was about to stand up and go back into the lobby to inform the others, when turning around he saw a black shadow blocking the study entrance. It quietly watched him.

The shadow had a black hood on. A huge golden earring hung from his left ear, the number '9' engraved on it. By the looks of his stature, this was a strong and well-proportioned man. His face was covered with a black mask that revealed only a pair of very beautiful sapphire like eyes.

"This is the underground entrance?" the man asked softly. His voice was deep, and the accent a very standard confederal one. "He is indeed the famous Detective Dale. We've searched for so long but never managed to find it, while he located it as soon as he arrived. This is excellent."

Garen turned around fully, carefully listening to the sounds from the lobby. The gunfire was still going on. Obviously this person had sneaked in here by himself.

Without waiting for Garen to respond, the man continued to speak. "Kelly, I heard that you are an expert in appraising Antiques of Tragedy. That's perfect. Follow me down for a look. If you can prove your talent, I'll consider sparing your life."

Garen was stunned. He had just told Detective Dale not too long ago, yet the Golden Hoop had already gotten wind of it.

The man seemed to think that Garen did not believe him. He reached out with his hand toward the wall on the left and applied pressure to it.

Crack!

A slight crack instantly appeared on the wall. It was like a piece of glass that was about to break.

"This will be your fate if you don't agree."

Garen took a look at the wall. He could have produced that degree of splitting too. The castle walls have been in disrepair for years, so the stone bricks were extremely fragile. What he found strange though, was that this Golden Hoop Number 9 did not regard him as a martial arts expert, but instead thought of him merely as a normal expert with a strong build.

That move on the wall could probably work on most people, but it wouldn't have any deterring effect on a martial arts expert. Moreover, Garen was the type of martial arts practitioners who were known for their strength.

"Does he not know that I injured Golden Hoop Number 10?" Garen speculated internally, but said, "Are you the Golden Hoop’s martial arts expert? As long as you can guarantee my safety, I'm alright with it." He was planning to go down anyway.

"You've got some nerve." Seeing that Garen was not afraid, a trace of admiration flashed across the man's eyes. He nodded, took the lead by walking to the entrance, and went down the stairs step by step. "Follow me. Don't play any tricks. Even if you have trained in some martial arts, I can finish you off in a few seconds."

Garen nodded.

"Don't worry. I'm very clear about the situation." He followed the man down the stairs.

Tap tap tap…

Both of them went down the stone steps, and soon they had completely entered the underground space.

The space was cylindrical. The black stone staircase spiraled down along the wall with white chrome handrails on the side. Garen looked down past the handrails.

Below him, the staircase spiraled into an infinite darkness, like a screw thread on a cylindrical inner wall. At the center was a small black void; it seemed bottomless.

When he looked up, the entrance they had entered from was reduced to a tiny hole.

The screw-thread staircase spiraled clockwise downwards, loop after loop. Strangely, this staircase and its handrails, as well as the surrounding walls, were exquisitely decorated. The walls were engraved with fine vines, and so were the handrails. The stone staircase felt unusually level and solid, like it was built by stacking whole stones together.

They walked in a single file. The black-hooded man was in front. The back of his hood would flap up from time to time, and a faint fragrance would disperse through the air.

Garen trailed behind. When he smelled the scent, his spirits lifted.

"Here, if you're not wary about the Mindtwister Vine scent, you’ll just be walking to your death," the man walking in front of him said in a low voice. "Stay close. Otherwise I won’t be able to take care of you either."

"Okay." Garen nodded.

The two of them walked down, round and round, their surroundings seemingly never changing. If Garen didn’t occasionally look up at the gradually shrinking entrance, he would have thought they weren't too far in, just going round in circles.

He wasn't sure for how long they were walking, maybe half-an-hour or more.

Garen looked up again. The entrance was completely out of sight now. There was only darkness above. The only source of light around him was the small torch that Golden Hoop Number 9 carried in front.

The amber glow illuminated up to one loop above and below them.

The temperature in the stairwell seemed to be dropping too. Garen could see a white mist when he exhaled.

"How long do we still have to walk? It's already very cold here. No wonder you wore such thick clothes." Since the detective and the others were trailblazing ahead of them, there shouldn't be much danger in here. And now since Golden Hoop Number 9 was walking in front of him, he didn't mind anything at all. He might as well think of this as an adventure. Since he didn't know the extent of the man's powers and wouldn't be able to directly confront him in his current state, it was better for him to conceal his powers.

"These stairs are endless…" the hooded man replied in a low voice. "These are the Infinity Stairs of Ancient Endor, the stone steps leading to the realm of the dead, according to legend."

"You really believe it's endless?" Garen asked.

The man did not respond.

They continued forward in silence. The walls were black, same as the stone steps, only the handrails were white. They seemed to emit an eerie pale glow under the torch fire.

It was extremely quiet up and down the stairwell. There was no sign of the detective and the rest who’d came in first.

Walking downward silently, an unknown amount of time had passed until there was a change of scene in the monotonous stairs ahead of them.

There was a stone table leaning on the wall to their left, and on it was a square fishtank.

Sealed. It was half full with water, and some fish could vaguely be seen inside.

The hooded man put down the torch and went up for a look.

The water in the fishtank was already dark green, like slimy sewage water. The three to four dead goldfishes inside were not golden-red anymore, but instead covered in dark green, floating dead on the surface of the water.

"I didn't expect there to be goldfish in here…" Garen was confused. "So deep in."

"There will be more unexpected things down here," Golden Hoop Number 9 said indifferently. He raised the torch and continued forward.

Garen walked past the fishtank. He couldn't help but give it another look, then keep up with the man.

"Since it's a fishtank used to keep goldfish, why would it be sealed?"

"This was a simple ancient ritual. Seal up life, let it slowly die inside until it decomposes completely and fully integrates with the other ingredients. The seal will be broken when the time comes, and the content inside would be consumed. The life, blood, flesh, and soul would all be eaten. According to legend, this was a ritualistic method to attain immortality," the man explained casually.

"How disgusting." Garen was speechless.

Chapter 65: Change 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Ancient Endor had many such disgusting practices. That was just one of the many inexplicably strange traditions that remains from the history of that grand bygone empire," Golden Hoop Number 9 calmly replied.

The two did not speak much after that and continued walking downward.

It was getting colder. A thin sheet of frost started to appear on the white chrome handrails. The breaths they exhaled visibly formed two white strands, then gradually dispersed into the air.

"Be careful," Golden Hoop Number 9 suddenly said.

Puzzled, Garen looked at him. Then he looked down to the front of the stairs and discovered a black uniformed policeman sprawled on the steps with a short black arrow pierced through his throat. He was slumped motionlessly against the wall. Blood flowed out slowly from his lower body, dripping bit by bit into the infinite darkness.

"The temperature is too low so his body temperature dropped too quickly." Golden Hoop Number 9 crouched to examine the body. "But he shouldn't have been dead for more than twenty minutes. Looks like the detective and the others shouldn't be too far ahead."

"If you meet Detective Dale, what do you plan to do?" Garen asked from behind.

"If he knew his place, I would spare him as well," Golden Hoop Number 9 answered casually.

As they stepped over the policeman's corpse and continued on, their crisp footsteps continuously reverberated in the silent space.

Bang!

A gunshot rang out from the darkness below, followed by a faint yelp.

"Quick, run!!" a voice shouted.

Golden Hoop Number 9’s expression changed. He sped up and ran downward. Garen hesitated for a moment, then jogged in pursuit.

Detective Dale and the rest soon appeared on the staircase in front of them. Stunned, they stood on the steps and looked down the stairs.

Garen followed their line of sight and looked ahead. The steps in front were like thin spinning plates, revealing the dark empty space below as they systematically revolved. There was a normal step every five steps, but the rest of the steps were constantly and rhythmically rotating.

The person who approached had to keep leaping forward. Otherwise, once they stepped on a revolving step, they would immediately drop through, get caught between the revolving stone steps, and be crushed to bits.

One of Dale Quicksilver's leather shoes had been clipped into two halves. He was with the White Eagle. The booby trap expert was behind them and a young policeman was protecting Miss Si Lan.

Apparently, the sergeant had refused the initial arrangement to follow them because he wanted to marshal and command the police force. Instead, Si Lan had volunteered to follow the detective and the others to this place.

The five of them heard footsteps coming from behind them. When they looked up, they saw that Garen was slowly walking over with a black-hooded man. The man caught their eye due to wearing a black mask over his face and a golden earring engraved with the number '9'.

"It's one of Golden Hoop's men!" The White Eagle reacted quickly, drew his gun, and aimed at Golden Hoop Number 9.

"Keep calm." Golden Hoop Number 9 was unfazed as he looked at the group in front of him. "I think our motives should be aligned: we all want to find out the secret of this underground passageway, correct?"

"So you mean…?" the detective asked with a somber expression.

"Cooperate, of course. You help me explore this cavern and I can provide you with a lot of valuable information. Rest assured, you'll be at the bottom soon enough." There was an unusual calm in the eyes of Golden Hoop Number 9, without a trace of ripples.

Detective Dale pondered for a while. No one knew what he was thinking.

"Alright, you have a deal," he actually agreed.

Everyone else looked bewildered and even Garen who was at the back was stunned.

"Word is that Golden Hoop Number 9 is someone who doesn't break his promises. I trust you." Dale Quicksilver ignored everyone else's expressions and directly addressed Golden Hoop Number 9.

"You know me well."

"Naturally."

"Let's move on then." Golden Hoop Number 9 smiled and suddenly lightly rapped the wall to the left.

Wham.

The revolving steps before them stopped spinning and froze completely.

"Great, let's move on."

He led Garen directly to the front. When they passed the group of five, the White Eagle and Si Lan looked extremely nervous. They were clearly angry when they saw Garen trailing behind.

Garen gave both of them a wry smile and shrugged helplessly. It was just as well if he walked together with everyone else.

At the front, Golden Hoop Number 9 did not seem to mind. He walked on alone at a moderate pace and soon only the amber glow from the torch in his hand could be seen.

"Why don't we head back now?" Garen suggested in a whisper.

"We can't escape. Golden Hoop Number 9 is extremely swift and silent, so it's impossible for us to escape." Detective Dale looked calm. "Come, let's keep up."

He took the lead in catching up. Everyone behind him looked at each other and could only continue.

Garen and the White Eagle walked together. As he reported on the situation above ground to the rest of them in an undertone, the atmosphere in the group turned bleak.

"We're in a really sticky situation right now. Fortunately, the one we've encountered is Golden Hoop Number 9. He’s a relatively unique presence within the entire Golden Hoop organization. If the key was in anyone else's hands, it would be much more problematic," Si Lan analyzed in a hushed tone. "I'm just not sure what Mister is thinking."

"Don't worry about it. Mister won't be wrong. Let's just keep up," the White Eagle said while frowning.

The policeman held the trap expert by the arm. The trap expert was so cold he was shivering and could not utter a word. Both of them tried to warm themselves with the torch fire, but it did not help.

Since they were now under duress from the Golden Hoop, they did not dare say anything, so they just gritted their teeth and went along.

It was unclear how long they kept walking down the staircase. Golden Hoop Number 9 would hit and knock on the walls from time to time, as if he was very familiar with the surroundings. They did not encounter any other booby traps along the way and soon the bottom could be seen.

At the end of the stairs was a small circular open space. On the black floor, there were three gray leather sofas arranged in a triangle and covered with a thin layer of frost. Not far from the open space was a grubby fireplace and the coal inside was also covered by frost.

There was a bookcase, but it was completely empty.

When he reached the last step of the staircase, Golden Hoop Number 9 stopped in his tracks. He stood on the step and did not walk down.

He furrowed his brows and slowly reached out his right hand which had been hidden under the cloak. He slightly flicked his wrist and something black could be seen between his fingers.

The black object flew out and landed on the black floor of the open space.

Woosh woosh woosh woosh…!!!

A dense flurry of arrows fired out from both sides, shattering the black object. Countless short black arrows punctured the floor.

Golden Hoop Number 9 tossed out another black object and triggered another shower of arrows.

After three consecutive instances, the holes in the walls on both sides finally sealed themselves up, and there was no more movement.

The crowd behind him was stunned. All in all, there must have been up to 1,000 short arrows released and the tip of each one glowed with a trace of purple.

"The short arrows have all been released," Golden Hoop Number 9 said casually as he crouched down and removed his hood. Unexpectedly, he had a white rat in his left hand and gently placed it on the black floor.

The mouse gave a few squeaks and scurried towards the sofas.

It traveled few steps in before its body suddenly plunged downwards. It sank into the ground. The white rat squeaked wildly, but it was no use. Suddenly, a black wire dragged it up and flung it back into the arms of Golden Hoop Number 9.

The tail of the rat was coiled with strands of black wire. It would have been easily missed if one did not look carefully.

Golden Hoop Number 9 gently soothed the white rat, then stood up.

"In front of us is the Swamp of Malice, one of the booby traps used in Ancient Endor to punish thieves. Only thieves and cowards with malicious intent will be caught in the swamp."

"What is your motive then?" Detective Dale questioned softly.

"Of course it's…that." Golden Hoop Number 9 did not turn around, but directly strode down the steps.

"Wait…!!" The booby trap expert was about to stop him, but was dumbfounded when he saw that Golden Hoop Number 9 was still standing firmly on the black floor and had already walked to the three sofas in a few steps.

In the middle of the group, Garen looked uncertain.

Just as Golden Hoop Number 9 approached the sofas, Garen suddenly felt a stream of mild warmth permeate through his skin into his body. It was Potential, a small amount of Potential.

Snap.

Golden Hoop Number 9 stood between the sofas — it was unclear what he did — but clicking sounds slowly came from the black floor.

Surprisingly, a light gray stone table gradually rose up from the floor in front of the fireplace.

The stone table was cylindrical and there were four owl sculptures around it. On the table was a black hardcover book.

There was finally a trace of excitement in the eyes of Golden Hoop Number 9. He strode towards the gray stone table and reached for the black book.

Bang!

A gunshot rang out. A smoking bullet hole suddenly appeared on the ground at his feet.

Golden Hoop Number 9 stood in his place and looked over his shoulder at the crowd.

"What are you doing?"

The White Eagle stood in front of Detective Dale Quicksilver with his gun raised and a solemn expression on his face, but he was not the one who spoke.

The detective's gaze silently concentrated on Golden Hoop Number 9.

"If my guess is correct, that book is your ultimate goal. Am I right?"

"Indeed." The man nodded without hesitation. "I am grateful that you helped us find this underground entrance, but my gratitude is that I let you all go. Since we are on opposing sides, I should directly kill you to rid my organization of trouble. You understand."

"You can't kill us." The detective smiled. "The booby traps here are no joke. If my guess is right, that book is the legendary Book of Silence. If this treasure fell into the Golden Hoop's hands, it would be as if a lion grew wings. The consequences would be disastrous."

"This book is not for the organization." Golden Hoop Number 9 smiled. His body jerked forward then swayed abruptly left and right. He grabbed the book and leapt from the spot. Like a black bat, he flew up and hung by the side of the upper staircase. With a somersault, he was on the staircase one level above their heads.

"Don't move!" Detective Dale halted the White Eagle who was ready to spring into action.

Suddenly, like a forest of skewers, a dense bunch of black spikes protruded from the ground. The sofas were instantly punctured with numerous holes. The White Eagle was so frightened he broke out in a cold sweat.

It was only then that the detective looked at the booby trap expert to his side.

Chapter 66: Change 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"It’s my fault." The expert’s face turned ghastly pale, he shook his head. "I was one step too slow, the strength needed to activate this trap was slightly higher than my expectations." He looked at the stone floor tile below his feet.

"Kelly is gone!" Ms. Si Lan suddenly shouted out.

"He will be fine. No matter who acquired that book first, Kelly will be safe. They both need him to identify the authenticity of it," the detective said, shaking his head.

"Who are you talking about?" The White Eagle lowered his gun.

"Behind us, behind Golden Hoop Number 9, there are people following us." Detective Dale whispered, "Let’s get going, keep walking. It’s too cold here, we won’t be able to hold for long."

"So earlier, you were purposely talking to Golden Hoop Number 9 like that?"

"Of course I was. Unfortunately, he didn’t realize this fast enough." The detective smirked.

***************

On the spiraling stone stair case, there were two silhouettes sprinting and chasing after one another.

Someone was held under the arm of the first silhouette. It was Garen in his black suit.

The one sprinting and carrying him was Golden Hoop Number 9, who had left the scene earlier. His cloak flapped behind him like a dark cloud floating in the air. It covered Garen almost completely.

Bang!

A gun’s barrel appeared around the corner of the stone wall, pointing at Golden Hoop Number 9. The silhouette made a few backflips on the railing, landing in front of him, and now stood with a pistol in each hand.

"I guessed it right, Number 9, you want to keep the Book of Silence to yourself." The man laughed grimly as he blocked the way. He lowered his head and stared at Garen and Number 9 with a sinister smile.

"So it’s you…" Golden Hoop Number 9 put Garen on the ground. "I didn’t expect the organization to be this suspicious of me. They sent you to spy. It’s a pity… I didn’t want to kill anyone."

"We’ve worked closely for many years, I didn’t want to do this either, but you betrayed us first." A golden ring hung on the man’s left ear, it was numbered 8. He was a rank higher than Number 9.

Both of them sneered without saying a word, and suddenly grappled each other.

There was no distinct sound of impact. They fought and tangled together, like two pieces of black cloth twisting and chafing. There was only the sound of friction as they jumped and dashed around the stairs.

Garen stood behind them on, watching the fight without blinking.

A while ago, he had let Golden Hook Number 9 take him hostage, so that he could find out where the potential qi was coming from. Now, he had it confirmed, it was from that book in a black cover.

It was the same type of antique as the Black Jade Disk, emitting Qi slowly instead of releasing it all at once.

"Should I wait for them to finish fighting and go plunder it then, or should I leave at once and wait for them to come to me for identification?" Garen hesitated.

The problem with waiting for them to bring the book to him for identification was that the Golden Hoop might have their own ways of confirming its authenticity. Thus, this method might not work.

He also didn’t want to get more involved in the Golden Hoop’s business. Pretending to be Mr. Kelly was only to find Antiques of Tragedy. But using brute force would risk his own safety, especially since the Golden Hoop already knew he was Garen. This could bring harm to his family.

"Catch!" Suddenly, a hurried shout came from the front. Garen didn’t get a chance to respond when he saw the Book of Silence hurled toward his face.

He franticly reached for the book, catching it. A flow of warm qi drifted from the book into his body, and the potential meter at the bottom of his vision started to slowly but steadily grow.

"Keep the book for now, whoever wins will come to you for identification!" Golden Hoop Number 9’s voice came from below.

After that, the two Golden Hoop members left Garen alone and fought their way down the stairs. Soon, they were three levels below Garen.

"Looks like I have to stay here for now."

Garen cupped the book in his hands. The Book of Silence had a pitch black cover with a white eye printed in the center. He flipped it open and found the cover to be made of stone.

Garen’s pupils narrowed as he turned to the first page.

That page contained a drawing. There was a man, a naked man. The weird thing was, the back of the man’s head was connected to a maggot’s body. It looked like a long white tube, and shared the same head as the man. The worm’s body was shining white, reaching down to the man’s thighs, and it was even slowly wriggling.

"It’s wriggling?" Garen closed his eyes and shook his head. When he looked again, the wriggling motion in the drawing had disappeared.

The strange man’s creepy green eyes were staring at him as if he was alive. It made Garen feel lightheaded.

When Garen finally composed himself and was ready to flip to the next page, a shadow flashed in front of him.

"Give it to me!"

A strong force gripped the Book of Silence, trying to snatch it from Garen’s hands. Suddenly, another silhouette raced toward Garen and quickly grabbed the Book of Silence by the other end.

Stunned, Garen instinctively held the book with all his strength. The sound of tearing came from his hands.

"If I can’t get it, nobody will!" Golden Hoop Number 9 ranted in an exhausted voice.

The Book of Silence was torn apart under the pressure of being pulled in three directions. The pages went flying in the air. Golden Hoop Number 9 held a short sabre in his hand and effortlessly slashed all the pages into pieces. A fireball emerged from his left hand, instantly igniting all the flying book scraps.

"Number 9, you’re insane!" Golden Hoop Number 8 tried to stop him, but was one step too slow. His fist struck Number 9, and the latter slowly slumped down against the wall.

It was a shame that the Book of Silence was destroyed and burned, but Garen did not want to get involved in Golden Ring’s internal conflicts. If he could find an Antique of Tragedy once, it was likely that he’d find another at some point too.

While regretful, he still backed off a few steps. As the two Golden Hoop members continued wrestling once more, Garen silently left up the stairs.

"What a mess." He was speechless. "But at least there were some gains. I found the picture of me traveling through an alternate reality. If what that book said was true, I must be the lucky survivor. It had to be at an exact time, and I was lucky enough to be there."

Things had taken an unexpected turn, and Garen’s primary target was destroyed. He didn’t get the Antique of Tragedy he came for, but instead got into a conflict with Golden Hoop Number 10.

He looked down the stairs at Golden Hoop Number 9 and Number 8. Number 8 was standing a few steps up, his face distorted with fury. Below him, Number 9 stood with a black stone in his hand. It was the white eye on the cover of the Book of Silence.

"Hand it over!" Number 8 said as he extended his hand.

"This is a legendary rune with mysterious power! You think I’ll just give it to you?" Number 9 laughed. "I had plotted for so long, and I’ve finally got what I wanted!"

Both of them had bloodstains on their bodies. But Number 8 looked quite normal, whereas Number 9 had blood streaming out of his mouth. Apparently, he had serious internal injuries.

Garen watched as they argued. His heart suddenly missed a beat when he realized that the flow of potential qi had not disappeared with the Book of Silence.

"Is it because of that rock?" His eyes landed on the white-eyed rock they were fighting over.

"The book was only about some cult’s legends and nonsense. The real treasure was this rock, you think I didn’t notice?" Golden Hoop Number 9 sneered. "I might not know what it could be useful for, but since it’s in my hands… don’t think about getting it back!"

Garen knew if he didn’t go right now, he would get involved in their internal conflicts. The more he knew, the more trouble he was in. As the two were still talking, he slowly backed off up the stairs.

As valuable as Antiques of Tragedy could be, he could not afford to get involved. Unlike last time with Number 10, this time they already knew his true identity.

Before he could walk further, Golden Hoop Number 9 acted first and erupted into a black shadow, racing up the stairs. Behind him, Golden Hoop Number 8 followed closely. The two were speeding past Garen.

Number 9’s face was as pale as paper, he couldn’t hold for much longer.

Garen squinted. To be honest, he had a favorable impression of Golden Hoop Number 9. Since the beginning, this guy had not done any harm to him, but protected him ever since they got into the lair.

At this moment, Number 8 was sweeping past Garen. His physique was larger than Number 9’s and could not get past Garen’s body on the stairs.

"Get lost!"

Number 8 was furious, his hand slapped at Garen with inertia. His fingers were gleaming with blue light; he must have learned a venomous technique. As his hand approached, a sharp and foul odor came with it.

Garen’s speed might not be faster than theirs, but he was able to block the attack at this range. He hadn’t wanted to fight them since he really didn’t want to get involved, but now that the opponent obviously wanted to kill him, rage surged in his heart.

"You’re courting death!" Garen growled as he raised his right arm and grabbed.

Ssss…

His arm instantly inflated and swelled up, doubling in size. His veins and muscles intertwined and inflated to at least a half-meter radius. It didn’t look like a human arm anymore.

His hand clashed against Number 8’s blue hand like the claw of a bear clashing with the hand of a baby.

Bang!

The two immediately separated after the impact, but Number 8 still had the strength to grab Number 9 with his other arm and used inertia to throw him back.

Number 9 was dragged down and landed next to Garen.

As the two bumped into each other, Golden Hoop Number 9 reached into Garen’s arms, acting like he was giving something. He then pushed Garen away while shouting, "Take it and go!" He himself immediately turned and tumbled down the stairs.

"You!"

Garen froze. Number 9 didn’t give him anything at all, and yelled like this only to mislead Number 8. He looked up at Number 8, who was furiously boring down on him like a dark cloud.

"He didn’t give me anything!" Garen shouted out.

"I’ll find out after I kill you!" Number 8 smirked.

"S**t!" Garen was livid. He hadn’t plan on fighting with the Golden Hoop, but now he was randomly involved. "You idiot! There’s an exit down there! He just wants me to slow you down! You really think he was injured that much?"

The two clashed with each other again. After the muffled sound of impact, Garen stood still, and Number 8 backed off a few steps.

"Indeed very strong, like it said in the intelligence report!" Number 8’s face slightly twitched, his left hand was shaking behind his back, but one couldn’t tell it from his straight face.

"That damned Number 9 framed me! I have nothing against the Golden Hoop! Let’s go down there and deal with him first, then you’ll find out where the antique is!" Garen said, enduring the prickling pain in his palm. He used the White Cloud Secret Arts on his hand, which made the skin too rough to be poisoned, but he still felt a slight uncomfortable numbing pain in his hand.

"You think I would trust you?" Number 8 replied.

"I’m coming along, what’s your problem?" Garen was now seriously angry. "I don’t want your stuff, but I can identify the item for you. You know who I am, you know where I live. Even if I run away, there’s still my family and friends. What are you so afraid of?"

Number 8 stared at Garen for awhile, then finally agreed. "Fine, I’ll trust you this time!"

"We have to hurry, he must know of a secret exit for him to fall down like that," Garen said ruthlessly. This was the first time he got used and framed by someone else. He quickly ran down the stairs.

"No s**t!"

Number 8 twisted and jumped down the stairs after Garen. The two quickly disappeared in the darkness.

Chapter 67: Alleviation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s current plan was to make use of the excuse of need to identify the eye shaped stone for a while, and keep the stone in his hands a bit longer; that would count as a way to absorb the potential.

To get away from getting suspected, he voluntarily asked Number 8 to chase after Golden Loop Number 9 with him, because the opponent intentionally pushed the blame onto him.

No matter what happened, he had to find Golden Loop Number 9 to clean himself from the blame. However, he knew that even if he was clean, Number 8 still won’t let him go; maybe that his identification technique would protect himself, but it wasn’t secure enough.

"The best case would be that they two kill each other during a fight!" Garen rushed down as a vicious expression flashed though his eyes.

Golden Loop Number 8 followed behind him closely. He had a small torch in his hand, and he used his cape to block off the wind that might extinguish the fire. The two of them were only about a meter apart; they could barely see what was in front and behind them.

Soon, a white stone gate that was half open suddenly appeared on the stairwalls. Peeking into it, Garen wouldn’t see anything; it was pitch dark and cold breezes were blowing out of the gate.

Garen quickly stopped his steps, and caught up on his breath.

"It’s the natural wind! They probably left from here!"

Golden Loop Number 8 had thought everything through by this point. He knew that he was tricked. Garen didn’t have to say much; Golden Loop Number 8 dragged opened the gate and entered.

A few strange expression flashed by Garen’s face as he followed Number 8.

There was a stone room behind the stone gate. There was a thick layer of dust on the ground, and there was a series of clear footprints leading forward, and these footprints disappeared as they got to wall on the right.

Golden Loop Number 8 walked up to the wall and rubbed it, however, he wasn’t able to find any mechanisms on the wall that would open up any hidden paths.

"Shit!" He punched the wall, and it made a loud "Bam" sound.

"There is still wind! There must be a way out!" Garen said calmly: "We need to find the ventilation exit."

Number 8’s eyes shined; he was very anxious and didn’t think out that. He started to look for the ventilation exit after he was reminded.

Garen stood there and didn’t move; he just watched as Number 8 searched.

What’s the use for the stone? Do you Golden Loop folks know?"

"Hehe, aren’t you afraid that you will die sooner knowing more?" Number 8 searched as he laughed. It seemed like he suddenly found the mechanism; he lightly pushed into the wall.

Crack! A small door flipped open on the wall.

At the moment where the door flipped out, a short sword pierced at Golden Loop Number 8 quietly.

Tink!

The short sword hit the barrel on Number 8’s Gun.

Number 8 took a big step back and raised his gun to shoot.

Bam! Bam! Bam! Bam!

After four shots, there weren’t any more movements inside the darkness behind the small door.

"He escaped, we have to chase!" Number 8 roared, but he didn’t move. He looked at Garen who was standing beside him; his intention was obvious, he wanted Garen to go first.

"The stuff isn’t mine, I don’t really care!" Garen sneered. His strength wasn’t as strong as these two people; with the injuries, he was only able to use 80% of his strength. There was no way that he could win against any one them. If he chased into the darkness, he won’t get used to it at all.

Although it was also dark in the stone room, but there was still some light, unlike the space inside that little door. At least Golden Loop Number 8 had a torch.

For a moment, the two of them froze inside the stone room. Number 8 knew that he wasn’t able to order Garen around, but he didn’t dare to rush in recklessly.

"If we delay it longer, he would be gone!" Garen said coldly.

Golden Loop Number 8 stared at him, bit his teeth, took of one of the two guns he had, and threw it into the space behind the small door.

The gun swirled in the air as it entered the darkness.

Bam!

After a gun noise, a small red flame lit up darkness inside the door. The gun exploded instantly! At the same time, there was a vague humph sound, followed by staggering footsteps.

Golden Loop Number 8 sneered. He didn’t say anything and rushed into the door. He used the cape to protect his body against the flame, and disappeared into the darkness.

Garen didn’t follow up. He saw what happened clearly; Golden Loop Number 8 shot the handle on the first gun using the second gun! The handle of the first gun was filled with explosives, and it acted like a bomb when it was shot.

Although the explosive was weak, but the sound of the explosive would shock and temporally disable one’s ear in that small space. Golden Loop Number 9 must have been hurt by that.

Therefore, Golden Loop Number 8 had no time to deal with Garen. He rushed in and chased after Number 9; he had to kill Number 9 before he recovered.

Garen knew that there was nothing for him to do anymore. He didn’t want to get involved in this in the first place. Since now both of Golden Loops were fighting again, it was time for him to leave.

As he was about to turn around and leave, he suddenly felt a familiar flow slowly drilling through his skin.

"This is….. Potential?!" He glanced around in surprise. There wasn’t any light, the surrounding was dark, he couldn’t see anything.

Garen slowly walked around as he leaned against the wall; soon, he arrived at the place where the potential energy was the thickest.

He slowly squatted down at the corner of the room; there was a piece of black cloth nailed against the ground, and it was covering something.

Because it was dark, and it was at the corner, both Golden Loop Number 8 and Garen didn’t see it. The potential energy as very thin at where Garen was standing at; Garen didn’t feel it at all when he was all tensed up. After calming down, he just noticed it. Apart from the Black Jade Disk, there was this source of slowly flowing into his body.

"Could it be?" Garen’s heart started racing. He slowly uncovered the black cloth, and a white stone revealed itself. The stone was in an eye shape; it also looked like a fish. It quietly laid on the black floor. Garen picked it up and rubbed it. Although he couldn’t see it clearly, but he knew that this was there the potential energy was coming from. From the shape of it, he knew that it was probably that white eye shaped stone.

"If it wasn’t the potential energy that helped me locate it, anyone else wouldn’t have been able to find it!" Garen quickly put the "white eye" into his pocket.

He stood up and walked toward the entrance.

There was still the smell of gas and smoke that came off of the torches left it the air; it was thick.

"It’s probably the detectives who just passed by."

Standing at the entrance of the stone room, Garen turned his head around and looked behind him as a sneer appeared on his face.

"One intentionally framed me, one wanted to kill me casually. Both of them are bad eggs. Unfortunately, I could get rid of them if I’m a bit stronger! I won’t let them get away easily."

He rubbed the white eye shaped stone in his shirt pocket as he thought of something. At the same time, he quickly ran up.

After a few minutes…...

A black shadow suddenly rushed out of the little door in the stone room. The black shadow didn’t light up anything; he rushed to the corner of the room, uncovered the black cloth and reached for something.

The black shadow was stunned as it didn’t find anything. He quickly swepped around with his hands, but he still didn’t find anything.

"That Kelly….!!" He bit his teeth and said.

Vague footsteps behind him, and the black shadow quickly stood up and rushed out of the gate.

As soon as he rushed out, he felt a wind gusting at him as a man jumped at him from the side.

Bam!

The two of them instantly separated, and the black shadow hit the gate forcefully. The whole wall shook as a result.

"Damn!!" He continued his rolling on the floor as he dodged the second attack; the frame of the gate behind him was smashed by a punch, and it let off a deep boom sound. A ton of stone chips crackled down the wall.

"Golden Loop Number 9, you deserve this!" Garen’s voice sounded in the darkness. "How dare you shift all the blame onto me? Do you think I’m scared of you?"

Golden Loop Number 9 grabbed onto the handle on the stairs as he tried helping himself up; he was only able to half kneel on the ground. He looked pale as blood flowed out of his ears, nose, and mouth; there were many thin blood streams all over his face.

He wasn't practicing Body Hardening Technique in the first place; after getting injured by Golden Loop Number 8, and getting sneak attacked by this, he felt sick to his stomach, and his head felt a little dizzy.

"Where is it?" He endured the pain and asked with his hoarse voice.

"It’s on me of course." Garen sneered. "I will give it to the Golden Loop, it will help relieve the tension between us. I will give it to Golden Loop Number 8 later."

"Idiot." Number 9 suddenly laughed reluctantly. He stood up straight and was about to speak; however, he suddenly opened his mouth and puked up a mouthful of blood.

The thick smell of bloody instantly dispersed into the space.

At this time, another black shadow dashed out of the stone room, and appeared in front of the gate; it was Golden Loop Number 8.

He was holding onto a small torch that was still lit, and the torch barely lit up the surroundings. Under the vague light, the three faces appeared red and looming.

"Do you really have it?" Golden Loop Number 8 looked at Garen: "Give it to me!" He said as he reached out his hand.

"I can give it to you, but it has not been identified yet. I think I’m the only one who is able to identify to see if it’s fake or not. You guys know how long it takes to identify."

Garen didn’t hesitate. He knew that he couldn’t protect this item. Although he didn’t like the way Golden Loop Number 8 talked to him, he threw the white eye shaped stone to him. The latter caught it in mid-air; he nodded in satisfaction after he checked it.

"It’s ok. I misunderstood you before. This item has no value to you, so you have no reason to jack it. In terms of identification, we will have to bother you on that. Everything here is a big misunderstanding."

"I only like identifying all sorts of strange stuff. I actually do hope that I could identify the stuff that you Golden Loop get," Garen spoke his mind.

Golden Loop Number 8 swirled his eyes and said: "The organization is always looking to treasure and protect talented people. The henchmen didn’t know much, and caused a lot of trouble for you; it is our fault. But I’m sure you know that you are on Dale Quicksilver’s side, and a lot people in the organization is not happy about that. But if you Kelly could join Golden Loop, then everything won’t be a problem." He just tested Garen’s strength and was impressed. Since Golden Loop Number 9 just betrayed the organization, a new person had to be added to the top ten Golden Loops, he had an idea.

The two of them started talking and actually ignored Golden Loop Number 9 who was severely injured temporarily. Number 9 was happy to see that too; he needed the time to recuperate, his body couldn’t handle it anymore.

"What can I get by joining Golden Loop?" Garen asked as he lowered his voice.

"Although we are not a Secret Martial Art Organization, we are not a pure Force Organization as well." Golden Loop Number 8 laughed proudly: "Detective Dale knew the reason why we, the Golden Loop exist, but he didn’t tell you."

Garen squinted his eyes.

"For us to like collecting this much, someone must need them."

"When what kind of a person like these Antiques that are stolen and hard to sell? After all, these items are small and incredibly old; they only have minute historic value." Golden Loop Number 8 continued with his hints.

Garen was shocked.

"Nobles!" He shouted out.

"Actually," Golden Loop Number 8 started laughing. "Golden Loop represents not just an ordinary underground force. We are backed by many influential people in high places! Strength is actually our weakest link, what we have is power and influence! There are only benefits and no harms by joining us."

Garen was relieved, and he knew there weren’t any problems; he said all of that to Golden Loop Number 8 Intentionally. He still had his families, relatives, and master; he wasn’t a single person who was isolated. Although Golden Loop wasn’t scared of Manuyllton Corporation or his master Fei Baiyun’s status and influence, they wouldn’t come and provoke him for no reason, as long as there wasn’t any conflict of interest.

"No wonder the detectives couldn’t do anything about you guys, so it turns out that Golden Loop’s influence is this strong!" He murmured.

"We just need an identification expert that could identify ancient and mysterious items. This is your opportunity!" Golden Loop Number 8 was getting more and more satisfied with his idea. All of Garen’s strength, background, and talent were what his organization was looking for. If he was able to add Garen into their organization, then the small conflicts they had prior could be solved easily. So only a few people died? They weren’t any of the top twenty Golden Loops, anyone after the twentieth position were pretty much useless, and their positions could be filled easily! At this day and age, experts and talented individuals are the most important resources.

Chapter 68: Alleviation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"No rush, let’s take care of business first." Garen looked at Golden Loop Number Nine, and the latter instantly tensed up.

Golden Loop Number Eight sneered as he charged at Number Nine and poked out with his index finger.

Pssh!

Weh!

Golden Loop Number Nine let out a deep "humph" as a bloody hole appeared in his chest.

Bam!

His whole body instantly flew backward, went over the handrail, and fell down to the "black hole".

"Let’s go." Golden Loop Number Eight didn’t even bother looking down. He turned around and began walking up the stairs. "What the people on top want is here, so we won’t have any problems after I hand it in. Identification will be something for another day."

Garen looked down at where Golden Loop Number Nine had fallen in, but the place was pitch black and he couldn’t see a thing. He quickly followed Golden Loop Number Eight up the stairs.

"Oh wait, did you guys get any clues in terms of the fragrance of the Mindtwister Vine? Why didn’t I see that particular plant?" he asked as he recalled the strange things he saw at the Silversilk Castle.

"Mindtwister Vine? That thing is best for creating illusions and killing people. All of them were collected from our people, except for that crazy woman. She still kept some, but not that much," Golden Loop Number Eight said casually. "Okay, I will go up first and retreat with my people. You can come up later, so Dale Quicksilver won’t get suspicious. If you join us, the Golden Loop, then your identity could be a great cover."

"Ok." Garen nodded. He stood still and watched Golden Loop Number Eight sped up and quickly disappeared into the darkness.

He turned around and looked back at the darkness behind him. The stairs seemed to extend downward forever, as if they led to the endless abyss. The whole stairway was so quiet that it was frightening.

"Why did this Golden Loop Number Nine rush in and try to steal this item?"

Garen still had a question on his mind, but unfortunately, Number Nine was already dead. There was no way that he could still be alive after falling down from a place this high up while already being severely injured.

After shaking his head, Garen paced himself and ran up the stairs.

At the very bottom of the staircase, Golden Loop Number Nine laid facing up. Numerous metal spikes extended from the ground, piercing his body. His eyes were open wide, but there was no sign of life in them. His blood slowly soaked into the black soil and solidified.

*****************

The Silversilk Castle during the afternoon glowed a warm shade of red under the sunlight during sunset. In the courtyard in front of the castle, a few guards equipped with guns were checking their teammate’s corpses. Their faces were all pale. Some of them were swearing, while others were choking and whining.

Their captain had a bandage on his arm and stood beside Detective Dale with an ugly expression on his face. The White Eagle and Black Panther were also with them. Grace, in the meantime, stood beside Garen and Cynthia. The latter wasn’t that upset. Her people hadn’t suffered too many casualties. They were within an acceptable margin.

Garen stood by the side and saw a bunch of detectives making small talk, trying to decide on something. However, he was not interested and too lazy to listen to it. The biggest reward for him in this trip was that he had built a connection with the Golden Loop. If everything went smoothly, he would no longer have to worry about his family's safety anymore.

"Unfortunately, I wasn’t of much help this time." Garen murmured. "My original plan was only to follow the detectives and figure out the secret of the Silversilk Castle, though I also wanted to see if I’ll be able get some antiques. It looks like I thought too much."

"Next time if you want to run around, can you please let me know first?" Cynthia said helplessly. Both her face and body were dirty, but she didn’t have any wounds. It was like a miracle! She didn’t get injured during that intense shooting at all.

**************

"Ok, I got it." Garen smiled and said, "We should go back This isn’t the time and place for us to stay."

He walked directly toward the bunch of people, including Detective Dale.

After some simple farewells, Garen led Grace, Cynthia and the other people who had came with him towards Canoe Town.

They returned to Canoe Town in the early evening, the sky had yet to turn dark. Garen jumped into Grace’s car and headed towards the city.

After getting back to the city, his life gradually returned to normal. Garen threw the situation with the Silversilk Castle to the back of his mind and no longer thought about it. Besides going to the library to read books, he would only go to the old man’s and learn about identification. Though at the same time, he was waiting for the boss of Manuyllton Corporation to find time to see him.

***************

After several weeks…

In a small room in the library, surrounded by bookshelves, Garen was seated down on a red sofa. He looked with concentration at the black hard cover book, which was about the size of a magazine, that he was flipping through.

There was a cup of coffee on the black table in front of him, but it had lost its heat already.

"Book of Silence?" a pretty blonde girl asked, leaning against an armrest as she sat on his right.

Her hair was bound with a black hairband, and she wore a tight, black silk shirt emphasizing her full chest and slender waist. There were many dark red flowers on the dress. The two colors, black and red, gave off an elegant and quiet feel. The skirt had a perfect length as its edge covered her knees.

"Why do you suddenly want to search for information on this book?"

This girl was Felicity. She had just gotten back from Manroland two days ago, and had contacted Garen, asking to meet up.

"I’ve heard this name before, and it sounds strange. I feel like this book is very mysterious." Garen shrugged his shoulder. There was no way that he would tell her the truth.

"You’re asking the right person for this kind of knowledge." The girl’s eyes opened wide. It was obvious that she was having a good time. "Book of Silence is an ancient book within which mysterious knowledge about the legends is recorded. The most mysterious and ruthless civilization, Ancient Endor, is the place from which the Book of Silence originates.

"Huh… There are a few mythology books that I want to read. I could take you to go though the books together, and we could see if we can find it." Felicity stood up, dusted her skirts, and said, "Follow me."

Garen quickly dropped the book in his hand and followed her out of the small room.

Felicity quietly said something to a maid at the door. The latter nodded and walked at the front, leading the way.

The three of them passed by a few connected study rooms, and then entered a small door on the left. There was a wooden staircase leading down to the basement behind the door. It was a bit dark. The floor was covered by thick black carpet that muffled all the noise made by their footsteps.

Garen followed Felicity and the maid. They walked down three floors of stairs, passed through a few gates, and opened a series of locks. After all that trouble, they finally arrived at a large, deserted underground library.

It was a rectangular hall that was dark and gloomy. There were a dozen so black wood bookshelves, but most of them were empty. There was no one in here, and it seemed very quiet.

Felicity waved, singalling the maid to leave. After that, she dragged Garen towards a bookshelf on the very right.

"The books here are centuries old. There are some on mythology, but you have to look for them."

Garen nodded as he sniffed the air. There was a vague musty smell.

They didn’t talk after that, each rolling up their sleeves and beginning their search for ancient books.

There weren’t a lot of them on the shelves, and the books that were there had a thick layer of dust on them. When they took them off of the shelves, they breathed in noses full of white dust and coughed violently. However, Felicity didn’t seem to care about that. Filled with excitement, she started to look for books on mythology along with Garen.

They started their search from the bookshelf on the very right to the bookshelf on the very left. They did find a few books on mythology, but they could tell that they were full of bullsh*t. The stories in them could only be considered tales for little kids.

"Most of the books here are left behind by one of my friend’s ancestors. He had taken the majority of the books out, but there were still some that he didn’t clean up. These were left here due to some family reasons, and now are forgotten and abandoned here. If you didn’t bring it up, I probably wouldn’t have even remembered this place," Felicity said in a quiet voice, coughing, as she took out a grey book and slapped the dust off of it. The dust immediately dispersed, prolonging the girl’s coughing fit.

"No rush, we have time, we can go slow." Garen laughed. He didn’t seem to be impatient at all.

Time ticked away, second by second, in this dark hall as the fire flickered in the torches on the wall.

After who knew how long, suddenly, a deep crackling noise sounded in the left corner of the hall.

A dense cloud of dust was blown into the air.

"Cough, cough… Cough! Cough! Cough!... Damn! Why did it fall down," Felicity complained as she walked away from the bookshelves. Her entire body was covered in dust. The black silk dress was no long pure black. There was a layer of white dust on the surface, and the girl looked miserable.

"Eh?" Garen was surprised. "There is a book there."

He was standing not too far away from the girl. After the bookshelf fell down, he suddenly saw a book fall down from the top shelf. Quickly, he walked up and picked it up.

After lightly dusting off the dust off of its cover, the book was unveiled. It was black, and its cover page had a set of golden necklaces. The author’s name was at the bottom: Philip Jeffries

Garen lightly opened the book. The pages were a light yellow color. He could tell that they used to be white, but due to the passage of time now had turned to yellow.

The first page only had one line on it: "Dedicated to scholars who are searching and studying mythology".

He turned the page, and there was a simple index on the second page consisting of three parts: Nightmare, The White Color, Ritual.

There were more detailed tags under each part, and the page numbers were after them.

"What is this?" Felicity got close to Garen and asked, "Golden necklace? Why doesn’t this book have a name?"

"No name?" Garen was surprsied. "Yeah, it really doesn’t have a name."

"There are only two possiblities. One is that this is a personal book. Books are regulated by the National Publications Bureau, and not putting a name is a way to avoid that. These kind of books are assumed to be notes or diaries." Felicity was very knowledgeable. She explained, "But the other one..." Her expression got serious.

"The other one would be the so-called banned books. They contain prohibited material. Not putting a name on it is also for the purpose of avoiding the National Publications Bureau. Because they’re all banned by National Publications Bureau, they only have the name of the author on it."

"Banned book?" Garen instantly got interested. He flipped through a few more pages and found that the whole book was filled with symbols and strange writings that he didn’t understand.

"Let’s go, let’s sit down over there and read it. This book must be a banned book! I’ve never seen a real banned book before."

Felicity got interested as well. Both of them came to a red wooden table, pulled out chairs, wiped them clean, and sat down. The light on the table was already lit up by the maid. Although it was a bit dim, it didn’t affect their reading.

Chapter 69: Shifting Destiny 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Putting the book on the table, Garen continued to flip through the pages.

The yellow surface of the paper was slightly rough and crisp. The corner of the paper broke off after Garen lightly touched it. It was like an extremely thin template.

"Be careful, these books are very old, at least hundreds of years old," Felicity said quietly.

"Okay."

Garen softened his movements even more.

After flipping to the fifth page, it was still the table of contents. Garen ignored it and kept on flipping.

‘Hereby I thank my friend, Lady Liana. If it weren’t for her careful correction and sponsorship, this book might not have been published…’ After this, the words became blurry like they had been soaked in water.

Garen frowned and continued flipping. To his surprise, the actual content of the book was crooked black letters that looked like toads. Garen could recognize individual ones, but when jumbled together, they became garbled and meaningless.

"Could it be… are these special codes? I need to decode it to read the actual content?" Garen said with a frown. He flipped a couple more pages again, but they were are all the same.

"I think so. When writing down important information, a lot of people design their own codes." Felicity nodded and looked through the book alongside Garen.

"Then what do we do?" Garen stopped at a random page. From top to bottom, there was not a single paragraph he could understand. All he could try to comprehend were some drawn engineering designs.

"One of my friends’ grandpa used to use this one method of encryption. I still remember it, so let me try to decode it." Felicity excitedly grabbed the book, took out a pen and started to work her way through the book.

The girl pushed Garen away and even stole his seat.

Standing at the back, however, allowed Garen to see Felicity’s perky butt. One of her legs was sexily bent on top of the chair, lifting up her tight black skirt. If he crouched a bit more, he would be able to see what was underneath that skirt of hers.

"I am relaxed and happy," Garen softly whispered to himself. With a grin on his face, he walked back a few more steps and enjoyed Felicity’s beautiful pose.

After about ten minutes.

"Garen, come here, I know what this book is about now!" the girl suddenly shouted.

Garen walked over in a hurry and sniffed her refreshing natural scent. He subconsciously inhaled deeply. However, seeing Felicity’s serious face, he organized his thoughts and looked at the table.

On top of the desk was a piece of paper. It contained a small paragraph decoded from the book.

"I have a general idea of what this book is about," Felicity said with a bit of excitement.

She flipped to the table of contents and pointed at the page.

"There are three parts in the book: nightmare, the color white, ceremony. These three parts are in correspondence to the three strange events the author encountered. It tells the boring and difficult journey he went through to try and find answers, as well as the clues he picked up in the end. Basically, this book is a travel journal. A journal detailing the journey of a man who was seeking the truth behind fables!"

"Travel journal? Does it really have records of the strange events the author encountered?" Garen asked suspiciously.

"It doesn’t really clarify what exactly was going on. However, the author has recorded that he wasn’t sure since when but he began to repeatedly have the same nightmare. To reach the roots of why he was having it and to ease the pain, he went on a journey to figure out why it was occurring. If it really was just about a nightmare, then it couldn’t be categorized as a strange event. But, at the end of the book, the author seems to have learned something. The way he wrote became a little unclear, it was as if he was tabooing something."

"Tabooing something?" Garen squinted his eyes. "Can we find some information on the author?"

"No. From what I’ve noticed, after the author arrived at this one place and came out of it, there was a huge change in the book’s content and it became ambiguous," Felicity explained.

"What is that place?"

"Rochwell Empire Library."

Garen frowned, picked up the book, and flipped through it.

"Look at the back cover, there is something!" Felicity yelled anxiously.

Garen flipped to the last page in a hurry. Immediately, a white piece of paper that was tucked between the cracks of the back cover fell out. If it wasn’t for the cover being cracked after such a long time, a knife would have been needed to pry open the cover to get that piece of paper.

Felicity quickly picked it up and unfolded it.

On it was written only a single line: Navici Tsunami Mountain No. 174, under the third tree and six meters deep. I left the stuff there. – Charlie

"It’s a note! Nobody has found it before us, or else this piece of paper wouldn’t still be tucked in the book cover." Felicity was thrilled. "Let’s go check it out! Maybe we can get our hands on something cool!"

"Navici… Where is this?" Garen had never heard of this place before.

"It’s at the Jade Mountain Province, on the border of the Confederation. The province’s capital is Navici. The Jade Mountain is a very poor province. It has awful soil and there is a lack of natural resources. Other than an overabundance of sunlight, there isn’t a lot of advantages to that area. Their grapes and honeydew melon are quite nice though." Felicity became even more eager. "What do you think? Want to go? Let’s go together!"

"Jade Mountain Province is too far from here…" Garen was speechless. "If we take the train, it’ll take us a week. Going there and back will take us half a month."

"What are you afraid of? We have plenty of time." Felicity waved her hand, indicating that she did not mind.

Garen thought about it for a second. "How about this, let’s decide after a while. I have to go back to school soon and the timing just doesn’t work out. I also have a lot of errands to take care of. Felicity, don’t you have some stuff going on at home too? How can you squeeze out the time to travel?"

"It’s not that bad." Felicity then remembered something, and her thrilled look faded a little. "You’re right. I do have some stuff to take care of. It might take us a whole month to go there and back. Okay… then let’s make plans for our next break."

"Sure." Garen nodded without hesitation.

The two of them studied the content of the book for a bit longer. Both were rather excited. Only when the clock on the wall announced the time with its loud bangs, did the two of them unwillingly stop.

"It’s almost noon, I have to go get some lunch. There’s some stuff I need to do in the afternoon." Garen stood up and softly sighed.

"Something to do? What do you have to do? It’s our break, yet you’re so busy all the time. Aren’t you tired?" Felicity finally took her leg off the chair. It was numb from keeping the same pose for so long, and she stumbled, falling backward.

Without knowing it, her small butt was aimed straight at Garen’s lower body.

At that moment, both of them froze.

Felicity’s cheeks slowly turned red as she felt a warm object slowly rising behind her. It suddenly jumped and stabbed her at a sensitive spot.

She screamed and jumped away as if she had been electrocuted. "You wanna die?" She turned around and cupped her butt with her hands. She stared down at Garen.

"I-" Garen shrugged. "You were the one that hit me. I can’t control something like that…" he responded in a low voice.

"Go to hell!" Felicity kicked Garen’s lower leg and left angry and red-faced.

Garen helplessly looked at the white and grey footprint on his leg. This kick didn’t even make him itch. To a regular person however, it would definitely be a kick hard enough to bruise their bones. She was wearing a pointy leather shoe after all.

"Whatever. I have to go the old man’s place in the afternoon. Ah, Ying Er is the only one nice to me. Even when she fights me, she doesn’t hit hard."

He dusted off the dirt off his pants and walked out of the library. There was no sight of Felicity. After taking out his card to sign out for leaving, he hailed down a horse carriage and went home.

Sitting in the carriage, Garen closed his eyes and rested his mind while checking the status of his attributes. This was something he did regularly everyday.

Strength 2.22. Agility 1.10. Physique 1.87. Intelligence 1.50. Potential 258%. White Cloud Secret Arts: Great Achievement (Stage 4). Explosive Fist Arts: Intermediate. White Cloud Combat Arts: Intermediate.

"Strength went up a little bit. I’m not sure what to do with the potential I’ve been collecting though…" Garen thought about it with a frown.

"Before I kept on improving my Strength and as a result my Explosive Fist Arts became intermediate level. After acquiring strong defense and solo combat skills, I should be undefeatable in the short term. But if I run into a speedy opponent, then I’m in trouble. With my physique and my grasp on combat, I am considered to be an advanced martial artist. Compared to second senior brother and elder senior sister though, I am still lacking behind by a lot despite my advantage over normal people. I am not sure which attribute I should try to improve next."

He glanced over the Agility attribute. The number 1.10 hadn’t changed since the beginning.

"I remember the elder senior sister telling me a few days ago that real masters cannot have any visible flaws. Even if they have them, they need to learn how to compensate for that weakness. My speed right now should be my most obvious flaw. It seems like I’ll need to greatly improve my agility as well."

After analyzing, he finally focused his view on the Agility attribute.

After a few seconds, the number jumped from 1.10 to 1.20.

Another second passed, the Strength attribute hopped as well, from 2.22 to 2.42.

Garen was somewhat shocked. He looked at his Potential Meter. He had used up all of the potential he’d saved up over the last few weeks. There was 158% left.

"Why does improving my agility causs my strength to go up?" He was speechless. "Could it be.." He suddenly thought of a possibility. "Even if I want to keep my strength unchanging and only try to increase my speed, the explosive force that results from it will definitely increase as well. This means speed plus strength creates the real explosive force and damage! I think this is the true trick behind these attributes. With a high strength attribute, I can add a little speed to exponentially increase my explosive force and damage."

He noticed that after the agility attribute went up, another symbol appeared. Looking carefully, the meaning of the symbol naturally flew into his mind.

"The difference between strength and agility is too big, therefore the two of them affect each other." Garen looked at the other attributes. "If that’s the case, then should I try to even out all my attributes? I shouldn’t be too extreme with one attribute because it will drag down my other attributes too."

With the little of potential left, Garen didn’t use it up. The potential in the Black Jade Disk had been dying down and the potential inside was less than he anticipated. Because of that, it took longer to absorb the potential and after another time, two at best, there would be nothing left to absorb.

Sitting on the carriage, he slowly took out the Black Jade Disk form his pants’ pocket. This piece of antique that looked like a tough medal was emitting potential that was as thin as a strand of hair.

Garen brushed his fingers over this long rectangular small medal and felt the uneven and bumpy words and carvings.

"After I absorb all of it, I can sell it through a company or through the Golden Hoop. It’ll probably fetch me a lot of money and I’ll be able to use it to find more Antiques of Tragedy." Garen moved around to feel the effects of the change in his attributes. "I guess I won’t go to the old man’s today, but try out my new physique at the dojo. If I don’t familiarize myself, I might screw up in my next combat. I haven’t been that dedicated to going regularly. When I see Master this afternoon, he will lecture me for sure…"

Garen smiled helplessly.

Chapter 70: Shifting Destiny 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Afternoon, Pennington street.

Grey clouds covered the sky, not letting a single beam of light shine through. It was a gloomy day.

Inside Dolphin Antiques, old man Gregor languidly sat in the chair behind the table. He seemed to be dozing off with his head tilted.

Suddenly, he heard a familiar footstep from outside the door.

"Garen?" the old man opened one of his eyes and asked listlessly. "Look at what time it is! I thought you weren’t coming today." He pointed at a white narrow-necked vase with two ear-like handles. "This is your mission for the afternoon, go take a closer look. Give me your appraisal report after."

Garen walked through the door in a red sports suit. When he saw the old man’s lazy attitude, he rolled his eyes and shook his head in silence. He walked up and reached out to take the vase.

All of a sudden, he flipped his fingers and launched what seemed to be a black line.

The black line drew an arch in the air like a flying bug, speeding toward old man Gregor’s forehead like lightning.

"Ow!"

It was too late for the old man to dodge, so he slightly tilted his head. Unexpectedly, the black line turned and struck down, stabbing into his left shoulder, and stopped there. It was a thin black needle.

"Garen, what in the world are you doing?" Gregor got up from his chair, took two steps back and pulled out the needle. He was both surprised and infuriated.

Garen was shocked. Suddenly, he had a pained expression and staggered two steps back. He spat out a mouthful of blood and his face turned pale.

"What happened? How are you?" Old man Gregor froze, but then immediately came around the table to hold Garen. His swift movements were completely contradictory to his elderly figure.

"My… my head hurts..!" Garen’s shouted out in a weak voice, his face twisting with pain.

"Damn it, it must be those guys! How dare they … ugh!"

Gregor’s voice suddenly stopped, his body shuddering next to Garen. He lowered his head and saw a short black dagger stabbed into his belly.

"You..!"

Garen sneered as he promptly pulled the dagger out, flipped it in his hand, and backed off a step without making another move.

"If I wasn’t disguised as that kid, I probably wouldn’t have been able to trick you."

He pinched the skin on his left cheek and gently peeled off a mask made of human skin, revealing a handsome yet sinister face of a man. "Long time no see, Gregor."

"It’s you… Sylphalan!"

Old man Gregor backed off two steps, holding his wounded lower belly. He had a complicated expression.

"Tell me, where is the thing?" Sylphalan demanded.

"The thing? Heh…" Old man Gregor smiled. "You still haven’t given up?"

Sylphalan laughed. "I know you’re strong, but there is no way you could escape after getting struck by my Duskhill Needle. Now come on, show me where it is…" He slowly approached Gregor.

Gregor unexpectedly started chuckling.

"Have you forgotten? No matter how many times you try, you will always eat my dust."

"We’ll see about that," Sylphalan mocked with a smile.

*****************

Phew!

Garen flung himself at the bed after the shower, his hair still wet. He took a deep breath, the blankets had the most familiar and warm fragrance.

"I’m so tired…" he mumbled. "Got beaten up by master Fei at the dojo, then scolded by mom and dad after getting home. Thank god Ying Er was home early, else it could’ve been worse…"

A tranquil orange light lit the bedroom, dyeing Garen’s white bathrobe a faint yellow. Outside the window, the day was turning dark. It was almost dusk.

His parents and Ying Er went for a stroll after dinner, but Garen was too tired to go along, so he stayed and rested in his room.

He laid on his stomach and dug out the Black Jade Disk, carefully rubbing its rough surface with his hand.

Creak…

The door abruptly opened.

"Brother, what are you doing with the door closed? Doing something sneaky?" Ying Er walked in holding a glass of water.

Garen hid the Black Jade Disc in a flurry.

"Could you knock on the door when you come in?" he complained, sitting up.

"Knock on the door? For what? How will I catch you doing your sneaky business if I knock?" Ying Er looked like she had just showered as well. Her skin was shining pink from the heat.

She was wearing a white t-shirt and shorts, revealing her long and slim thighs. She stood at the door, her thighs level with Garen’s face.

"Didn’t you go out with mom and dad? Why are you back?" Garen asked while trying to avoid peeking at his sister’s legs.

"I never left. I was just saying that to deceive you, and I’ve finally caught you in action!" Ying Er said with an evil laugh. "If you don’t want mom and dad to know about your fishy business, you’ll have to promise me something!"

"Promise you something? You think you can threaten me?" Garen replied, acting stubborn. He had nothing to hide, but he was trying to tease Ying Er. "What do you want?"

Ying Er walked toward Garen and looked down at him with one arm on her hip.

"What I want is simple!" She hummed and sneered. "That is …"

Rumble!

Suddenly there was a thudding sound, and a violent rumbling came after.

The whole apartment started shaking strenuously, an eerie noise came from afar and numbed Garen’s ears.

Ying Er couldn’t even stand still. She fell into Garen’s arms, her legs spread out, and sat up straight in Garen’s right leg.

The two shuddered. Garen warily gripped onto Ying Er, but the latter blushed and ran out of the room in an instant.

Garen turned around to face up, still immersed in his sister’s refreshing fragrance as she fell onto him.

"I’ve been quite lucky recently…" He lightly chuckled and collected himself. He sat in front of his desk and started reviewing the antiques appraisal knowledge.

*************

Suburbs of Huaishan City, inside a forest.

Old man Gregor covered his stomach and stood facing the burning woods. He quietly watched as the torching flames consumed the trees. The fire reflected on his face, coloring it red.

"If you still had the book, I might have been a little reluctant, but now…" From the searing flames walked out a man, Sylphalan. He had a wound on his left cheek, and blood was slowly streaming out of it onto his chin. "Gregor, you have become mortal … Your only hope is the sustenance."

"Even without it, I can still… Cough Cough…" Gregor coughed abruptly, his hand was still placed over his abdomen, blood gushing from between his fingers.

"Weak and powerless, you even lost that book. The once glorious genius has turned into today’s tragic sight!" Sylphalan said, opening his arms. "It really is …. pathetic…" he murmured in a poetic tone. "What do you wish to accomplish by extracting your power? Do you want to give it to the boy? It’s no use, he isn’t gifted enough. He is a mere mortal who will easily perish with time."

"Whoever I’m giving it to, it’s my business. As for that book, I’ve placed it far far away, in a place you would never find…" Gregor panted and faintly laughed.

"We’ve lived together for all those years, brother. Do you really think I don’t know that you would give it to that old hag?" Sylphalan smiled.

Gregor’s face twitched a little. It was too late when he realized it.

"I knew it! Haha!" Sylphalan started laughing maniacally. "I was just trying to test you first, but your mind is still as slow as a turtle, even after all these years."

He stared at Gregor, his eyes full of sorrow.

"You’ve always put all of your life and power into someone else’s hands. Even until the day you die, you’re still like this. You think I can’t tell how many days you’ve left? Putting all of your vitality into the ritual, only you could do something like this."

"I was already a useless man, I just wanted to leave a trace of myself in this big world…" Gregor had a tearful smile.

Bang!

It looked like he had been hit by something invisible; his body abruptly flew out and hit a trunk. Then rolled for a bit.

"Ugh…" Gregor covered his mouth with a hand, but blood flowed out from between his fingers and dripped to the ground.

"Why are you always this stupid! Why?" Sylphalan ran at him and fiercely hit Gregor’s stomach.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Sylphalan’s feet stomped and kicked, harder and harder.

It sounded like something hitting a leathered sack, the sound was clear even at the edge of this burning forest.

"Trace?" He finally stopped. "A scumbag like you wants to leave a trace in this world? Keep dreaming!" At some point during the kicking, his face had turned diabolical. "I’ve made up my mind. I will erase everything you’ve left! All of it!" he roared at the top of his lungs. His face was twisted, purple veins throbbing on his forehead.

Suddenly a hand gripped Sylphalan’s boot. Gregor desperately raised his head, his face covered in blood. He was completely mute, thick blood continuously welling in his mouth. He stared at Sylphalan with it wide open, unable to say a word.

"You want me to leave him alone?" Sylphalan stopped raging and regained his calm expression. This time he had a mysterious smirk. "You’re begging me? You are begging me, right?"

Gregor’s pupils were dilating, his eyes had gone blurry, and he could not see anything. But he kept his grip on Sylphalan’s boot.

"You’re really begging me?" Sylphalan’s smile turned into a wild laugh. "If you want to beg me, then lick my boots clean!"

Bang!

He stomped on Gregor’s face.

"Lick it… the once glorious genius … my dear brother.. LICK IT!"

His face turned diabolical again.

He stomped and grinded Gregor’s face, again and again.

Suddenly he froze.

Old man Gregor, who was dying beneath his feet, really reached out with his tongue and licked his boot.

An inexplicable emotion filled Sylphalan’s chest. He raised his head and felt a sudden bitterness.

"It… was… my fault… back … then…" Old man’s voice came from below his feet. "Forgi… me…"

His head slid down to the ground, the last bit of luster gone from his eyes.

Sylphalan did not respond. He looked at the body at his feet. The cold wind blew and angered the flames in the forest, but they were starting to burn down.

"Brother…"

Sylphalan silently squatted down next to Gregor’s body.

**********************

At the same time, Garen sat at his desk and felt a warmth in his chest.

He pulled out a necklace from beneath his collar. It was the book shaped one old man Gregor had given him.

"What’s going on?" He checked it again, but could not find anything abnormal. The necklace was as warm as his body’s temperature.

He decided not to overthink it, chucked the necklace back beneath his collar, and continued to study the appraisal cases.

As he stuffed the necklace back, a small line of text appeared on its surface.

‘Ain Gregoria, third life ritual – protection.’

Chapter 71: Shifting Destiny 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Knock! Knock!

"Open the door, old man!" Garen kept knocking on the door of the antique shop.

It was early in the morning, and there were only a couple workers in blue walking down the street. They saw Garen violently knocking on the door but did not bother to stop.

"Old man! You still sleeping?" Garen was out of patience and started to yell. He went to bed early last night and wanted to ask Gregor a few questions before heading to the Martial Arts Association for the ranking test, but no one was answering the door.

"Is he not here?" Garen thought and scrunched his eyebrows. He looked around and made sure no one else was around. He tiptoed and reached the edge of a window with his hand. He grabbed a blue key from the windowsill.

"I knew it would still here." Garen smiled and opened the door with the key.

Creak.

The door opened slowly, and the place remained silent. The floor was covered with a black carpet, and there were several paintings hanging on the wall. The paintings were done in various colors, but mainly gold and silver.

Garen closed the door, walked toward the wall, and touched all the new items. He shook his head in disappointment. There was nothing that could increase his potential. Garen turned back and walked to the inner chamber.

It was dark behind the door curtain, so Garen carefully lit the oil lamps on the wall.

"Old man? Are you alright?" Garen scrunched his eyebrows and looked at the bed. It did not seem like anyone had slept in it. The blanket was still well organized.

Garen walked toward the bed and put his hand on the blanket. Cold.

"No one slept in here for sure. Did he go out last night?" Garen wondered. He knew something was not right. He walked toward the front of the shop and sat down on the old man’s chair.

(P.S. I thought of using Double Gourd Vase with Slender Neck, but amphora seemed more appropriate)

Garen suddenly saw the dark red stain on the white Slender Neck Amphora. He narrowed his eyes and grabbed the amphora. Scratching off some of the dark red stain with his finger, he smelled it.

"It’s blood…" Garen stood up slowly, a serious expression on his face.

"I hope the old man is okay…" he thought.

Garen started to investigate the situation and after several minutes he found some more bloodstains on the black carpet. He carefully checked around, but that was the only thing he found.

"Huh?" Garen found a white rectangular letter lying on the carpet under the table.

It said ‘To Little Bastard’ on the envelope. The words were written in black ink, and the handwriting was a bit messy, but still easy to read.

"It’s the old man," Garen scrunched his eyebrows and opened the envelope. He pulled the letter out, noticing that there was almost no empty space left on the paper.

‘I am on vacation kid! Don’t try to find or contact me. I am good. An old friend invited me, and there are a lot of delicious dishes and nice drinks here. I heard he also prepared beauties for me. Hahaha. Don’t get jealous. I don’t think I am coming back. I opened the shop for fun, and I will leave it to you. You can do whatever you want with it.

Wait. I taught you how to identify the antiques. You better keep learning. I am counting on you.’

The letter ended here.

Garen finished the letter, but his expression did not change. He became even more serious.

"Old man… You think I will be tricked by this?" Garen thought and took the letter to the table. He lit an oil lamp with a match and toasted the paper carefully over the flame.

Sentences started to slowly show up on the back of the letter. Garen read the letter again after all the hidden sentences appeared.

‘Garen, I’m sure you’ll find my hidden message. But by the time you’re reading this, I’ll probably be gone already. To be honest, you remind me of myself. Though you aren’t talented like me, our personalities are really similar. Well, make sure you take care of the necklace I gave you and don’t lose it. It might help out in a certain situation.

Also, if… I mean, if you find something is strange in the shop, you need to leave it immediately! If anyone asks you about me, never say you knew me! There is barely anyone who can deal with them in this world. Don’t call the police and don’t seek help from others. It will only put them in danger. Only people with equivalent power would be able to fight them.

Sadly… You don’t have the talent…’

The message ended here.

It seemed like the old man still had something to say.

Garen was breathing heavily while reading the message. He knew something happened to the old man, but he tried not to think about it.

"They? Old man, who are they?" Garen thought

There were many thoughts going through Garen’s mind, and he just stood there with the letter in his hands.

Ka!

Suddenly, he heard some noise.

"Who’s there!" Garen yelled. He put the letter down and rushed toward the source of the noise.

A man was walking toward the backdoor of the inner chamber. He turned back and looked at Garen after hearing his yell. The man looked surprised.

"Master was right. The kid came back!" the thin man suddenly yelled out.

"We didn’t come here for nothing," someone else agreed. He then continued, "Take him out and we can leave."

"Got it. I will take care of him." The thin man laughed and walked toward Garen.

"Kid, you’re unlucky," the man said, pointing a finger at Garen.

Boom!

Some invisible force stopped Garen from moving, and he felt like he was glued to the floor.

"What is this?"

Garen’s expression changed. He wanted to raise his arm but he could not move at all. It was as if he was locked between two cement walls.

"Is this the talent the old man spoke about? That’s their power?" Garen thought. He tried his best to move, but nothing happened.

Garen stared at the man in front of him and saw there was a black tattoo on the back of his right hand. It looked like a complex pentacle.

"James Silva, stop playing and hurry up," the man outside the door spoke again.

"Okay, fine." The thin man named James Silva looked annoyed. He pointed his first finger at Garen again.

Crack!

There was a sound of glass shattering.

The man no longer seemed annoyed. He froze, then slowly looked down and saw a arm jabbed into his chest. The teenager who had been previously restrained was now standing right in front of him with a cold look on his face.

Boom!

The thin man was struck again and fell to the floor after hitting the door. He stopped breathing after rolling several meters away. Garen walked out through the backdoor and entered the backyard.

There were three men in black standing in there, staring at the thin man lying on the floor. For a time, they couldn’t understand what had just happened.

"It’s Old Man Gregor! It’s him! He’s back!" a man at the left yelled in a shaky tone.

"Shut up! That old bastard is dead already! He was finished off by our master!" the leading man in black yelled back at him. "Take him out. We need to leave!"

"I only want to live a peaceful life, why do you have to do this?" Garen had no expression on his face as he looked at the three men calmly. His body started to expand, and his muscles puffed up. Garen’s upper body became twice its original size, and he looked like a demon from the tales.

"I don’t have the talent? Ridiculous…" Garen said.

BAM!

Garen leapt forward, the floor shaking underneath him, and caused a hole to appear after landing. It was as if the ground was struck by lightning.

"Spread out!" the three yelled, but Garen grabbed two of them before they could act. He squeezed the two’s heads with his hands and they exploded. The backyard was splashed with blood and brains, painting a horror-filled scene.

The last man jumped away and trembling drew out his two daggers. He leaned forward, in a desperate attempt to stab Garen’s neck.

BAM!

Garen slapped the man like one would slap a fly. His victim lost his balance and was blown away by the impact. The man hit the wall, dropped his daggers, and remained stuck like a gruesome painting.

Garen inhaled heavily and quickly walked towards the wall. He then dragged the man by the hair and punched him in the stomach. The man coughed blood and it splashed on Garen’s clothes.

"Tough guys, huh? Without the invisible force shield, you’re all weak, just like any other normal person," Garen said.

"Ha…Haha…" Blood was coming out of the man’s eyes, ears, mouth and nose, but he could still laugh. "You’re done… You still live with your parents, right? And you have a young sister? White Stallion is on his way to your home. If it was not for the Master’s order, I’d be having a great time with the young girl… But White Stallion is worse than me… He’s going to f*ck your sister to death! Hahaha!" the man yelled until his last breath.

Crack!

Garen broke his neck without hesitation.

"Telling me your friend’s location, huh? Don’t worry… He’s going to be there with you soon…" Garen said.

He went back to the ground and rushed out of the backyard, leaving a hole where he came down. With just one step, Garen moved four meters forward and soon disappeared in the morning mist.

Chapter 72: Shifting Destiny 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

White fog surrounded Huaishan City without anyone taking notice of it.

From the main street to the back alley, everything was covered in fog.

Bluetree Street.

Rows of light yellow covered buildings stood side by side. A man could be seen strolling along the sidewalk in his white suit, playing with the keys circling his finger.

"This mission isn’t half bad… I can have a rest, even take a break from those three idiots. Also have a taste of a little girl as an extra."

The man seemed to be mumbling something to himself as he walked with a wide smile across his face. His eyes fixated on the little girl not far in front.

The little girl was Ying Er, who was leaving her house to buy some stuff. She was wearing a white t-shirt and low-waist jeans with her waist line showing. She had the slim legs and waist that many girls envied her for. Though her chest was not fully developed and her looks were average, but this young body that was rich with youth was the type that White Stallion liked the most.

White Stallion followed closely behind and couldn’t help but gulp, noticing the movement of her hips while she walked.

"I should take action once there are fewer civilians around…" He counted the distance and resisted his urge to act immediately.

After some distance, he spotted Ying Er humming while turning right into a narrow back alley.

White Stallion was delighted by the situation and increased his pace. It could be seen from his face that he could not hold back anymore. A white handkerchief appeared on his hand out of nowhere, coated with something needed for this occasion.

Clack. Clack. Clack.

Suddenly, footsteps could be heard coming from the corner ahead of him. Three tall men slowly walked out from the alley, each of them with golden earings of various sizes hanging from their left ears.

The three men prevented White Stallion from entering the alley.

"Piss off!" The good-looking one among the three told him. He seemed to be the leader of the group. His expression was dim, obviously in a bad mood.

This guy in front of White Stallion wore a brown coat with a furry collar and had his hands tucked into his pockets. His hair was bright red, like a fire burning in a fog. The golden earing hanging from his ear was carved with a clear number 6.

"Puny mortal…" The smile on White Stallions face faded. "How dare you to address me in this tone…"

The red-haired man was taken aback. He didn’t expect someone to speak to him in that kind of manner. He let out an awkward smile before speaking,

"It’s been so long since someone dared to speak to me like this…." He took out his right hand from his pocket. "It seems as though you are one of those experts that are tracking me… Would be disrespectful of me if I don’t give them a gift…."

"Cocky… Still, mortals are mortals." White Stallion smirked, reaching out with his right hand to take off his black gloves, revealing the Black Pentagon Tattoo. "I will gouge your eyes out and keep them for my new collection." A mysterious energy began forming around him.

"You must be looking for a death bed…" The two men beside the red-haired man retreated after he raised his hand. Oddly enough, a blood red scar began emerging from below his right eye. It looked like an eye shadow done by a lady, sharp yet enchanting.

Huff…

A wind blew past, racking up some leaves along the way.

*************

Garen was running hastily through the streets, surging past the pedestrians. He had already taken off his shirt and was gripping it under his arm. The upper part of the shirt was stained with blood.

"Damn it… Please don’t be in trouble!" His face was pale, heart growing more impatient by the second.

It was a 20 to 30 minutes’ walk to get from Pennington Street to Blue Tree Street, but Garen managed to reach his home in ten. Unfortunately his parents must’ve gone out, as well as his little sister, Ying Er. Garen wasted no time leaving the house and continuing his search along the street.

He was trying to figure out where his sister might have gone to while running wildly around the neighborhood.

"She might’ve gone to the market at this hour! Or maybe she’s at a fruit stall!"

Garen hesitated for a while before deciding to head off to the market.

The scenery beside Garen started to blur in reverse yet the road ahead of Garen was still clear in his eyes.

"Pass this crossroad and make a right turn, then I should make a left turn after a few hundred meters."

Thump!

A muffled sound came from the empty street in front.

A blurry figure could be seen flying in the fog. It tumbled to the ground and rolled a few times before stopping in front of Garen’s boots.

He came to a halt, lowering his head to look at the man lying in front of him.

A suit dirtied to a point where it was barely recognizable to have been white once. Right now it was only grey and brown due to numerous stains. Even the man’s neat hair was thrown into disarray. However, what was most worth noting was that both of his arms were twisted in an unnatural way, obviously broken.

Then Garen noticed the Black Pentagon Tattoo at the back of his right hand.

"It’s similar to those guys’ tattoos…"

He bent over and grabbed the man’s collar, bringing him upward.

"You’re White Stallion?" he asked. After all that running, his breathing took a bit of minor adjustments to return to normal.

"It’s you… Hehe… I can’t believe I will die in the hands of a mortal…" White Stallion chuckled before letting out his last breath. His eyes slowly faded as his soul began to seep away from his body.

Garen was stunned by what he had just witnessed. He shook the body for a while before noticing a black shape emerging from White Stallion’s neck’s right side. It was connected with the Black Pentagon behind his right hand.

Garen tossed away the corpse and let out a breath. He took a few steps forward as he began to see clearer what was ahead of him.

Three tall men wearing golden earrings sat in front of a narrow back alley with exhausted looks on their faces. Dark blood stains could be seen under the nose of the one with red hair.

The red-haired man raised his head to look in Garen’s direction after hearing the footsteps.

"It’s you." He let down off his guard for a moment. "Damn it, I thought there was another monster like him coming!" He scowled while trying to get up using a wall.

"Might I ask, expert, what kind of monstrous opponents are you facing exactly? I even had to let out my qi-gong because of him! You’re lucky I got here in time or your sister would be in deep trouble by now."

Garen just nodded along, not knowing what had happened. He noticed that the golden earring on the man’s ear had a number 6 carved on it.

"I owe you one, Sixth Golden Hoop." He turned his eyes toward the other two. "What about them?"

"Temporary henchmen, they practice Body Hardening Technique. They helped me block some of the attacks but from the looks of things they won’t live long." The red-haired man shook his head. "I’ll have someone inform their families." He suddenly turned and looked at Garen furiously.

"I’ve already taken care of this incident for you! Don’t tell me you’re still not joining the Golden Hoop? Don’t blame me if I turn against you!"

Garen was speechless. All he could do now was force a smile.

"Take this!" The red-haired man tossed a piece of a golden earring toward Garen.

Garen caught it properly and took a look at it. It was a golden earring with a number 9 carved on it. It was as big as a finger nail and it looked delicately made.

"Temporary replacement for Ninth Golden Hoop?"

"Not temporary. Didn’t you almost take care of Tenth Golden Hoop? It’s only natural that you have this ranking." Number Six sneered.

"You even know this?" Garen was stunned.

"The trait of your combat arts is too obvious, even your whereabouts are too obvious."

Garen shrugged, having nothing to say.

"Alright, go take a look at your sister. I have to ask someone to take care of things here." The red-haired man wiped off the blood stains from around his nose and walked toward the dead corpse.

Garen picked up his pace and walked into the back alley. This was the shortcut his little sister always took. After getting out of the back alley, Ying Er’s back figure finally appeared within Garen’s eyesight.

He rushed out, hugging his little sister.

"Ying Er!"

Ying Er felt a familiar presence hugging her from behind. She almost dropped the tomatoes and potatoes that she was carrying from the market, startled by this sudden action.

"Brother! What are you doing! Are you not embarrassed? We are on the main street!" She struggled to get away from Garen but felt the difference in strength between them. Trying a few more times to no avail, she gave up and just let him do what he wanted.

"Ying Er… I’m so glad you’re fine…." Garen held his half-a-head shorter sister tightly in his arms.

"Fine from what?" Ying Er was being hugged by Garen from behind with her hips awkwardly positioned against Garen’s crotch region. "Let me go or I’m going to be so pissed!"

"Okay, okay, I’ll let go." Garen also felt the awkwardness and swiftly removed his arms from around his sister. He was relieved to know his sister’s current condition. Most of the passers-by stared at them ambiguously, assuming that they were a in a relationship.

"Where is mom and dad?" Garen asked, ignoring the attention of the passing people.

"They went to get some coal and firewood. The winter is coming, we need to have these stuff prepared to avoid getting cold." Ying Er held up the groceries she bought from the market. "It’s your turn to carry this as a punishment for the jump scare just now!" She shoved the sack to Garen.

"Okay!" Garen was relieved. He felt good at this moment.

"I have to continue buying groceries. You follow me closely and try not to lose me okay?" Ying Er turned and walked forward, toward the sidewalk not far in front of her. Both sides of the street were full with various stalls selling vegetables along with some housewives who had woken up early to pick the fresh ones.

Garen carried the groceries with one hand, while tucking away the golden earring into his pocket with the other.

"I owe the Golden Hoop big this time… Still, at least the safety of my family is guaranteed. If the Golden Hoop’s background is what Number 8 said…"

If it was true, it should be a good thing for Garen to join the Golden Hoop. One thing for sure was that he had to be cautious when he was around Dale and the gang. One false move may lead to them discovering his secret identity.

Taking a deep breath, Garen realized that he was too lazy to concern himself with this issue. His heart sank when he recalled that the old man had gotten himself into trouble.

"Judging from the looks of these guys just now, the old man should’ve been a respectable figure in the past. Just his name was enough to frighten them back there. As to the master they were mentioning…"

Cold determination flashed through Garen’s eyes.

"Whoever brought harm to you, I swear, I will take revenge for you… I swear."

A sweet and fishy smell suddenly burst from his chest and to his throat. Garen immediately covered his mouth and forced it back down. His entire throat was covered with a sticky smell of blood.

It was the internal injury he had gotten from forcing himself to fight the three black-suited henchmen earlier on. He didn’t take the time to adjust himself before rushing out from the scene. It was not until 10 minutes after that he took a proper rest.

If it wasn’t for Garen’s strong physique, and he was like other Martial Adepts, he’d be left unable to move.

"That power felt like psychokinesis. Its force was really strong. Luckily it was countered by pure strength, but other types of fighters would find it difficult to face. Maybe I can get some evidence from the corpse…"

Chapter 73: Meeting and Discussion 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen applied direct pressure to his chest and tried to hide his injury. He thought he needed to go to the Dojo and ask for Master’s help.

"Ying Er, I will have lunch at the Dojo so don’t wait for me. I will take the groceries back home first," Garen said.

"Dojo again… Mom and Dad are home today," Ying Er said, disappointment etched on her face.

"Don’t be upset. I heard they got a better job and we’ll be able to spend more time together now." Garen patted his sister’s head and smiled. He asked Master to move his parents to a better position, and it seemed as if Master had already done it.

Garen’s uncle could do something like this easily, but for some reason he never helped his parents. He arrived home and put everything down, then went straight to the Dojo.

There were a lot of repairs going on in the city, and many infrastructures were being rebuilt. Garen could see workers and bullock cars that carried materials everywhere. The downtown area had become messy, no longer as clean as before.

He kept thinking about the three people he met earlier, while quickly walking down the street, and just felt that something was not right.

"If the invisible force field was the talent the old man talked about before, the key to all the questions would be the book he asked me to read that day." Garen thought he finally found a clue. "After watching me read the book, the old man looked disappointed and said I was not talented. I’ve not seen that book since. It may contain the answers to all my questions…"

Garen slowed down a bit. He saw a pancake stand moving towards him after turning at a corner. The owner of the stand smiled and handed him a small piece of paper before passing.

Garen stopped for a second and looked at the piece of paper. A Golden Hoop was drawn on it, and there was a sentence written below the graph: ’28-3 Stone Bridge, Willow Street. Urgent.’

Garen put the paper into his pocket and took a deep breath. He then turned back and crossed the street.

********************

East of the Huaishan.

A yellow river slowly ran across the city area, and it looked like a wide yellow ribbon dividing the city in half. But it was a dirty one.

There were many square shaped light-yellow houses on both sides of the river. Some of them were tall and some short. They looked like a bunch of unorganized blocks. Sometimes, people in the houses could be seen through the windows.

There were many dark yellow stone bridges built over the river. Many pedestrians and cars were going across them. There was a silver black bust standing in the middle of one bridge that was far from the downtown area. The bust with its stand was about three meters tall, and it was a man with a moustache surrounded by flowers.

There was a bronze introduction panel in front of the bust, and a man in check sweater was standing beside it. The man was about 30 or 40 years old. He had brown eyes and an aquiline nose. With his short grey hair, he looked ruthless.

A strong young man with short purple hair appeared on the left side of the bridge and slowly walking toward the bronze panel. He was wearing a black sweatshirt, though the shirt was large, it could barely hide his muscles. The sunlight was not strong, but the young man’s arms still looked shiny.

"Master Nine?"

Garen heard the voice and looked at the man’s aquiline nose. The man revealed a golden earing he was holding with his right hand.

"Nine?" Garen scrunched his eyebrows and stared at the man. He then realized he just took over position of Number Nine. "What’s the matter?" he asked.

"Master Six was checking the retrieved bodies, and he thought you would be interested in the results. He asked me to inform you about them," the man answered respectfully. His voice was low, just enough for Garen to hear him.

"The bodies… Lead the way." Garen’s expression changed, and he said with a deep tone.

"Sure, please follow me."

They went across the bridge and left the downtown area. There were many oxcarts and carriages on the road. Garen barely saw any cars around, just ox feces by the roadside from time to time.

They crossed two streets and walked into a narrow path beside a small hill. On the other side, there was a black wall separating the living area from the path.

The two had already left the city area, and Garen could hear insects making noises in the bushes on the side. He followed the man with an aquiline nose and kept checking the surroundings.

Quack. Quack.

Garen saw several white-feathered ducks crossing the path after turning a corner. An old farmer with a straw hat was guiding them with a branch. He looked relaxed. Garen and the man went around the procession and kept advancing. They saw an empty ground by the end of the path, and behind the empty ground, there was a small building that was surrounded by green trees.

The sunlight was blocked by the trees, and the building was covered in shadows.

"That’s it." The man stopped by the entrance of the building. "This is one of our bases in Huaishan. Please go to the second floor. The other masters are waiting for you there."

Garen looked at him but did not say anything and just entered the building. A lady with black hair walked out of one of the rooms on the second floor. She looked sexy dressed in a tight leather suit. The lady had a ponytail, and was tall and slim. Her eyes were dark purple, and they caught Garen’s attention.

The lady was pretty, but she seemed hard to approach. She saw Garen going upstairs and walked back into the room without saying anything. He felt a bit speechless.

"No.10 is here too… I guess she knows who I am." Garen shook his head and kept moving. There was a strong man standing by the entrance to the second floor.

"This way, please. According to the rules, please put on your earring," the strong man told Garen.

Garen nodded and took the golden earring out of his pocket. He hesitated for a second, rubbing his earlobe. He decided to just put it on his left little finger, turned the number side up, and entered the room on the right.

It was the only room on the right side of the second floor. It was big with a rectangle table, two bookshelves, and several high backed chairs. All of the furniture were made of some red wood. Garen could smell its light fragrance.

A man and a lady were standing in front of the bookshelves. The lady was Number Ten, while the man was blonde and had only one eye. They were talking about something.

Number Six and a pale man with a black cape were playing cards on the table.

"You’re here? We can start." Number Six stood up and laughed, he put down his cards. "Sorry, Number Eight, I win again."

"Bullshit!" Number Eight cursed. He stood up and looked at Garen. "You’re a bit late," he said.

"Sorry, I am not familiar with the route," Garen replied, nodding to him. Number Eight had invited Garen to join the Golden Hoop, and he was the only one Garen was familiar with. So he walked toward him and stood by his side.

"So, what’s the matter?" Garen asked.

Number Six smiled but did not answer the question.

He clapped and said, "Okay everyone. We’re here to discuss the thing about the Silversilk Castle. There are five members from the top ten here, and we haven’t met like this in years."

"Cut the crap!" Number 10 barked, stopping Number Six from saying more unnecessary things. "We’re busy organizing our territories and aren’t here to waste our time."

"Fine." Number Six scratched his head. "First, I would like to introduce our new member, Number Nine!"

Clap.

They clapped their hands several times but no one seemed to care.

"I still have no idea about the Golden Hoop." Garen shrugged.

"Take those," Number Eight handed Garen a stack of paper. "Leave them here after you finish reading. Someone will burn them."

Garen grabbed several pages, and found out they contained the information about the Golden Hoop.

He read through the information quickly, and learnt some basic knowledge about the Gold Hoop.

It was a large organization that sold antiques and jewelry. The top ten members of the Golden Hoop created an information network that collected rumours about antiques. If there were requests for certain items, the organization would do whatever they needed to get them for the buyers.

The top ten members were responsible for the organization, but they were not ranked with the numbers, and they all had their own territories and networks. They joined the organization just to make more profit.

Each of the top ten members oversaw a certain task: some needed to collect information about antiques while others needed to communicate with buyers. They could buy the antiques they wanted, or they could also get them from the others’ territories. They would work together as long as there were benefits.

Number Six spoke again while Garen was still checking the information. "Recently, our customers have shown a great interest in Antiques of Tragedy, and Number Nine is an expert of Antiques of Tragedy. He will make sure the antiques we get are real. This is the main reason I agreed to take him in."

"Also, Number Nine is a Martial Adept, and he is very close to rank E," Number Eight added. "We’ve already voted to confirm his membership and don’t need to discuss it anymore. Number Six, get to the point."

"Fine." Number Six nodded and looked at Number Ten. She did not seem to care about any of this. "We sometimes make changes to our top management, like Number Seven, who just joined us about two years ago. Well, let’s get down to business." His face got serious.

Chapter 74: Meeting and Discussion 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Just then, I had a fight with Number Four about that item from last time. You guys are well aware of that. So I was in a terrible mood and received the news from our dependents. They said people are targeting the relatives of the newly joined Number Nine. So I rushed there to unleash my anger. However, I didn’t expect…"

"What did you encounter?" Number Eight asked in a lowered voice.

"I don’t know." Number Six shook his head.

The other people focused their attention on him. He had obviously piqued their curiosity.

"Just be straight forward and tell us. What’s with the hesitation?" Number Ten grimly said. Number Seven beside her calmly glanced over with reticence.

Number Six closed his eyes and didn’t respond right away. He was instead trying to remember what had happened.

After ten seconds, he gradually opened his mouth.

"I originally thought it was releasing the body hardening technique outside of the body, but later I realized it was impossible." He looked at everyone, and even Garen, who was looking through the documents, raised his head to focus on him.

"I would imagine it was psychokinesis. The guy I encountered must be someone who possessed the power of psychokinesis from the legend!"

"Psychokinesis?" Number Eight rubbed his chin, pondering.

"You read way too many novels, Number Six." Number Ten sneered. "I still have a business that I need to negotiate. If you’re telling me something imaginary and fake, you’ll have to excuse me for leaving!"

"No, what he said is true," all of a sudden said the silent Number Seven. "I have seen psychokinesis before. The world they live in is completely separated from that of normal people. Just like martial adepts, they’re light years ahead of ordinary people."

"Do you have any evidence?"

"Unfortunately, no." Number Six shrugged. "There was a black tattoo on the back of the corpse’s hand, but for some reason, it disappeared after death."

"It’s gone?" Garen put down the documents.

"Mhmm, completely vanished," Number Six confided. "I got someone to dissect the corpse but didn’t manage to find anything useful. Psychokinesis is one thing I want to remind everyone to be careful of. If possible, collect some intelligence in this area. Number Nine, if you have any information, try your best to notify everyone since it originates from you. You also have to be aware that they are strong, at least the person I met was powerful."

Garen nodded.

"The second thing, it’s the white rock eye we have. It already has five bidders. Currently, 56 million is the highest price. The item was acquired through our back office, and the front office has nothing to do with it. Therefore, the money will be only divided among the people that contributed," Number Six explained. "The appraisal will be up to Number Nine. This thing could count as an Antique of Tragedy, and it is said that anyone who keeps the antique in possession for over two months would be overwhelmed with diseases and pain. The book of silence… I don’t know if it is true or not."

Joyous in his mind, Garen immediately nodded in agreement. "My appraisal is not a problem." He looked at some information and became aware of the difference between the front and the back office of the Golden Loop.

The front office consisted of the first five numbers, whereas the back office were the latter five numbers. The two sides never got on friendly terms since the relationship had always been strained.

"That’s good. Now we divide up the money. Number Eight is the pivotal contributor this time and takes home 80%. Number Ten receives 10%. Number Nine and I will each take 5%. Us four will divide the money. Number Seven will take 100 thousand from number eight that received the most as tradition. Is everyone okay with this?"

"Yes," Number Eight said. "Number Nine contributed a major amount as well and should be rewarded accordingly. If it were not for him, I wouldn’t have been able to acquire the item. I’ll split one-third of my share with him."

"It’s okay, 5% is more than enough." Garen smiled. "If it can be sold for 50 million, I can receive two million. It is enough."

"There is no rush. The money is not as simple as it looks." Number Six gestured. "As a newly joined member, you have to prove your worth to the group. Appraisal alone is not enough to assume the position as Number Nine. Everyone must complete a mission when they join which would be beneficial to the organization. It is your turn now.

Garen slightly raised his eyebrows. "Is this an examination? What kind of mission?"

"We don’t know yet. But next time when trouble arrives, you alone will have to take care of the problem. This is to prove your ability to handle difficult situations alone as part of the top ten golden loops." Number Six shrugged.

Unbothered, Garen nodded. "This is not a problem. Also, about those psychokinetic individuals, are there any leads? Regarding their origin?"

"The only thing we know is that it’s connected to the explosion case in a rural area. As well as the Dolphin antique store’s owner’s mysterious disappearance along with the three bodies found in the backyard."

"I killed those three people," Garen interrupted him. "Can you help me look for Old Man Gregor’s information? His store should be recorded within certain bureaus. At least his personal information."

"Let me try. Number Ten is in charge of Huaishan area. You can go talk to her about it." Number Six mischievously smiled at Garen.

Garen was speechless. He had just injured and almost accidentally killed Number Ten. It would be senseless to ask her for help now.

"If there are any leads, please let me know as soon as possible."

"No problem." Number Eight patted Garen’s shoulder. "Don’t be too sad."

"No need to be sad. I’ll eventually find him, and kill him!" Garen said calmly.

After the money was split, the white rock eye fell into the hands of Garen to determine its authenticity within three weeks. He took it and left the small cabin while everyone else dispersed separately as well. Only Number Ten stayed behind. It was her place after all.

******************

Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!

The black sandbag flew higher and higher.

Garen forcefully smashed the sandbag with all his might, one punch after another. The metal sand inside the sandbag concaved from the excessive force.

His upper body was exposed, and the sweat dropped down like rainfall. He was only wearing black shorts, and the contracting and expanding muscles gave a sturdy but flexible vibe.

"From a martial adept’s perspective, you’re doing quite well."

In the training hall behind his back, Fei Baiyun took a white colored chair and sat down firmly. He had a cup of hot tea in his hand and occasionally took a sip or two.

"White Cloud Secret Arts, Combat Techniques, Explosive Fist Arts. You have learned it all. The next step is to take it to real combat. You must fuse all the techniques into particular moves and fully unleash your potential. This is what you need to do. In a few days, you’ll go with me to a conference and see the skill level of other martial adepts," Fei Baiyun said in a calm and slow voice.

"Yes, Master," Garen answered respectfully, stopping his training.

"There is nothing wrong with hiding your power. It’s just that if you don’t usually fight at your limit, your performance would be below expectations in a critical battle. Although hiding your power would make your opponent underestimate you, there are always accidents. You can never completely hide." Fei Baiyun took another sip of the tea.

"Everyone at the conference will be martial adepts. You’ll have to remember that you can’t be arrogant just because you have some achievements. The White Cloud Gate is nothing within the martial adept circle. There are far stronger opponents out there. Don’t underestimate anyone because of your mastery in Explosive Fist Arts."

"Don’t worry Master. I know where my limit is." Garen nodded in agreement. After witnessing Golden Loops’ martial adepts as well as the existence of psychokinesis, his original thoughts of being considered a strong marial adept after a couple of breakthroughs were shattered. His opponents were stronger than ever, and no one was weak. This point alone was enough to eradicate his arrogance.

"As long as you understand. Now go back and pack a few things. We’ll leave the day after tomorrow. Remember to let your family know." Fei Baiyun smiled, pleased.

He was extremely satisfied by this latest disciple. As long as he didn’t betray the White Cloud Gate, everything else would be irrelevant. His potential and power were impeccable even compared to Farak. It was unbelievable that he managed to reach the second level of Explosive Fist Arts in just one year time.

"I’ll only bring you this time. I’ve brought your senior brother and sisters separately before. This is the opportunity for you to expand your understanding of the martial adept world. There will be plenty of opportunities to fight, and you must be prepared for them. Also, you’ll be representing the White Cloud Gate as the core disciple. You have to be cautious of your image."

"I’ll be leading?" Garen was surprised. "Master, how many people are going this time?"

"Including you, a total of five people. The other four are selected based on their potential. They are your junior brothers and sisters. You’ll have to take care of them." Fei Baiyun smiled.

"Ok…" Garen was slightly troubled as he had a lot of things that he needed to figure out, which meant he wasn’t in the mood to take care of other people.

It had been several months since he met with the Golden Loop. He had to return the rock eye within three weeks. He had also saved up four attribute points.

The Black Jade Disk was completely out of potential now. Garen tried to absorb the potential from the Bronze Cross Emblems at the Silversilk Castle that he got from Dale Quicksilver. However, the absorbing speed was too slow. It was questionable whether he could increase one attribute point in a year’s time.

Therefore, he only had four remaining attribute points left, and he was faced with the situation where he had ran out of potential that could be absorbed.

During this time, he used Manuyllton Corporation and the Golden Loop to collect Antiques of Tragedy, except that none could provide the potential at a fast enough pace. He started to suspect that the problem came from himself. Potential generated attribute points, therefore, when he was weak, it was easy to absorb a large amount of potential from any Antique of Tragedy.

But now, the potential he was absorbing was becoming negligible. A large factor in this could be that he was stronger compared to before, thus, to generate an attribute point a significantly larger amount of potential was required. Therefore, normal Antiques of Tragedy could not sustain his needs.

A stream of water was ample to fill a cup, but for a jug, it would be minuscule.

That was what Garen deduced. The stronger his body was, the higher amount of energy would be required. It would only be natural this way.

Chapter 75: The Speechless Martial Adepts 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There were no more sources of potential, as well as no leads to the old man’s death. It all made Garen impatient.

Adding to it the inheritance of his uncle’s business and the trouble caused by the teens from Lambrath’s mom’s side of the family, Garen was becoming even more frustrated.

He watched Fei Baiyun stroll out of the practice hall. He glanced at the attributes below his vision.

Strength 2.43. Agility 1.21. Vitality 1.88. Intelligence 1.51. Potential 498%. White Cloud Secret Arts: Mastery (Level four). Explosive Fist Arts: Intermediate. White Cloud Combat Arts: Intermediate.

"All four attributes have increased by 0.01. This is too slow." He let out a breath. "The daily exercises and routines are no longer useful for me. Adding attribute points is probably more helpful."

He gazed at strength for three seconds, and it gradually changed. It increased from 2.43 to 2.63.

"I can add it again?" Overjoyed by the finding, Garen suddenly realized something was different. "Why did only increase by 0.2?" He carefully examined the other attributes. Only strength had increased by 0.2 while the others hadn’t changed.

"What’s happening?" He took a deep breath. "I may have mistaken the original stats…"

He didn’t think too much about it and let his vision fall on Explosive Fist Arts. This was the move he was most dependent on. When he fought with Number Ten and later the psychokinetics, it was because of the absolute vibration and defense from this move that he had won.

The Explosive Fist Arts not only increased defense but also the effectiveness of attacks.

But after he gazed at it for a while, a few red symbols appeared gradually below the attributes bar as if explaining something. Garen glanced at it, and his facial expression suddenly changed.

"Attribute explanations?"

‘After the special ability collected information regarding the arts, one attribute point could be used to increase the level of beginner level skills. Two could increase intermediate skills, while advanced skills required five attribute points. The advance criteria had to be met before the skill could be leveled up. The unavailability of leveling could be a result of lacking information.

Absorbing the same type of attribute over a period would develop resistance within the body. The effect on body condition would decrease.’

The rows of the symbols were easy to understand for Garen.

"No wonder attribute points would have less of an impact on the body’s condition. I felt something was odd. It was okay in the beginning, but as soon as the ratio changed... The actual attributes decreased, just that I didn’t notice. After the prolonged period, the decrease became significant enough. But it was only after it became as large as 0.1 that I noticed it."

His vision focused on the Explosive Fist Arts. A symbol gradually appeared behind this skill, which was the missing criteria to level up this skill.

‘Five attribute points.’

Garen frowned. The last time the Explosive Fist Arts leveled up was because of the body quenching pill along with the attribute points. To increase the skill forcefully, it would require five points!

He only had three points remaining.

"If I knew this, I wouldn’t have added strength." He smashed the wall in regret. "Only missing two points. I need to find a way! But I have to attend the conference in two days."

The practicality of the Explosive Fist Arts was remarkable. Garen spent over half of his effort on this skill. If he improved this fist art to a mastery comparable to his master’s, his power would change significantly. If added with the fact that Garen’s strength had already reached its limit, he couldn’t imagine how powerful it would be if he achieved advanced mastery of the skill.

Garen carried his clothes when he left the White Cloud Gate. He stood outside in front of the rows of cars.

From a black car, Grace peeked her head out.

"Dale Quicksilver has new information."

"Oh?"

Garen opened the car door and sat down beside Cynthia. He glanced at Cynthia who was chewing on something. "What are you eating? It smells awful."

Cynthia smirked as she spat something black out of the car window.

Garen focused on Grace again. "What’s the new information?"

Grace looked at him through the reflective mirror as she said cautiously, "After what happened at the Silversilk Castle, Dale Quicksilver and his companions left the province to Evenia Province’s Blue Gulf City. The case is closed for now. A few of the Golden Loop’s middle managers were arrested. They also received a request for help from the police department."

"Do you know what exactly it is?"

"I think it is because of Huaishan City. The explosion case that night along with the murder at the Dolphin Antique Store. Pennington Street is where the high-end communities are located, which makes this a bit trickier. An incident on this scale not only shocked the governor’s office, it even angered the officers on the national level. So Dale Quicksilver and other famous detectives received an invitation to investigate this case."

Garen frowned slightly. "There are plenty of cases at Huaishan city, and murders are not that uncommon. Why did this one case trigger such a drastic response? There are many cases of homeless men that died in the alleys, but those don’t seem to bother them at all."

Cynthia, who sat beside him, began to giggle. "You don’t understand. The primary reason is that of the Silversilk Castle. The Golden Loops are too ruthless and cocky as they had the audacity to confront the police department. They even killed multiple police officers which caused a sequence of reactions. An investigation team was created to deal specifically with this case. The antique store murder had also happened during this sensitive period which stomped on the dignity of the provincial police department. It is no wonder then that they are furious over this. They’re certainly playing with fire. However, the newspapers and magazines are more than happy."

"In this case… the place Dale Quicksilver went to is related to the antique store murder?" Gloom cast on Garen’s face immediately.

"Yes. Based on the information from the police department in the other province, a similar murder had happened in a small town nearby. There an aged lady who also owned an antique store had went missing. It is rumored that she was connected with the old man from the Dolphin Antique Store. They were communicating through mail," Grace explained.

"Exchanging letters?" Garen’s expression tensed. "Grace, I need to attend a martial arts conference in two days with my master. I need you to keep an eye on information from Dale Quicksilver."

"No problem."

"What about me?" With an uninterested expression, Cynthia leaned over. "Bring me with you, I can warm the bed for you." She pouted with her pink lips and smiled gracefully.

"I’m going to my master. You’re in charge of protecting my family, is that okay?" Garen pushed her away as he had no energy left to waste time on these things.

"Wu… This is too heartless. This is the first time I am so proactive." Cynthia pretended to rub her eyes as if her feelings were hurt.

"Okay, that’s enough." Garen was speechless. "Dale Quicksilver’s ability to trace things is impeccable. Maybe he will find something I need. You have to keep a close eye on him."

"Okay."

**************************

~~~~

Two days later.

Wooooo!

With a deafening screech of a train horn, a dark red wooden train emitting black smoke gradually came to a halt at a terminal at Huaishang City.

Around ten people were scattered across the rectangular platform beside the train track. There were males and females, both young and old people. The majority of them carried a suitcase and covered themselves from head to toe with their jackets and trenchcoats.

When the train stopped, the conductor forcefully pushed open the door.

"Time to get on the train!" The white-bearded train conductor yelled. "Passengers at the ninth compartment get on the train. This is the train headed to Hela, don’t get on the wrong train!"

The passengers waiting for the train began to board in a line.

Among them, there was a young and an old man that carried a red leather suitcase. They both wore black wool coats along with black cap. They were Fei Baiyun and Garen of the White Cloud Gate.

They blended in among the passengers.

Garen followed behind his master. He passed the white ticket to the conductor before grabbing the red leather suitcase and stepping on to the train.

At the point of entrance, the left side was a sealed train compartment, while the right was the exit.

"Why are you standing there? Our seats are inside, hurry up and don’t block anyone." Fei Baiyun turned his head.

"Oh." Garen was distracted by the fact that it was his first time seeing such an ancient train, which slowed his actions. He hastened his steps to follow his master.

The compartment was a dark red color. The grains of wood were exposed inside the compartment. The entire train was made of this particular timber.

Four seats were divided into two rows, just like the individual rectangles that were scattered along the two sides of the train. The middle was a walkway.

The compartment was hardly filled with people. The master and student passed five rows of seats before finally stopping at the left side in the middle of the compartment.

There were already two people that sat there. A male and a female in their teens, and they were falling asleep. The two of them had certainly put some thought into how they dressed as both wore matching white shirts and pants. Judging by their facial features, they were brother and sister. Their hair was also idnetical silver white.

"Do you want to sit on the outside or inside?" Fei Baiyun glanced at the two people and pointed toward the seats.

"I’ll sit on the inside," Garen said without hesitation and took the seat.

Fei Baiyun smiled and didn’t say anything as he slowly sat down.

The two teens across them heard their voices and slightly opened their eyes. They kept their silence and then fell asleep in the same position.

Sitting, Garen carefully examined the two people across from him. He noticed that the girl’s hands were covered with calluses and had short fingernails. They looked rough and coarse.

"Teacher, how long is this train ride going to take?"

"Not long, about three days." Fei Baiyun took off his hat and tried to pat away the dust.

"Three days…" Garen let out a light breath. He stored the suitcases one by one underneath the chair before leaning against the window without saying a word.

Chapter 76: The Speechless Martial Adepts 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The death of the old man, the dispute between the Golden Hoop and Dale Quicksilver, and the mysterious enemy who had used telekinesis had been attracted because of the old man. These matters appeared one after another, causing Garem to be unable to settle down recently to practice his combat techniques.

Compared to these matters, the inheritance issue on his uncle's side, the exchange gathering between dojos, and meeting the chairman of Manuyllton Corporation were just small matters.

The thing that Garen currently wanted to do the most was finding the true murderer of the old man, and at the same time, the ones who threatened his family. Unfortunately, the telekinesis users who appeared to stop him did not leave any clues. Now, he could only count on Dale Quicksilver's side to find out more about them.

"Are you still thinking about that matter?" Fei Baiyun whispered beside him, "Don't think too much about it. From now on, you need to adjust your condition. This exchange gathering is not just an opportunity for you to gain experience, but also a chance for you to know your ranking."

"My ranking?" Garen nodded, "Just as well, I also want to know what level I am currently at."

Wu...

The train whistled once more, and the sound of the wheels moving against the tracks gradually rang out. As the rhythm started to increase in tempo, the train carriage gradually moved forward with an increasing speed.

The train carriage was also slightly livelier after some passengers got on.

Garen recalled the data that his master gave him the day before.

They were going to Hela City, one of the famous exchange gathering spots for Martial Adepts within their province and its surrounding provinces.

This exchange gathering was conducted by a local Secret Martial Art sect—the Celestial Circle Gate. It was also one of the three strongest clans in the confederation.

More importantly, the Celestial Circle Gate had an influential position within the northern part of the confederation. The main reason they hosted the exchanged gathering was not just for creating an opportunity for interaction between disciples, but to establish a ranking between each sect.

And during the previous exchange gatherings, White Cloud Gate's ranking within the Secret Martial Art world was number seventeen.

The two of them were going there earlier to reserve a strategic position during the exchange gathering. Otherwise, if they went late, the students from the dojo might not even have a place to stay.

According to the data, White Cloud Gate was within the ordinary martial arts world. However, it was only an unremarkable sect within Secret Martial Art sects that truly possessed ancient inheritance.

The Mammoth Secret Technique was the foundation of White Cloud Gate. The other techniques: White Cloud Combat Arts, Explosive Fist Arts, or the fundamental wrestling techniques, were all just simplified versions of this Secret Martial Art. It was the most powerful martial art within the entire sect.

However, within the entire Secret Martial Art world, there were many sects with similar Secret Martial Arts. This type of Secret Martial Art was actually just a fundamental martial art for tempering the body. The training requirements were strict, the training speed was extremely slow, and the external prerequisites required were troublesome. It was only considered third-rate within the Secret Martial Art world.

As a result, White Cloud Gate was only considered a third-rate sect within the Secret Martial Art.

Garen recalled the exhortation from his master on the previous day.

"When we get there, you need to remember to listen more, watch more, speak less, and create less trouble. Our White Cloud Gate is situated in a remote location, and we're still quite powerful locally. However, we're only considered insignificant outside, so we can't rashly get into a dispute with others. Of course, there are many sects like us in the exchange gathering, so there's no need for you to draw back when you have to display your strength. We might not be able to win against Martial Adepts from powerful sects, but we can still compete for the ranking against small sects."

For some reason, after recalling this, Garen could not help but think about his senior sister, Rosetta. Garen looked toward his master beside him.

"Master, what happened when Senior Sister came with you previously?"

"Rosetta?" Fei Baiyun was originally recuperating while shutting his eyes. When he heard Garen's question, he slightly opened his eyes. "She was still young when she went with me, around the age of seventeen or eighteen years old… At that time, her foundation was firm, but her talent was ordinary, and I had no intention of teaching her true martial arts. However, Rosetta completely changed after she returned from the exchange gathering and became reticent. Her personality began to change as well, and her talent suddenly improved. In the end, I decided to impart true martial arts to her. It was really strange, but my guess is that she probably received some sort of stimulus during the exchange gathering. Then she started to truly work hard after she went back and exhibited her true talent."

Fei Baiyun patted Garen's shoulder. "You're different. Your talent is much better. You'll definitely receive a huge improvement if I hand the White Cloud Gate's Secret Martial Art to you. This is the true foundation of our White Cloud Gate."

"I will definitely not let you down!" Garen heavily nodded his head. However, he still felt that his senior sister had a weird personality. She always acted mysteriously and was difficult to locate. She would appear from time to time, but no one would not be able to find her when they wanted to look for her.

Fei Baiyun thought for a while and took out a white piece of paper from one of the interior pockets in his black overcoat. The paper was folded into a small square. He carefully handed the squarish paper to Garen.

"Since your Explosive Fist Arts has already reached the level of minor achievement, you've also fulfilled the basic requirement of practicing the Secret Martial Art. This is the chant. Once you've memorized it, swallow the paper. This is the true key to the Mammoth Secret Technique and must not be divulged to others."

Receiving the piece of paper, Garen did not expect his master to give something so important to him on a train.

"Practice it on a train? Should I really do that?" He found it slightly unbelievable. "Shouldn't I find a safe and quiet environment?"

"There's no reason why you shouldn't." Fei Baiyun chuckled. "Various requirements are needed in order for this to work. This piece of paper was specifically soaked in medication. If other people were to practice the chant written on it, they would only become handicapped. Without a sufficiently strong Explosive Fist Arts as the foundation, it's all pointless."

Immediately after, he bitterly laughed again.

"Actually, our martial art is nothing profound in the eyes of other sects. A lot of the larger sects probably have something similar, and the effects would only be much stronger. Only we would act so carefully and think that it is important."

Garen nodded and was slightly able to understand his master's helplessness and sadness.

He looked toward the young people in front and found that they were still sleeping. That was when he softly opened up the paper in his hands.

There was only a line of words written on the white piece of paper. It was a revision of the utilization method of the second level of Explosive Fist Arts, the Vibration technique. After the revision and combined with White Cloud Secret Arts, a fundamental change would appear in the body. That was the so-called essence of the Mammoth Secret Technique.

"It's that simple?" Garen blankly stared at the line of words. He was wondering how difficult and complicated secret it would be.

"It's that simple," Fei Baiyun replied. "Eat it."

Garen was speechless. He looked at the paper once more, then crumbled it into a ball and directly threw it into his mouth.

The ball of paper had a salty and astringent taste and was slightly bitter as well. After chewing it a few times, he swallowed it along with his saliva. Garen smacked his lips.

Just when he was about to speak, Garen suddenly discovered the Skill Pane at the bottom of his field of vision had suddenly changed.

White Cloud Secret Arts and Explosive Fist Arts were gradually blurring. The two skills immediately disappeared, and a new skill gradually appeared. There was a mysterious symbol behind that provided an explanation.

——Mammoth Secret Technique— Greatly increases the toughness of skin and greatly increases explosive force. It is a strength type Secret Martial Art that emulates mammoths. There are two levels in total: White Elephant, Mammoth.

Currently, the state indicated behind the skill was White Elephant level.

"There's only two levels?" Garen was startled. "As the true secret technique of White Cloud Gate, there shouldn't only be two levels..."

"Your feelings are correct; there are only two levels. This is the true inheritance of White Cloud Gate. To put it bluntly, there's a lot of things that are only simple secrets. However, these secrets needed countless trials and errors to finally obtain the best result and combination," Fei Baiyun sighed and softly explained, "actually, Explosive Fist Arts does not have a so-called third level. The third level is actually the first level of Mammoth Secret Technique."

He patted Garen's shoulder. "Properly familiarize yourself with it. This time, go and take a look at other Martial Adepts. Look at their levels and their strengths, and you'll realize your current level. Don't be disappointed when you fail. As long as you don't give up, there's a chance for you to make a comeback!"

Garen solemnly nodded as well. If even Fei Baiyun—who was far stronger than him—was saying such a thing, then it was quite evident that there would definitely be many powerful opponents at this exchange gathering. Even Garen was starting to get worried as well.

"For Master to exhort in such a serious manner, the opponents are evidently not just ordinarily powerful. I definitely need to be careful."

Setting aside his distracting thoughts, Garen looked out of the train's window on his right.

Empty yellow paddy fields continuously flitted across his field of vision. The harvested paddy fields were filled with numerous tiny black dots as if countless wooden sticks were inserted into the paddy fields. Within the center of the open fields, there were bundles of straws stacked into piles. Once in awhile, farmers could also be seen transporting these piles of straws.

The grayish white sky had some dark clouds, and it seemed like it was about to rain. Two swallows flew across the sky as one chased after the other.

Garen felt his emotion was gradually calming down and once again looked toward his Skill Pane.

"I still have three Attribute points. Let's see if I can forcefully increase this martial art."

His line of sight landed on Mammoth Secret Technique.

Three seconds later, Mammoth Secret Technique slowly changed. It suddenly changed from White Elephant to Mammoth.

"It increased!" Garen's heart skipped a beat, and he carefully observed the changes in his body. Strangely, he did not feel anything from his body.

"It definitely increased! Why isn't there any changes?" He looked at his Potential Pane, and his Attribute points had indeed decreased by two.

"Could it be that it can still be increased?"

He looked at the Mammoth Secret Technique and noticed that it did not turn into a gray color, which meant that it could still increase. There was a symbol floating behind it as well, indicating that five Attribute points were needed to forcefully increase it.

Mammoth Secret Technique was actually just a crucial key that combined White Cloud Secret Arts and Explosive Fist Arts together. It was actually an overall harmonious adjustment to the body. This type of adjustment was very strange, and even Garen was not able to understand the theory behind it. However, it was evident that this adjustment had not reached its limit.

With doubts in his mind, he looked toward Fei Baiyun sitting beside him.

"Master, does this martial art really have only two levels? What's next after these two levels? Is there a possibility of continuing to improve?"

"I don't know." Fei Baiyun shook his head. "However, reaching the master level of the Mammoth level is already very troublesome. The glorious period of Martial Adepts is before the age of twenty-five. After we reach twenty-five years old, our body's functions, spirit, and vitality all start to weaken, and we're unable to advance to the next level. Putting aside what's after Mammoth level, no one in the older generations of our White Cloud Gate was unable to reach major achievement before the age of twenty-five. So..."

"So, there's a chance to reach higher levels by reaching master level before our spirit and vitality begin to deteriorate?" Garen thought of something and continued.

"That's correct. The improvement of Mammoth Secret Technique is very difficult, only your senior sister has a chance. Four years ago, she was at the White Elephant level. Now, she has already reached the Mammoth level and is only twenty-four years old. She's our White Cloud Gate's greatest hope..." when Fei Baiyun mentioned Senior Sister Rosetta, a smile subconsciously appeared on his face.

Chapter 77: Probe 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen's heart skipped a beat. If his senior sister was only at the master level of Secret Martial Art, would it mean that he was comparable with his senior sister right now?

"However, why aren’t there any changes to my body after combining them? In any case, I spent two Attribute points! There should at least be ripples even if I threw it into the water..."

This was what he was most confused about.

At that moment, the girl sitting across him opened her eyes and slowly woke up. She sleepily looked toward the master and disciple sitting across her and friendlily smiled toward them.

Garen smiled back at her.

"Are you going to Hela City as well?" the girl whispered.

"That's right, are you heading there as well?" Garen replied.

"That's right, why are you going there?" The girl brushed away her hair that was covering the side of her face. "With your age, are you going there to enroll?"

"Uh." Garen did not know how to respond. Could he just tell her that he was going to participate in a martial arts exchange gathering? It was actually forbidden to divulge the martial arts exchange gathering to outsiders since it was confidential.

Seeing that he did not reply, the girl smiled and assumed that her guess was right. From the looks of it, she probably assumed that Garen was a new student being sent to school for enrollment by his father.

"What about you? Are you going to Hela for a vacation?" Garen asked as his gaze slightly sized up the girl.

With long silvery hair coming down from her shoulders, the girl wore a white lace dress and gave off the aura of a magnanimous and refined lady. Her skin was fair and tender like it was coated with a layer of white powder. It was fine and smooth to the point where there were almost no imperfections.

The girl was like a young lady who went for an outing and gave off a very cultured and pure feeling. Even though she was not very pretty, this sort of quiet and graceful aura was abnormally rare.

Garen was reminded of Felicity who had just left Huaishan a while ago. She was different from the girl in front of him. If you judged her from her appearance, you would think that she was a haughty, dazzling, and beautiful young lady.

However, he was slightly baffled by the fact that the girl in front of him had coarse hands, which was completely inconsistent with her aura and the way she dressed.

"We're not going for a vacation. We're also going to enroll at the school. However, we're going there earlier to learn more about the local culture," the silver-haired girl smiled as she replied Garen's question.

Garen nodded in acknowledgment.

"Where did you set off from?"

"We started from Xining. Before you got on the train, we've been riding for over a day and a night." The girl covered her mouth and lightly yawned. "Oh… I am so tired. Even though I've been sleeping for so long, I still feel very tired."

"If you've only been sitting like this, then it would definitely be tiring." When Garen saw her yawning, he felt a little sleepy as well.

As the two of them had no other common topics to talk about, Garen turned his face over to look at the scenery outside of the window. A yellow beetle car was driving alongside the train at the same pace. The driver of the car was a man wearing an army uniform with aviator goggles on. He was glancing toward the train from time to time.

"That's the navy uniform of the Confederation. From the badge on his chest, this man should be a lieutenant in the Navy."

"Navy of the Confederation?" It was the first time Garen saw a regular military personnel of the Confederation, and he could not help but glance a few more times.

The train gradually surpassed the soldier's car, and Garen was feeling slightly tired just from watching the scenery as well. He looked beside him at his master and discovered that Fei Baiyun was sleeping soundly with his head tilted to the side.

Garen drowsily dozed off and slowly woke up after an undetermined amount of time.

The sky outside of the window had already turned dark, and the interior of the train carriage was slightly noisy. In the middle of the aisle, an attendant was slowly passing by while pushing a food cart.

"It's time to eat!"

Within the train carriage, there was a sparse amount of passengers. Some of them were yawning, while some stood up to buy food, and there were others that took out their own food to eat. Garen even heard children's voice yelling in a dialect that he did not understand.

The silver-haired boy sitting across of him had already woken, but he was not as friendly as the girl. He only faintly glanced at Garen and his master and did not converse with them.

His master, Fei Baiyun, was taking out a small sack that contained some cakes, bread, and two bottles of tea.

"This is dinner. Take it yourself."

Garen speechlessly looked at the cakes and bread that was crumpled together and almost could not differentiate between the two. He was completely without any appetite as he looked at it.

"Master… There's no reason for this… It's not like we don't have money..."

"What do you know!" Fei Baiyun glared at him. "This is something that someone had kindly made for me! It's not about the money!" as he spoke, he seemed to remember something, and a slight redness faintly appeared on his face.

Garen had a slight urge to puke… Looking at an old man foolishly smiling while blushing was indeed a little disgusting.

However, he still took a lump of cake that looked like bread and a bottle of black tea and placed them on his lap.

"Master's second spring..." He already knew who made the food. It was obviously master's lover.

He lowered his head and looked at the thing in his hand. Garen was still hungry a while ago but no longer had any appetite.

The silver-haired siblings sitting across of them were currently eating exquisite-looking buttery apple cakes while drinking coffee from a porcelain cup. The redwood lunchbox contained all kinds of pastries that were neatly arranged. There were red cherries, baked banana chips, pink cream, light yellow sponge cake, and a few pieces of vegetables as decoration.

Just based on the appearance, it was far superior to the thing in his hand.

As Garen looked at the lump in his hand once more, his appetite dwindled even more.

Fei Baiyun, the owner of a gigantic dojo that earned tens of millions per year, was currently eating such a wretched meal on the train.

Garen could not help but disdainfully look toward his master sitting beside him. He was stunned when he realized that his master had already finished the thing in his hands within a few bites and seemed to be choking as he guzzled the bottle of black tea.

As Garen looked at the soft and mud-like thing in his hand once more, he firmly decided not to eat it. He lifted up the bottle of black tea and drank a mouthful. Fortunately, the black tea was sweet since sugar was added and his hunger was satiated after drinking it. The only problem was that he had no idea how long that would last.

The sibling sitting across of them saw the scene and could not help but smile. Even the silver-haired boy was unable to continue pretending to be cold.

"If you don't mind, there's still some pastries in my lunchbox. Please try some," the silver-haired girl softly said to Garen.

"How could I do that.' Garen was originally planning to sneak out and buy food with his own money, but he was immediately tempted when the girl pushed the lunchbox over and smelled the rich buttery aroma drifting out.

They only ate half of the contents of the lunchbox, while the other half of the exquisite pastries were left untouched. The exterior of the pastries was attentively wrapped with a layer of plastic paper, so he could directly pick them up with his hands and eat. It looked clean and hygienic.

"It's okay, as long as you don't mind. I can tell that you forgot to prepare your own food," the girl gently smiled and said.

Garen sneaked a glance at his master.

"Since it's the kind intention of others, just eat it!" Fei Baiyun speechlessly slapped Garen on the head. When he looked at the exquisite pastries within the lunchbox and compared it with what he ate just now, he was feeling slightly imbalance in his mind.

"Thank you so much."

Garen gave a hollow laugh and received the lunchbox. He lightly lifted up an almond cake and took a bite. It tasted very aromatic and had a very fluffy texture. There was also a trace of almond flavor mixed inside.

The pastries within the lunchbox that were as big as his fist were eaten by Garen within a few bites and were quickly finished. He was originally prepared to hand one over to his master, but Fei Baiyun was obviously embarrassed about eating something from a younger generation and benefited Garen.

He managed to finish all of the pastries in the lunchbox within ten minutes. The siblings sitting across him were dumbfounded as they watched him.

"It's much more delicious than what they sell on the train. Thank you very much." Garen placed the lunchbox on the small rectangular table between the seats and gently pushed it back. "Sorry, I couldn't stop after I started eating..."

He was already very hungry, and the pastries inside the lunchbox were indeed very delicious. It was the first time Garen had tasted pastries that were this delicious, and they were much better than the ones sold outside.

"Is it really that delicious?" A smile appeared on the girl's face.

"They're very delicious." Garen nodded. "They're so much better than the ones being sold outside. Could you tell me where you got them? I'll definitely patronize the store next time!"

"It's good that you like it..." The girl was obviously very happy as she lowered her head in embarrassment and said, "I didn't buy them. I made them myself..."

The silver-haired boy sitting next to her was pouting as he muttered, "What's so delicious about it, is there a need to exaggerate so much? Really... "

"You actually made them yourself?" Garen was slightly surprised. "How remarkable. With this kind of skill, you can open your own store."

"You're kidding!" The girl was slightly embarrassed after being praised.

The boy sitting next to her immediately rolled his eyes. "You think that it's delicious when it's only at this level? What a country bumpkin..." He was in a bad mood as he looked at the muscular and tall young man sitting across of him. Even though there was not much of a difference in their age, there was a sharp contrast when they sat together as the other party was at least twice as muscular as him. Also, the moment he got on the train, he was looking around like he had never been on a train before. When he was eating just now, he was eating so fast that it seemed like he had never eaten anything for over ten years.

On the other hand, Garen and the girl were vigorously chatting. The two of them had already changed topics from pastry tips to the books they liked and their topics were endless. Next to them, Fei Baiyun and the silver-haired boy were bored and began to doze off once more.

With nothing to do on the train, they could only take a nap.

**************

Two days later.

Hela City Train Station

As a screeching whistle rang out, the mahogany train gradually came to a stop.

With a loud bang, a conductor vigorously pulled open the door of the train carriage. "Passengers bound for Hela City, it's time to get off!"

Within the train carriage.

"It's time to get off." Fei Baiyun patted Garen on the arm and was the first to stand.

Garen quickly pulled out a red leather suitcase from underneath their seats and stood up.

"We're finally here. Are you getting off as well?" he asked the silver-haired girl. The both of them had become quite familiar after chatting a few days.

The sibling sitting across them had brought out a small, black leather suitcase as well.

"That's right. Actually, we went to Xining for a vacation, and we're going back home now." The silver-haired girl embarrassedly smiled.

"I already knew it." Garen laughed and said, "While we were chatting the past two days, you were obviously more familiar with Hela and knew little about Xining. Alright, let's get off."

"Alright."

The four of them left their seats and followed the sparse stream of passengers toward the exit.

Chapter 78: Probe 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There were already several cars waiting near the train station. The silver haired girl walked to a silver sedan and turned to look at Garen and Fei Baiyun and their huge luggage. She hesitated.

"Their luggage looks really heavy, so they must be new to this place. Should we give them a ride?"

The silver haired boy opened the car’s door and curled his lips. "Up to you, but be honest with me, you seemed to get along with those two guys from the small town. Do you have a crush on that lubber?"

"Don’t say that." The girl bluntly twisted the boy’s ear. "So what if they’re from a small place? They seem to be quite well mannered to me. And what crush are you talking about? Are you trying to embarrass your sister over some casual talk?"

"They don’t look like students checking-in to me. They were hiding something from the way they talked, so they’re probably just some countryside hillbillies here for work. These days a lot of people from the countryside come to the cities to do hard labor." The silver haired boy frowned as he lightly pushed away his sister’s hand. "What’s so interesting about talking to some guys from the countryside? You’re just flattered by their compliments."

The girl thought so as well, especially since the two men were powerfully built and had rough hands. They had to have done a lot of farming work. But she was intentionally leaving out the topic about their family and occupation. And it was obvious that they were trying to avoid talking about it as well.

"So what if they’re farmers? What would you eat and drink without them?" She pinched her brother hard again. She then turned to the two strangers. "Where are you headed? Do you need a ride? I’m a local at Hela, and I could introduce you to our town."

Garen and his master Fei Baiyun were both flattered. It was nice for the girl to offer, but they already had other plans.

Fei Baiyun blinked at Garen, telling him to deal with his own trouble. He hadn’t interfered with Garen’s and the girl’s small talk on the train. He could see she was well educated, although he didn’t expect for this to happen.

Garen was dragged out by his master and looked reluctant.

"Actually, it’s fine, someone is coming to pick us up. But still, thank you very much for your offer."

The girl did not expect they would reject her, she nodded back. "Fine then, you guys take care. Goodbye."

"Farewell! Maybe we’ll see each other on a train again next time."

"Yeah, we might." The girl laughed and winking turned around and got back to the car.

"What happened? You got rejected?" The silver haired boy gloated.

"How do you know?"

"I’m telling you, people like him have big egos. He won’t accept help from a girl, especially a girl that he likes," the boy answered with confidence, sitting in the driver’s seat. "Did he say he has made plans and someone is picking him up? Guys who want to save face all do that. Even if he doesn’t have a ride, he wouldn’t want to disappoint his beauty."

The girl speechlessly glanced at her brother and got into the car. "Yeah, yeah, you are the all- knowing saint, all right? Most intelligent man on earth. And, I’m not a ‘beauty’, don’t try to give me a tall hat. Now drive, we should get home and rest. I’m really tired after riding the train for so long." She laid back in the passenger seat, her expression revealing her exhaustion.

The silver car slowly drove out of the train station, turned at the exit, and merged into the traffic outside.

Garen turned his gaze from the silver car and looked at his master.

"What do we do now, Master?"

"We wait," Fei Baiyun said casually. " The folks from the Celestial Circle Gate are coming to pick us up, so bring out your vigor and don’t let our White Cloud Gate down. Even if we are a small sect, we’re still the strongest in Huaishan City. If we lose our cool, Huaishan Secret Martial Arts get disrespected as well."

He looked at Garen. "You’re not only representing yourself now, but also thousands of disciples at the White Cloud Gate and the entire Secret Martial Arts community at Huaishan. Your senior brothers and sisters have already graduated, so technically, you are the eldest senior brother at the White Cloud Gate. Don’t lose our White Cloud Gate’s prestige."

"Yes, Master!" Garen answered sincerely. He vaguely understood his main goal on this trip.

Fei Baiyun was treating him as the White Cloud Gate’s next successor. He was treating him like a true heir to his mantle.

Garen adjusted his body form and lifted his spirit. He waited at the station with his master.

There were less and less passengers getting on and off at the isle. Soon, three young men came out of the entrance. They had great body forms and wore different clothing. The one who walked in the front had a hard-edged aura around him. He had blond hair and blue eyes, his expression cold.

The blond man approached at a fast pace and stopped in front of Fei Baiyun. The three of them bowed down and saluted.

"Is it master Fei Baiyun from Huaishan’s White Cloud Gate?"

"Yes, I am Fei Baiyun, and you must be Jaden. Last time I visited you were still an apprentice to your senior brother. But after all these years, you now take charge of things on your own," Fei Baiyun smiled and answered politely.

"You are exaggerating, sir, I wouldn’t say I’m ‘in charge’. This way please, the driver is waiting for us at the exit," Jaden answered respectfully, lowering his head.

"Very well, lead the way." Fei Baiyun nodded, following Jaden and the other young men.

Garen strolled along behind his master. A handsome young man behind Jaden took a step back to walk in parallel with him.

"Senior brother, your luggage looks heavy, let me help you carry it," he whispered and reached out with his hand, clawing toward Garen’s wrist.

His movement looked like he was trying to help. But in reality, his fingers were held together and fast like a thrusting sword, stabbing toward Garen’s wrist silently.

Garen’s heart skipped a beat. He knew this was the Celestial Circle Gate trying to probe his strength. Master must have noticed, but did not turn around. He knew this would happen.

The opponent was too fast, there was no time to react.

With a faint sound of impact, the young man’s finger hit Garen’s wrist. Both of them froze.

"So weak." Garen watched speechlessly as the young man blushed. "Is this for real? A mosquito’s sting could be stronger than this."

The young man’s face was completely red. He raised his head and gazed at Garen with astonishment.

Both of them were speechless.

Garen had no words. What should he say, "Wow I’ve heard so much about you, your finger strength is truly unmatched!"? He planned to say this before, but now if he said this, they would think he was sarcastically mocking them.

"So- sorry." The young man’s face turned white and red. He walked up to Jaden and his shoulders began to shudder. He was crying.

Garen was out of words again. "I was the one that got hit … Why are you crying?"

Fei Baiyun turned around and gave Garen a scolding stare. Garen looked back with an innocent expression.

"It’s none of my business, Master… I didn’t even hit him back. Is standing still and taking the hit a bad thing to do now?" Of course he couldn’t say it out loud, but he was puzzled in his mind.

"Isn’t this the Celestial Circle Gate disciple too fragile? …" He looked at the young man again, suddenly seeing his long and slim legs together. There was no gap between them at all, and he had an amazing S curve around his butt and waist.

He looked again at the youngster’s neck. The skin was white and smooth, and there was no Adam’s apple.

"So he’s a girl…" Garen realized. "Now I’m in trouble."

Sure enough, Jaden turned around and looked at him. There was fire in his eyes.

Garen straightened his face and back. He narrowed his eyes and stared back at Jaden, trying his best not to show any sign of weakness.

The group soon exited the station, and there were three cars parked to the right of the exit. They looked luxurious, and there were even decorative silver linings on them.

"Master Fei, would you please ride in the first vehicle. I will accompany your esteemed disciple in the second." Jaden respectfully opened the door for Fei Baiyun.

After settling down master Fei, he came back to Garen.

"Please."

"Thank you." Garen nodded, ready to get into the car.

"Your luggage is a little too big. It’s not easy to fit in there, so why don’t you let me help." As Jaden’s voice came, his right hand turned into a white shadow, jabbing toward Garen’s wrist.

This move was a lot faster than the girl’s earlier, and it felt powerful too. His fingernails were emitting a sharp, knife-like aura.

Jaden’s eyes turned cold. His fingers split up, the white shadow turning into five, and simultaneously grabbed toward Garen’s wrist. There was no chance to dodge, Jaden’s hand was like five steel knives slicing down.

Garen’s face turned cold. His wrist suddenly swelled, and his skin and muscles instantly turned blue and dark. He was ready to take the hit without dodging.

Bang!

After a thud, Jaden felt pain in his fingers. But he acted like nothing had happened and took his hand back. He sneered and sat in the front passenger seat.

Garen looked down at his wrist. It had five distinct white marks. He felt a stingy pain as the attack had almost scratched his skin.

"Worthy of the the Celestial Circle Gate’s name, this should be fun." Even though he did no use the secret arts to strengthen his body, his resilience at a normal state was extremely strong already.

Right now, the two were just trying each other out, and the first round was even.

"Looks like I have to keep working hard, a disciple from the Celestial Circle Gate is this strong. If I faced someone stronger from other places…" Garen thought as he entered the car with his luggage.

"Drive," Jaden whispered to the driver.

The luxurious silver lined black cars slowly accelerated. There were even two police cars in front of them, whom the traffic avoided dodging in both directions.

Three cars formed a line and drove steadily forward.

Chapter 79: The Exchange 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Sitting in the car, Garen glanced at the driver and Jaden sitting in front. Both were silent. It didn't seem like they intended to speak.

He turned to look out the car window. The buildings in Hela City were similar to those in Huaishan City, but taller. Some were even tens of meters tall, straight and boxlike, like huge pieces of stacking blocks. The shadows they cast were massive and black.

The motorcade seemed to drive from under the shadow of a building immediately into another. Garen could vaguely make out that there were external lifts on the sides of some of the tall buildings. They were those old-fashioned ones made of wood and metal with an extremely slow speed.

Pedestrians on the streets were fashionably dressed. Some girls and rich ladies even wore slightly revealing clothing, displaying their slim figures.

The motorcade kept going forward. Time passed. The buildings on both sides became less dense and older. The scene outside gradually resembled Huaishan City, and the pedestrians seemed to dress more modestly as well.

This was the first time Garen left Huaishan. Previously, he had thought it was one of the more modern places of this era. He didn't expect Hela City to be so much more developed than it.

The car slowed as it drove into this area. Soon it turned a corner into an underground carpark within a housing area.

The car gradually slowed to a halt, and the engine was cut off.

"We're here. Please step out," Jaden said in a low voice.

Garen nodded, pulled the handle and stepped out. He scanned the whole underground carpark—it was filled with silver-striped cars. There were a few still driving in, yet to park, and some with car doors open and the passengers standing around the cars taking in their surroundings.

The sound of car doors closing echoed around the carpark. His master Fei Baiyun stepped out accompanied by two Celestial Circle Gate disciples. Garen quickly walked over to follow behind his master.

"This way please." Jaden bowed respectfully, then walked toward the elevators in a far corner of the carpark.

A few Celestial Circle Gate disciples trailed behind, leading Garen and his master.

"What a grand display by the Celestial Circle Gate. They escorted us with police cars and sent so many disciples to receive the practitioners of Secret Martial Art from all sects," Garen said.

"This is normal. The Gate Master of the Celestial Circle Gate has several disciples who serve as senior officials in this province and a few other neighboring ones. He has a lot of soft power," Fei Baiyun explained softly. "You'll be directed to the student area later. Take care, don't get into trouble."

"Yes, Master." Garen nodded.

They followed Jayden into the elevator.

The inner walls of the elevator were made of mahogany. It was spacious inside. The floor was covered with a square black rug with "The Celestial Circle Gate" printed in calligraphy on it.

The few of them were silent inside the elevator. The movement of the elevator could barely be felt.

Ding…

The elevator announced its stop, and the doors slowly opened. Beyond the doors was a black corridor with stone floor and walls. Every few steps along the corridor, a disciple in a sharp black suit stood in attention, lending a sense of formality to the atmosphere.

The corridor was linked to others at both ends. From time to time, there would be people in all manner of dress passing through the corridor, escorted by the Celestial Circle Gate disciples. All of them went toward the left.

Jayden led Fai Baiyun and Garen into the corridor, then turned left into a wider one.

Garen walked along the passage. He could feel the cold hard stone surface beneath his feet. There was a faint scent of incense in the air.

He had a vague sense of excitement. It was his first time being at a grand event like this. Putting aside all else, just by looking at the two rows of disciples in black suits standing in attention—sharp and alert, with fingertips like sharp spikes, emitting a faint white glow—one could tell that they were not mediocre.

His master in front started greeting peers upon turning the corner. It seemed like he had met some close acquaintances. Fei Baiyun put his arm over the shoulder of a short and stout man and walked with him. They greeted each other affectionately.

Garen lowered his head and looked solemn.

He walked into a small hall with a circular fountain.

"Senior Brother, please follow me," a Celestial Circle female disciple walked over to Garen and politely said. She led him away from Fei Baiyun and the rest, toward a corridor on the right. Several disciples from other sects, like Garen, were led toward the same direction.

They followed the female disciple to the end of the corridor and entered a spacious square black hall which was filled with large mahogany round tables and chairs. A lot of people were already seated inside.

By a wall in the hall, a few clowns in colorful clothing were performing an act, attracting bursts of laughter from the crowd.

No one noticed as Garen walked in. The female disciple handed him a sign with 'The White Cloud Gate' written on it and left.

He found an inconspicuous corner to sit down and stuck the sign into the placeholder on the table. Full-length windows spanned one side of the hall. Even though Garen sat in an inconspicuous corner, but it was right by the full-length windows. He could look out down below.

He turned his gaze there. He saw the middle floor of the grey building opposite. There were three more floors below that. That meant that he was on the fourth floor. He could vaguely make out the e Celestial Circle Gate disciples escorting people and constantly walking around in the building opposite. They entered another large hall.

"What a grand event…" Garen couldn't even begin to speculate how many similar large halls there were, but it was clear that this wasn't the only one.

Not long after he sat down, a muffled commotion seemed to come from the corridor’s entrance.

"Beo is here…"

"It's Beo!"

"Such a big reputation. I'd like to see how great this so called 'one of the two stars of the South' is," a bald man sitting at a round table toward the front right of Garen sneered.

"One of the two stars of the South?" Garen looked up toward the entrance.

After a few seconds, a blue-haired youth wearing casual dark blue clothes walked in. He looked indifferent. His eyes, brows and hair were all blue, even his skin had a blue tinge to it, which gave him an ice-cold impression. The youth scanned the hall and walked straight toward the front-most table on the right. A group of people in white automatically stood up and gave him their place. They moved to an empty table at the back and sat down.

"Thank you," Beo calmly said, then sat down.

"I can't believe…" a middle-aged man said woefully. He was sitting with a woman of similar age to Garen's right.

Garen looked at the sign on their table. It read "Orthogon Sword".

The man who sighed had black hair, black eyes, white skin and a tall nose. He seemed to be of a mixed race.

Garen hesitated slightly, then poked his head over and asked, "Sir, who is this Beo? Why is he blue from top to toe? And they call him 'one of the two stars of the South'? Do you mind enlightening me?"

The middle-aged man was stunned for a moment, then a smile broke across his face. He glanced at Garen's sign on the table.

"I see you're from the White Cloud Gate. Our Orthogon Sword Gate is right by your dojo, we've heard of your sect. I'm Raydon. It's an honor."

Garen was stunned. He saw a room full of foreign people with all types of hair and skin colors speaking in a Chinese-martial-art-world tone. Even though they were speaking different languages, it still felt bizarre.

"I'm Garen, brother Raydon. Can you tell me more about the Secret Martial Art scene in the South?"

"Of course." The man looked like a talkative person. He came over and started explaining in detail about the whole Secret Martial Art situation in the South.

"Looks like you're a new disciple. I'll explain it to you in detail. The strongest sects in the Secret Martial Art world in the South are the Celestial Circle Gate and Crimson Sand Sword. I don't have to say much about the Celestial Circle Gate. They train in the Celestial Circle Fist. Their fingers are extremely powerful. You will see it in the next few days. Crimson Sand Sword is another large sect. They occupy two provinces in the South, but are slightly weaker than the Celestial Circle Gate. This Beo is currently the most outstanding disciple in Crimson Sand Sword, comparable to Andrela of the Celestial Circle Gate. It is rumored that he has trained in the Secret Martial Art of his sect to a terrifying stage. His true strength has almost surpassed their masters and elders."

"Surpassed masters and elders? Is it possible? This Beo doesn't look a day older than twenty-five. His true strength is that powerful?" Garen was slightly surprised.

"You should know, in the Secret Martial Art world, strong youths have the physical advantage. Experts who are a generation older can only rely on their rich experience. In order to achieve a higher level, if they don't do it in their youth, by twenty-five or so, they wouldn't have a chance after that. But before then, it all comes down to talent and effort. Andrela of the Celestial Circle Gate and Beo of Crimson Sand Sword are the type of geniuses who are not lacking in both. Coupled with the best Secret Martial Arts, it wouldn't be difficult for them to become powerful," Raydon lamented. There was a hint of envy in his eyes. "The body weakens with age. No matter how you maintain it, your true strength would start declining. Such is the law of nature. There is no way of resisting."

"You have worked hard enough," the middle-aged woman comforted Raydon, gently holding his hand.

Garen seemed to be deep in thought.

"So Andrela and Beo are the two strongest people from the South?"

"That I'm not sure of, but it should be the case." Raydon nodded. "It is a widely recognized fact that Andrela is the top Secret Martial Art practitioner in the South. Beo lost to him in the previous tournament. But from the looks of it now, he seems to have had a breakthrough. It's apparent that he is prepared to compete for the top spot again."

"There's going to be a good show then!" Garen said excitedly. "I haven't witnessed the true strength of a real Secret Martial Art expert. This is the perfect chance."

"You look quite young. I'm sure you're very talented. No wonder your master brought you here to gain experience," Raydon said with a smile. "But you may have gotten the wrong idea. Before they fight, we from the smaller sects would have to duel first."

"We have to duel first?" Garen was confused for a moment, then instantly understood. "That's right. If the strongest duel first, who would still want to watch us fight?"

"It's great that you can understand that." Raydon smiled and didn't say more.

Garen then asked about some common knowledge in the Secret Martial Art world.

There weren't many people in the Secret Martial Art world, but every one of them was at a strong level envied by general martial art enthusiasts. Not to mention, there was much sway and power involved behind every sect. With so many of them gathered in one place, even though it was the era of firearms, the government still had to increase the scale of security to be able to provide a timely response if and when conflict arose.

Chapter 80: Exchange 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Of course, martial artists couldn’t fight against strong firearms. But the forces behind them, the combination of martial arts enthusiasts, their communities and their influence was still a force to be reckoned with.

The police cars clearing the way was primarily to separate the martial adepts from normal people. After all, some of them were monsters unaffected by small firearms.

Garen got to know more about the Secret Martial Arts scene from Raydon.

The Secret Martial Arts scene was divided into the Northern and Southern sects. The Celestial Circle Gate and the Crimson Sand Sword led the Southern sects while the Gramdon Sword Sect led the North.

It was unclear to them what the situation in Northern side was, but the Southern scene was very chaotic. Small sects came and went every decade. Even some middle-sized sects fell from power. Only the unshakable Celestial Circle Gate and the Crimson Sand Sword thrived on throughout the years.

The biennial exchange held by Celestial Circle Gate was less of a communication event for all sects and more of a show of power between it and the Crimson Sand Sword.

Inside the main hall, an opera show started after the clown performance, and after that was a diva battle which made all the men start howling.

Two divas with hot bodies walked on the stage and started fighting. Whoever lost would strip off a piece of clothing. The blood of male audience sitting below started boiling.

However, the Celestial Circle Gate had full control of the situation. The two ladies left the stage in their underwear.

A band immediately followed the fight, and a couple waiters started serving the guests with an appetizing soup.

People watched the show while waiting for their friends and sect members to gather. As time went by, there were more and more people inside the hall. From ten to twenty people in the beginning to around sixty later on.

After dinner, Garen and Raydon followed the Celestial Circle Gate’s disciples out of the hall, they crossed the corridor and a garden and arrived at their respective rooms to rest.

The next morning, they were led to a practice ground for some morning exercises and flexing their bodies. Garen then returned to the main hall with the Raydons, waiting for people from the White Cloud Gate to arrive.

Raydon’s Orthogon Sword Gate already had a female disciple there.

Garen was still by himself.

On stage, the performance from yesterday repeated. After breakfast, Garen waited until noon. Finally he saw his fellow disciples from the White Cloud Gate come in after a few Celestial Circle Gate disciples.

"Senior Brother!"

"Senior Brother, how are you here so early?"

"Good morning, Senior Brother."

Four young people wearing white training uniforms came to Garen in a line and respectfully greeted him.

There were two guys and two girls, their ages ranging from fifteen to twenty.

"I’ve been waiting for the whole morning. You guys are so slow." Garen stood up and smiled. "All right, sit down and get some food. Tomorrow is the main tournament event. You all have to reach your best forms and don’t lose face for us all."

"Yes!" four disciples replied uniformly as they sat down around Garen.

Scenes like this had happened for countless sects over the course of a few days. People around them did not care for it.

The five disciples watched some opera. The main hall was filling up as more people from other sects came in.

The group was very patient, a disciple from the Celestial Circle Gate had come earlier to hand them the event schedule.

Garen had already watched the show yesterday, so it was boring watching it again. The other four were not paying attention either, showing great anticipation for tomorrow’s tournament.

"This is an opportunity for the disciples to show off their strength. They have also formed a tournament ranking among themselves."

Raydon was sitting close to Garen, the two sects had pulled their tables together. As time went by, they were getting closer.

"There is a ranking for normal disciples and one for the Secret Martial Arts disciples. Of course the latter is the more important one, but a sect’s overall strength is estimated by the overall rankings."

"Does the overall ranking include the masters?" Garen asked in a whisper.

"Of course, but what’s different from the disciples is that the strength of older Secret Martial Arts masters is relatively fixed. They can’t improve too much in a short period of time. Normally these masters only compete once in a few years, which is why the younger disciples are the deciding factors of the rankings."

"If that’s the case, shouldn’t every sect send out their best disciples to compete?" Garen was puzzled

"Naturally, but this ranking is not fully representative of a sect’s strength. Some disciples have graduated from their masters, and thus, cannot come to this tournament.

Which is why the major purpose of this ranking tournament is to find out who is the strongest among the young generation of disciples. Even if it’s rather inaccurate in estimating a sect’s overall strength," Raydon explained.

Garen then understood. Fei Baiyun’s other three disciples had already graduated. Therefore, they did not meet the requirements of this tournament. Bringing Garen to this tournament was probably also intended to enrich his experience.

Afterall, this exchange was held once every two years, so he could try again if he didn’t make it this time.

The White Cloud Gate was already one of the bottom small sects. It wasn’t easy to drop even lower.

After thinking this through, Garen started chatting with Raydon. The middle-aged man introduced some famous sects and gates to him.

Usually at Raydon’s own gate, nobody could bear his nagging. Now that there was someone willing to listen to his chatter, it lifted his spirits. Words shot out from his mouth non-stop.

Garen sat there with him the whole day and learned many things about the Secret Martial Arts world.

The next morning, Garen led the four disciples from the White Cloud Gate and followed someone from the Celestial Circle Gate. They did not go back to the main hall, but rather headed toward a platform along the corridor.

The platform was circular, located in an open patio on the ninth floor. Four highrise buildings surrounded it, blocking the scenery.

The stage looked like a giant white concrete button in the middle of a dark well, strangely eye-catching.

The area around it was spacious, over twenty sects all had their own sections. They circled around the platform, surrounding it.

Garen sat to the left of the platform, near the entrance, with the other four disciples behind him.

He glanced around. All he could see on the four sides of the platform were people’s heads. Each sect had only five people, other than the servicing disciples from the Celestial Circle Gate. In total, there were over a hundred people. All of whom looked very young.

The oldest he could see were middle-aged men and women. They were around the age of Raydon, less than forty-years-old.

The Crimson Sand Sword and the Celestial Circle Gate stood on opposite sides of the platform. Beo was in all blue, standing across a one-eyed man on the other side. Unlike Beo, the man was smiling with a mild and polite temperament.

Garen carefully observed that man. He was the strongest man from the Celestial Circle Gate, Andrela. He didn’t look too exceptional, far from Beo’s dazzling and intrepid appearance, but Garen could tell that the man was extremely self-confident, as if he could calmly face anything in the world.

Not only Garen, any disciples who were ambitious had their eyes on these two.

The chaotic platform settled down thanks to the organization from the Celestial Circle Gate’s disciples.

A skinny elderly man with a long beard jumped onto the platform holding a big brass bell.

"The ranking tournament officially starts now. We will begin with the lowest ranks from last time. Which sect would like to challenge first?" His voice was not loud, but everyone could hear him clearly.

Garen took out a piece of paper which listed the rankings of the twenty-seven sects.

White Cloud Gate was ranked seventeenth.

"I’ll go first." A man in black clothing jumped onto the platform. He ripped off his clothes and threw them off the stage. "Encore Fist Sect, Laffer Draco. I challenge the Knife Fist Sect!"

Just then, a flat chested woman rushed onto the stage. "Nola, Knife Fist Sect!"

Without any more words of greeting, they started fighting. Hitting back and forth, their forms and techniques looked rigorous, but their hits were shallow and soft. The impact sounded weak. Oobviously, they both lacked strength, and their martial arts were focused on technique rather than strength.

No more than ten seconds later, the man in black was pushed off the stage. The sect he came from sent another disciple up the stage, which also got pushed down quickly. There was clearly a huge skill gap.

Normally, a match would not last a long time. The slightest mistake could be the deciding factor between people of a similar level. If they were close in strength, the result would depend on their current state of mind.

Garen sat in the audience and watched casually. The starting matches were only show matches between disciples without Secret Martial Arts.

Match after match ended on the platform. Some disciples with conflicts also used this place to solve their problems.

Soon, the White Cloud Gate was challenged by the eighteenth ranked Fighting Association. The challenger was a hot blond girl with blue eyes. She had just defeated her challengers from the nineteenth ranked sect. She had beaten four opponents all by herself and was still able to challenge the seventeenth ranked White Cloud Gate.

"Let me!" Behind Garen, a sturdy young man stood up excited. "Senior brother, can I go?"

The young man was middle of the pack among the four disciples. His Explosive Fist Art was not rank one yet, but his skin was still stronger than that of normal people. He was also very strong for his age.

"Simon, you think you can handle her?" Without master Fei, everything was up to Garen to decide. This was also an opportunity for him to solve problems on his own.

Simon nodded. "I watched her matches. Although her legs are well trained, her overall strength is weak. I just have to find an opportunity and take control of her lower body."

"Fine then, don’t disappoint our White Cloud Gate," Garen told him. The overall ranking didn’t depend on this match, but mostly on the Martial Adept disciples. Yet if they lost too many matches, it would still have a negative impact on the ranking.

"Got it senior brother, don’t worry." Simon smiled, and saluted his three other friends.

"Get lost, we all know you only wanted to fight because she’s hot." A girl waved her hand speechlessly.

Simon laughed as he earnestly climbed onto the platform and walked in front of the blond girl.

Bang! Bang!

The opponent straight up gave him two side kicks, hitting Simon’s arm, and made a loud thud.

Simon stood steadily, his face showed a complacent smile.

"You are too weak!"

Chapter 81: Ranking Tournament 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The golden haired beauty did not say anything as she got down to the floor and performed a leg sweep. Her movements were fast and precise. The part where she sweeped towards was extremely accurate as well; it was in the back of Simon's knees.

Bang bang bang bang. As the sound of a series of blows rang out, Simon's expression suddenly changed. He tried to grab ahold of his opponent's long legs but was easily avoided each time and was repeatedly kicked in the same location instead. His opponent's speed exceeded his by far too much.

Even the strongest power was useless if it could not hit the opponent.

As the two of them fought in the ring, one of them was standing still, while the other was circling around the opponent and kicking from time to time. It was as if an agile monkey was teasing a clumsy bear.

The golden haired beauty's leg sweep was abnormally fast each time. Her fighting skills showed that she had a deep foundation. Her accuracy was also very astonishing. As she circled around Simon, the places that she kicked would always be the same five positions. No matter how much her opponent would try to block, she would be able to repeatedly hit the same positions from different angles.

Pa!

Finally, Simon fell down on his knees, then could not maintain his balance any longer and fell flat onto the ground with a bang. With his opponent's foot stepping on his back, he could no longer move.

"The Fighting Association wins."

Garen, who was spectating below, knitted his eyebrows. He was bothered by this type of opponents who specialized in speed as well. With his current increase in combat skill as well as his explosive force, he could easily take down any opponents that entered within a certain range. However, the other students were unable to do that. Simon did not even use the White Cloud Combat Arts. He only relied on his talents and the Explosive Fist Arts to fight and could only be made a fool of by his opponent. It was no wonder that he lost.

"Simon lost, I'll go!" A tall and slim woman suddenly stood up. "Senior brother." She looked towards Garen.

Garen glanced at her. "Keling, are you confident that you'll win? The other party are preparing to change their member as well."

"No, I can only give it a try. I checked their information beforehand. The Fighting Association was only inferior to us by just a little the previous time. The fact that they're proactively challenging us this time means that they're confident." Keling was one of the most elite students picked out from White Cloud Gate and one of the two strongest students. She was also present in the previous exchange gathering.

"It's better if someone else goes. You can't lose here, otherwise it'll affect our morale." Garen hesitated for a moment, then looked towards another female student. "Jiali, you'll go."

"Alright." Jiali was not bashful at all. She stood up and somersaulted into the ring from the side.

"We'll let Jiali squander the opponent's stamina first," Garen whispered towards Keling. Then his line of sight landed on the other muscular male: he was the last candidate of White Cloud Gate. Out of the four candidates chosen by Fei Baiyun, the main force was the two of them. They were chosen to improve their ranking.

Jiali fought against another student of the Fighting Association in the ring. Even though her legs were sturdy, her opponent's kicking power was stronger. After a few kicks in the same spot, Jiali immediately fell down and could not get up any more.

It was just that the girl was born with a strong tenacity. When she fell over, she would get up, doing it three times.

"The people from White Cloud Gate isn't much after all. With this kind of level, you're simply too weak," the male student from the Fighting Association taunted. Before he even finished speaking, he kicked out once again and viciously struck Jiali's abdomen.

Bang!

Jiali staggered backwards and fell down on her buttocks. She could not get up for a while.

This girl was still struggling and wanted to get up.

Below, Garen immediately stood up and announced with a frown.

"White Cloud Gate admits defeat for this match!"

Ding ding ding… "The Fighting Association wins." the old man loudly shouted while shaking the bell.

The other female student standing behind him, Keling, quickly went up to help Jiali get down.

"Are you alright? How does your knee feel?" Keling had a good relationship with her; she immediately took out an ointment and used it on Jiali.

Garen was standing one side with a frown on his face.

"She's even weaker than the external student, senior brother Erwin. I really don't understand how she was even selected." Back then when he went for the core disciple examination, even the senior brother Erwin who was together with him was stronger than her.

"And if we're comparing tenacity, that girl, Daris, who joined White Cloud Gate for her family's dojo wasn't any inferior to her." Garen shook his head.

"Senior brother, she's the cousin of Keling..." Simon, who was resting nearby, moved closer and whispered.

Garen finally nodded in realization.

"Who's going next?"

"I will!" Keling stood up while coldly staring at the man standing in the ring. "I will go and educate that trash who doesn't know how to speak like a human."

Garen carefully sized up Keling. She was known as the strongest female disciple within the White Cloud Dojo and was indeed somewhat skilled.

From the luster of her skin, he could tell that her Explosive Fist Arts had almost reached the rudimentary level. Looking again at her posture and movements, there was a strong hint of the Four Big Forms of White Cloud Combat Arts. She actually assimilated the Four Big Forms into her daily movements as training. Her talent was truly astonishing.

"Your Four Big Forms is very powerful. You should be able to win." Garen nodded.

Keling was startled that her strong point was actually immediately seen through by her senior brother. She did not think much of him previously, but she was currently alarmed and did not dare to act as carefree as before.

"I am going!" She slightly bowed towards Garen, then ran a few steps and jumped into the ring.

Garen did not watch Keling's match and looked towards the male student who remained silent.

This last core student was called Rimridor. He was currently the strongest male core student in the dojo. Rimridor's elbows were slightly sharp; when his arms were folded together, it was like two blades were placed on his knees.

He was not a new student and had been in the dojo for a few years. He was currently twenty years old. Whether it was the Four Big Forms or the Explosive Fist Arts, he had already truly mastered them. He was different from Garen; Rimridor relied purely on his willpower and perseverance to master this two martial arts. Just by sitting there, he gave others a feeling of a dormant volcano.

"Rimridor, you're up next. Are you confident?" Garen was the senior brother in name. Since his master was not around, then it was his responsibility to ask this question.

Rimridor nodded. "The Fighting Association is not a problem."

Garen could tell that other than the other Secret Martial Art disciples, Rimridor was not afraid of other ordinary students. If it was not for his age, then he would already be qualified for learning Secret Martial Art.

****************

On the top of the two storey building next to the ring, several semi-circular platforms extended out. On each of the platforms, the Dojo Masters of various dojos were seated.

Fei Baiyun was among them as well. He was seated on a white wooden chair on the right and was looking at his student, Garen.

"Fei Baiyun, is that your last disciple that you've brought this time?" A man with a red goatee was all smiles as he stared at Garen. "I am not impressed at all… He's still inexperienced compared to my Shield Strike Gate's head disciple, Pharo."

"The ability of someone is not determined by words, Gate Master Chris." Fei Baiyun glanced at him. "Even though Garen is still young, he can calmly and independently handle matters on his own. Regardless of his martial prowess, I am very satisfied with this."

He originally thought that the sixteen year old Garen would panic when handling such matters when he was not around. He did not think that he would witness Garen methodically handle things in such a mature manner. Little did he know that Garen was actually not an ordinary sixteen year old. Adding his previous life, Garen would be in his forties.

The man with the goatee snorted and did not continue further. There was no point since he already knew that White Cloud Gate did not have any intentions of competing this time.

However, an elderly man with dark skin sitting on the other side narrowed his eyes.

"Old man Fei, let's set aside this exchange gathering. Your eldest disciple, Rosetta, crippled my second disciple. How are we settling this matter?"

Fei Baiyun's expression became cold. He recognized the other party as the Faction Leader of the number ten Double Halberd Fist. He was an experienced veteran from the south.

"I see that it's Faction Leader Watson. It's just that your second disciple, Bessie, is extremely talented and was personally taught by you. How could my disciple, Rosetta, have injured him? Doesn't it seem unlikely that Rosetta was able to defeat Bessie?"

"The great detective Fisto has already thoroughly investigated the matter. In addition to the investigation on Rosetta's movements, it has already been confirmed that it was your eldest disciple, Rosetta, that injured Bessie. All four of her limbs have been crippled. Hehe… How cruel of her." Watson sinisterly laughed.

"No matter what, I will thoroughly investigate this incident and give Double Halberd Gate an explanation!" Fei Baiyun knew about the severity of the situation. The sort of move that easily cripples others was no longer an orthodox move.

"There's no need for that." The elderly man sinisterly laughed once more but he did not continue further and looked towards the ring below.

Fei Baiyun became sullen. This was not the first time he received accusations. Rosetta had caused trouble a few times before, resulting in an awkward situation for the current White Cloud Gate. A few friendly dojos that used to be familiar with them were gradually drifting apart. They were almost isolated.

"It looks like I really need to properly investigate when I get back. Right now it's the exchange gathering between sects, I won't think about such things for the time being." His gaze landed on the ring below once more.

Above a circular platform, the leaders of the Celestial Circle Gate and Crimson Sand Sword were seated together and were discussing the performances of the disciples below. The two sects had always been united. Even though there was fierce competition between their disciples, the relationship between the two sects were still friendly.

The other leaders of various sects had their own social circles and were discussing their own matters.

Soon, the disciple from the Fighting Association was knocked out of the ring by Keling and was quickly caught by his fellow disciples.

"White Cloud Gate wins. The Fighting Association has failed their challenge," the old man loudly shouted while shaking the bell.

Keling did not move from the ring and loudly said.

"White Cloud Gate wishes to challenge number sixteen White Shark Gate."

The White Shark Gate was a very strong sect. A female disciple with fair skin and tall figure casually came up and traded a few blows with Keling. Both of them did not want to expend their energies further and simply came to a draw.

It was obvious that they were conserving their energy for the disciple ranking tournament later.

These matches were just an appetizer. The true show was the ranking tournament later. It also included the true ranking competition that even disciples of Secret Martial Arts had to participate.

It was also the focus of the various sects.

After Keling returned, Rimridor did not wish to participate. His objective was the ranking tournament later as well. Garen simply stood up and announced that White Cloud Gate gave up on continuing their challenge.

The matches at the beginning was originally intended for ordinary disciples to demonstrate their skills.

Chapter 82: Ranking Tournament 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The real focus was on the ranking tournament later. Each sect would send out five pupils and each of their rankings would be aggregated to determine the real ranking of each sect. It was also the stage to find the strongest among the younger generation.

After that, it was just more matches between ordinary disciples of a few sects. There was basically nothing to see; it was only contests between those using basic skills at the most. Without any Secret Martial Arts, they were only slightly better than general hobbyists.

Finally, the match between ordinary disciples of Celestial Circle Gate and Crimson Sand Sword ended. The elderly judge raised up the bell in his hand and was no longer listless like before.

"Next, we'll begin the official ranking tournament. Each sect will send out disciples to participate as individuals and the overall ranking of each sect will be determined by a fixed formula."

The old man waved his hand and a few beautiful young ladies appeared. They were wearing short skirts and stockings, while their hair were tied into ponytails. One of the young ladies was carrying a large box as she stood next to the old man.

"Could each sect please send out their representatives to draw lots! Then head toward your respective rings for your qualifying matches." The old man pointed toward the surrounding buildings. "The rest of the matches will take place within the surrounding buildings. The previous top three sects will automatically enter the finals and need not participate in the drawing."

Andrela from Celestial Circle Gate smiled toward Beo from a distance, then turned around and walked into the building behind him. He could not be bothered to continue watching the lot drawing.

Beo snorted and not wanting to be outdone, left as well. The two of them were far stronger than the other disciples. There was no need for them to worry that a new opponent would suddenly appear. They only had each other as opponents from the start.

Garen was queuing up within the crowd as he watched the both of them leaving. He could feel the powerful confidence and pride from the two of them. He did not understand how strong they were, but he knew that the average person would not be able to ignore all of the Secret Martial Art practitioners there and calmly leave. It was a sign of confidence from having great power and success.

He could not help but recall the words of his senior sister, Rosetta. "Every single victory will nourish your confidence… and make you more powerful."

Soon, the people in front of him had drawn their lots and it was his turn.

Garen walked to the front, then nonchalantly reached into the box and pulled out a lot. The number written on the white paper was 24.

He stood on one side as the rest of the disciples from White Cloud Gate drew their lots as well.

"Could the participants who have drawn their lots please proceed to their respective rings. The winner of each match will proceed to the next ring according to the referee's instructions. Participants that have lost will all return to this ring to participate in another round of ranking. Everyone will be given a chance to challenge any other participant, other than the winner, for their rank. Once the matches has ended, the top ten will proceed with the finals," the old man loudly announced.

Garen and the rest of the disciples from White Cloud Gate went on separate ways and headed for their respective rings.

Garen's lot number was 24. After entering a large building, an attendant escorted him through a series of corridors to a spacious workout room.

The room was white and was the size of a large conference hall. There was a white, circular ring in the middle and there was ropes surrounding it just like a boxing ring.

A young female referee in black clothing was already waiting in it.

There were also some other young people standing in the room, who were there to watch the fight.

There was also a bald and muscular man—who was so muscular that his muscles was slightly deformed—standing next to the ring. He was staring at Garen the moment he entered.

This man was wearing a black leather pants while his upper body was naked. His muscles seemed to throb along with his breathing and the muscles on his shoulders looked like malformed roots growing out of the ground.

"Could the contestants please come to the stage," the female referee on the stage loudly said.

Garen stopped appraising his opponent. He slowly walked to the side of ring and somersaulted into the ring.

Even though he was muscular as well, there was still quite a difference between him and his opponent. It was like the difference between an adult and a child. His opponent also got into the ring.

One of them was big and the other was small. On one side, his skin was dark and he was wearing a black leather pants. On the other side, Garen's clothing was entirely white and his skin was fair. As the two of them stood on the stage, the contrast between them was clear.

At that moment, a pair of man and woman entered the room as well. They were the two that went to receive Garen and his master: Jaden and that crossdressing girl who tried to sound out Garen but ended up crying.

"Junior sister, this is the ring of that Garen from White Cloud Gate. This is his first match,"Jaden whispered to the girl while his gaze naturally landed on Garen.

"This guy is pretty lucky: his opponent looks strong." The girl gloatingly whispered while giggling, "He deserves it for being so arrogant at the station! This time he's definitely going to suffer."

Jaden nodded.

"His opponent is Benjamin, the third Holy Fist disciple from Holy Fist Gate, and has been practicing Secret Martial Arts for three years. Even though Holy Fist Gate's rank is only twentieth and isn't strong, the strength of its third strongest disciple definitely isn't ordinary. If I were to meet this Benjamin, I can only admit defeat as well. I heard that this Garen was only accepted as a Secret Martial Art disciple a while back. The difference between them is very clear."

"In addition." Jaden added, "That Garen's defense isn't bad. He's definitely going to be beaten up for a long time." After finishing, he could not help but laughed as well. "He's going to suffer this time."

Within the ring.

Garen moved his head from side to side while calmly analyzing his opponent. His opponent's size was indeed giving him a lot of pressure. This type of body size was already similar to his second senior brother, Farak, and the power is definitely very scary.

When Jaden and that girl entered the room, he saw them from the corner of his eye. It was obvious that they were there to watch the show.

"To meet me in the first match, you're unlucky." The muscular man grinned, revealing a set of pearly white teeth. "My name's Benjamin, the third holy fist disciple from Holy Fist Gate. You should feel honored for losing to my fist."

Garen was dumbfounded. His opponent was so egoistic that he was proclaiming his victory before they even fought.

"I am Garen, disciple of the seventeenth ranked White Cloud Gate. Can we start?" He looked toward the referee.

Ding.

The female referee nodded and shook the silver bell in her hands.

"You may begin." She quickly got off the stage, so that she would not be accidentally injured.

Garen narrowed his eyes and analyzed this Benjamin.

This was the first time he fought with a disciple from the true Secret Martial Arts World. He had Mammoth Secret Technique but his opponent had their own Secret Martial Art as well. Obtaining victory depended on the difference between their experience and strength.

"I'll test his strength first."

With his mind set, Garen slowly took a standard White Cloud Combat Arts stance.

"Go ahead."

"Your stance isn't bad, but let's see how your strength is. Rank seventeenth, don't disappoint me." Benjamin laughed and walked toward Garen with a boxing stance.

Chi!

His right fist extended and instantly disappeared into the distance. It turned into a black line as it smashed toward Garen's chin.

It was a simple uppercut but the speed was fast and the strength was strong. Before it even reached, Garen felt a slight blast of wind pressing on the skin of his chin.

"What a powerful strength." Garen quickly reacted and his stance immediately changed. His right elbow swung forward and accurately arrived in front of the fist.

Bang!

As their fist and elbow collided, both of them took a step back.

Garen narrowed his eyes as he looked at his opponent.

"He's very strong; his strength should be close to 2. If this was his normal strength, in addition with the force of impact and speed, he should be able to hit as hard as me. He's indeed strong. However, I am stronger!"

His current Strength attribute was at 2.45. Even though his body size did not stand out, the muscle density of his body was extremely high. He might not be eye-catching, but his actual explosive force was far stronger than most people.

"Kill him, Benjamin! Kill him!" the girl beside Jaden suddenly loudly shouted. Raising up her fist like a little girl, she continously waved. "That fellow from White Cloud Gate said you're a big piece of shit! He even said that he can beat you using only one hand!"

"What a dumb way to goad someone, even an idiot wouldn't fall for it." Garen was speechless. He looked toward his opponent.

"Uhh..."

He was even more speechless when he looked toward his opponent.

Benjamin's forehead was bursting with blue veins and his eyes were bright red. It was evident that he was really angry.

"You brat... " He heavily panted. "Tyrant Star!!"

He suddenly roared. Both of his fists started to darken, turning from a normal suntanned color to a pitch black ink color.

"I am going to smash you to death!!" Benjamin charged toward Garen like a mad rhinoceros while panting heavily. The stage was trembling under his heavy footsteps, generating a series of disintegrating sounds.

A straight punch!

Benjamin's fist was like a blackened piece of metal as it rushed toward Garen's chest. It was like a heavy, gigantic hammer was fiercely swung at Garen.

"Shoot! Charge! Step!"

Garen suddenly shouted. He lifted his elbow and knocked aside the punch, then his body moved forward and charged into his opponent's chest.

Benjamin's face went pale as his body flew backwards from the impact.

Garen chuckled as his right leg rose up and stamped forward.

Boom!

Benjamin was knocked down from the air and heavily landed on the ring, causing it to shake violently. He lay there with froth coming out from his mouth and had already fainted.

With three simultaneous moves, Garen was able to knock down Benjamin—who had already been sent flying—into the mat of the ring.

With his White Cloud Combat Art having reached intermediate level, he was already considered a seasoned veteran. Dealing with someone who had not gone through brutal combat was simply too easy for him.

The intermediate level of White Cloud Combat Art allowed Garen to swiftly switch between his Four Big Forms. He was also adept at baiting his opponents with deliberate flaws in his stance and exploiting that moment to strike. On the other hand, Benjamin's combat level was still at the beginner level. The difference between them was too large. The fight was already over before Garen even used half of his strength. His opponent's Secret Martial Art did not have any effects at all.

The entire hall was silent. The referee, who was standing at the side of the ring, did not expect the fight to end so quickly as well. She was stunned for a moment before she quickly went into the ring and shook her bell.

"Winner! Garen from White Cloud Gate! The next match will take place at ring no.17!"

That was when the spectators finally reacted. With the referee's announcement, a huge uproar occurred. A few members of the Holy Fist Gate quickly went into the ring to check on Benjamin. They breathed a sigh of relief when they discovered that he had only fainted.

Jaden and that girl were dumbstruck as well.

"What a high combat level!"Jaden muttered, "Out of all of the disciples that I've seen, his combat level is enough to rank within the top ten!"

That girl who previously goaded Benjamin was dejected at the moment. Even with her level, she could tell that she was not his match.

Garen got out of the ring and headed toward the entrance while tidying his clothes. Seeing that Garen was heading toward their position, the two of them quickly got out of the way.

As Garen was walking past the two of them, he glanced toward the girl. He slowly reached out his hand and stopped in front of her neck, then suddenly clenched his fist.

"Kacha." He mimicked the sound of bone breaking with his mouth.

The girl shivered and her face went pale. She was like a pitiful little lamb.

"Little fellow, you're still too inexperienced." Garen laughed as he left. He followed the attendant standing outside to ring no.17.

Her senior brother, Jaden was also held down just now by the aura that Garen deliberately emitted. He felt that he would be instantly crushed if he tried to move. He could only watch as his junior sister was being bullied and did not dare to move.

He was only able to relax when Garen left.

"Junior sister… Are you alright?" He could tell that Garen did not have any ill intentions against his junior sister. That was just a small punishment for her previous actions.

Wa!!

The girl started to wail out loud as tears flowed out of her eyes.

Chapter 83: Ranking Tournament 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After exiting the tournament grounds, Garen walked along the black corridor and rushed towards the tournament venues of White Cloud Gate trainees.

A medical team in white suits in the corridor rushed into the tournament grounds. They put Benjamin who was in the ring onto a stretcher then quickly passed by Garen.

Garen looked at Benjamin on the stretcher.

"I won the first round…" he mumbled.

Walking along the corridor through several corners and break rooms, Garen soon reached a small room with a sparse crowd.

He gently opened the door. The interior had the exact layout as the tournament grounds earlier.

In the ring, Collin was leaning on the pillars panting. Her whole body felt weak, and there were blood stains all over her face and body. Her opponent was a slender young man with a cool air about him. He didn't have on him any trace of having been in a fight.

From the looks of it, Collin could still hang on for a little longer. Even though she was at a disadvantage, but the outcome couldn't yet be determined anytime soon.

Garen didn't stay. He just casually looked at Collin, and let her see him, then decisively turned around and walked towards the other tournament grounds.

After that, he visited the tournament venues of the rest of the trainees.

Simon had won easily. He was up against an average opponent whose Secret Martial Art was relying on a burst of pace, but that had been completely inundated by him.

Carrie and her opponent were difficult to set apart.

And lastly, Rimridor.

Garen walked into the tournament venue.

In the ring, Rimridor silently stood his ground, and managed to strike his opponent to the ground with one punch. He had a blank look on his face, and there was a strange air about him.

His opponent was a young boy with a short stature. The youth was wounded all over his body—he must have been struck to the ground multiple times—but this time he still managed to slowly get up, albeit with some difficulty.

"You want more?" Rimridor said casually. He was wearing a pair of black cuffs; both his elbows were bent so it made his arms seem like two sharp gimlets. "If we go on like this, you'll die."

Bang!

He adopted a lightning-quick Shot Form and viciously struck the youth's chest. The blow caused the youth to rebound off the ring ropes.

"I…admit defeat!" the youth struggled to spout those few words out. His head slumped, and he fainted.

"No fun," Rimridor said indifferently. He waited for the referee to announce his victory, then somersaulted down from the ring and walked to Garen. "Eldest Senior Brother, why are you here?"

Garen frowned slightly. He sensed an inexplicable temperament on Rimridor, similar to Eldest Senior Sister.

"Your combat skills…were they taught by Eldest Senior Sister?"

"Yeah." Rimridor casually nodded.

Garen was slightly worried, but he wasn't sure why. He patted Rimridor's shoulder and didn't continue the subject. "Time to go to the next tournament."

Rimridor nodded, and followed Garen out, leaving the slightly deserted tournament ground.

Both of them came out from the door and went their separate ways. Garen found his next tournament venue based on the room number: 17.

As he reached the corridor of the room, he saw that the entrance was already crowded. Most of them were students wearing tight yellow clothes. Garen wasn't sure which sect they belonged to.

Garen furrowed his brow a little, and slowly walked forward.

Clap.

The first brawn he touched felt his whole body shudder all of a sudden, and automatically avoided him and gave up his place. Then the second one, and the third…

A series of people, those that Garen touched, all voluntarily parted to let Garen pass. Even they were confused as to why they were giving way to Garen.

Garen slowly walked into the room through the middle of the crowd, as if it was parted seawater revealing a narrow aisle; it made him unusually conspicuous.

Inside the room, Jaden and the crybaby girl from Celestial Circle Gate were already there. When he saw how everyone politely gave way to Garen, Jaden was impressed.

"See that, Long Er? That's the Vibration that can only be mastered by a true expert! This guy…so powerful!" Jaden was in awe.

"Vibration?" The girl still had tearstains on her face. She stared at Garen menacingly, and was shocked to hear what her Senior Brother had said. "He can master Vibration? Senior Brother, do you not see it? Vibration is a threshold only mastered by the top ten level of experts!"

"Stop talking. By mastering Vibration, he is already qualified enough to become a contender for top ten! Just watch this tournament," Jaden whispered as he dragged Long Er to an inconspicuous corner. He was worried Garen might make Long Er cry again.

Garen walked in through the crowd. His strong and tall body was extremely proportionate, his stride calm; his face didn't show the slightest trace of anxiety of someone about to compete in a tournament.

"You kid! How dare you shove me!" a brawny man with stubble clad in black roared and shoved Garen.

Clap.

His hands were on Garen, but he didn't manage to move him. He was stunned.

Clap clap!

He shoved hard again, twice, but there was no reaction. It was like pushing against a high wall: it was impossible to move.

"The weak can only rely on such means to win, huh?" Garen looked down at the stubbled man in front of him, and casually waved a hand.

Bang!

The brawn crashed onto the side wall like a swatted fly; his eyes rolled and he blacked out.

Woah!

The crowd was in an uproar. Everyone avoided him like the plague; no one dared to stand too close to Garen.

"So powerful!"

"Margent was dealt with just like that!"

"This guy is from White Cloud Gate, right? Who would have thought there was someone so strong in the Southern Twelve Gates?"

Garen didn't bother looking at the others. He threw away a fine needle: it was the secret weapon that the stubbled man tried to use on Garen, of which he had managed to neutralize. He walked straight to the ring and asked a stunned Celestial Circle Gate referee disciple.

"Where's my opponent? Still not here yet?"

"Uh… You just settled him…" Under Garen's piercing stare, the referee broke out in a cold sweat.

Garen was shocked. He looked at the stubbled man passed out by the wall, and shook his head slightly.

"Where is the next round?"

"…You don't have to move for the next round, your opponent will come over," the referee hurriedly explained. "Your winning time was the shortest. The future tournament venues will be determined by winning times: the shorter time would gain the home advantage."

Garen nodded, closed his eyes, and sat down cross-legged to rest.

As he quieted, the whole room slipped into a murmur of discussion. The twenty over people in the room didn't dare to speak loudly, for fear of accidentally disturbing Garen. Everyone was whispering to their companions, and would look in awe at Garen—sitting by the side of the ring—from time to time.

Jaden and the young Long Er were infected by the atmosphere too: they lowered their voices.

"An expert who has mastered Vibration… I can't believe that White Cloud Gate, one of the Southern Twelve Gates, would produce such an expert. I thought this time would be the same as before, and the Southern Twelve Gates Union would just be eliminated. I didn't expect that there would be someone like Garen."

Long Er hid behind her Senior Brother, as if she was worried she would be spotted by Garen.

"So Senior Brother, is this Garen the strongest person in the Southern Twelve Gates Union?"

"Maybe, if we don't consider the disciples trained by masters, then he should be the strongest one. The Southern Twelve Gates was originally an alliance of multiple small sects forming a strong force to counter other bigger sects and increase its influence as an organization. Most of the sects within it were of a similar level, but now with the sudden appearance of this Garen, there might be issues with the balance amongst the sects. But this isn't something for us to consider," Jaden patiently analyzed. "I've seen the strongest disciple from the remaining eleven sects, not comparable to Garen at all. This Garen could indeed be the strongest man within the Southern Twelve Gates."

"The strongest man within the Southern Twelve Gates huh?"

Garen's figure sitting cross-legged reflected in Long Er's clear pink pupils for the first time.

******************

Upon defeating the stubbled Margent with one blow, Garen's fame was spread by the students who had witnessed it.

Margent was the elite fighter from Myriad Manifestations Gate. He broke into the final fifteen the last time around, and was the strongest core from the Southern Twelve Gates. Now he had been sent flying against a wall in one blow by Garen, and had passed out.

This instantly caused a stir amongst the spectators in all tournament venues.

In that instant, all the disciples from Southern Twelve Gates who had felt ashamed for always ranking low in the tournaments could hold their heads up high. They had always swallowed their pride in front of stronger sects, and held their tongues when they met with trouble; they were always the side to suffer. All because they didn't have strong Senior Brothers and Sisters to back them up, and it would be impossible for masters to intervene in disciple-level conflicts. After all, others would have stronger masters.

Natural selection was accepted as an inalienable principle, so the disciples from the entire Southern Twelve Gates were used to such oppression.

Now that Garen had outshone everyone, this gave all the disciples of Southern Twelve Gates hope. If he could defeat a top fifteen contender with such ease, they could have a good chance at top ten this time!

"Senior Brother Garen from White Cloud Gate is the strongest man from our Southern Twelve Gates! I heard he easily defeated Benjamin from Holy Fist Gate!"

"What about the rest of the disciples from Southern Twelve Gates?"

"All eliminated…"

"It's all up to Senior Brother Garen now!"

Within the tournament room, more and more disciples from Southern Twelve Gates crowded in. The tournament venue was packed; there were people everywhere.

The voices of the students were rowdy. These disciples who had been subdued for too long finally saw hope; they all crowded over to watch Garen compete.

Garen slowly opened his eyes, and looked at a disciple not far off in front of him.

"You said everyone else from White Cloud Gate has been eliminated?"

That disciple nervously nodded.

"Yes…yes, Senior Brother. Seventy to eighty people have already been eliminated. No one from White Cloud Gate managed to enter the third round except you…"

"So that means, I'm the only one left?" Garen wasn't surprised. He looked over to the entrance: Collin, Simon and a few others were shielding Carrie as they squeezed in.

At that moment, a stout youth with fat all over his body climbed into the ring. He was wearing a white tank top, tight against his thick layers of fat, like a large stuffed balloon.

The portly youth seemed to still be chewing something, and swallowed it with a gulp. His eyes stared straight at Garen outside the ring.

"A contestant from Southern Twelve Gates? How lucky."

Garen stood up, somersaulted onto the ring and stood his ground.

The referee rang the bell.

"Let the tournament begin!"

Chapter 84: Ranking Tournament 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I am Ai Luo of Asura Palm. And you are?" The portly youth had a head of blonde hair; it didn't look dyed, but instead natural. He reached a hand to brush his blonde hair off his face, and asked earnestly.

"Garen. White Cloud Gate." Garen raised his hand, put on a Four Major Forms pose, and he instantly sharpened up.

"I'll just stand still and let you hit me, how's that?" the stout youth Ai Luo said, chuckling. "As long as you manage to injure me, you win."

"You idiot!" Jaden outside the ring covered his eyes as he couldn't bear to look.

Bang!

Garen leapt forward, his elbow straight like a sharp arrow, piercing straight into the fats of the chest and abdomen of the stout youth.

The layers of white fat started to violently vibrate; fatty ripples formed in the parts that were hit.

Ai Luo's expression changed: his face was pale.

"Go!"

Garen's expression was composed. He gathered momentum with a twist of his foot, and thrust his entire body against the stout youth.

Wham!

The force caused the hill-like body of the stout youth to fly out of the ring and crash onto the ground, creating a huge cloud of dust as he landed.

"Declare it," Garen said casually as he straightened up.

"…Yes…yes, very well." The referee snapped out of his shock. "The winner of this round, Garen from White Cloud Gate!" He rang the bell hard, but the sound produced by the small bell was too soft; it was completely muted by the gasps from the crowd.

Jaden stood in a corner with a somber expression.

"Looks like we underestimated his strength. He is already qualified to challenge Beo of Crimson Sand Sword. Asura Palm is ranked seventh. This stout one was one of their best: he was ranked eleventh in the previous meet. The fat all over his body was his best defense. His Secret Martial Art is the constantly activated tough Ripples of Fat to counteract Vibration. Vibration by average experts have almost no effect on him."

To a side, Long Er's petite face turned pale.

"So…so how did he take down the stout guy in such a short amount of time…?"

"His Strength, Speed, and his technique of consecutively concentrating power onto one point; he combined all these to directly break the surface tension and counter the Ripples of Fat Secret Martial Art. What a terrifying fighting spirit!" Jayden explained with a mumble. "His Vibration, his physical coordination, and most importantly the speed of his Explosive Force, is so much more powerful than average practitioners of Secret Martial Arts! I once saw the Secret Martial Art of White Cloud Gate, the Mammoth Secret Technique. Its general effects could not achieve the toughness that he had displayed. Is it possible that he is training in a new martial art technique? Something that's not from White Cloud Gate?"

"No! He did actually use the Explosive Force Technique from White Cloud Gate," a male voice could suddenly be heard beside them.

Jayden and Long Er were both startled. They turned around, and both instantly displayed reverence.

"Eldest Senior Brother!"

"Greetings, Eldest Senior Brother."

Both of them quickly greeted him.

Standing to one side, was the one-eyed Andrela, who had just rushed over to watch the tournament. He was the strongest disciple of their generation from Celestial Circle Gate, and the most prominent youth martial arts expert in the South.

He had a black eye patch over his left eye, and a crystal clear, dark golden pupil for his left eye. A head of long, jet black hair was casually draped behind him to the waist. This gave him a mysterious and gentle impression.

"19, 23, you're still fresh. With only a few years of training under your belt, it's natural that you can't recognize his true style." Andrela looked at Garen in the ring with a trace of admiration.

"If I'm not wrong, this Garen has mastered the highest level of Secret Martial Art of White Cloud Gate. How terrifyingly talented! Mammoth Secret Technique of White Cloud Gate is merely a third-rate Secret Martial Art; many sects have a similar training method for Secret Martial Arts. I can't believe he could actually train in a third-rate Secret Martial Art to such an extent."

"It can't be… Eldest Senior Brother, you mean to say that, the Secret Martial Art level of this Garen is higher than that of his master?" Jaden asked, aghast.

"I'm not sure. The true strength of the White Cloud Gate Master is known only to the masters who have dueled with him. But it's just a third-rate Secret Martial Art, so even if he's highly trained in it, the power would be limited. Not to worry." Andrela looked at Garen who was resting cross-legged, and shook his head regrettably. "What a shame. If he was discovered by Celestial Circle Gate first, his accomplishments would be unimaginable. Shame… His Secret Martial Art is limited; he has peaked."

He used the word 'shame' twice.

Jayden and Long Er understood what he meant. Garen had trained in the Secret Martial Art of White Cloud Gate to such an extent that his physicality had crystallized. It was impossible for him to change course and train in another Secret Martial Art. Moreover, the limit of a third-rate Secret Martial Art was the level on which Garen was at; there was no way to enhance it any further.

"So Eldest Senior Brother, in your opinion, what ranking does this Garen deserve based on his true strength?" Long Er asked curiously. With the strongest Eldest Senior Brother by her side, the trauma that Garen caused her seemed to completely vanish: she was instantly more relaxed.

"It should be the same as Eastern Saintcloth from Quicksand, around fifth or sixth—provided that the true strength of the rest hasn't changed much this year," Andrela replied casually.

"Fifth or sixth?!" Jayden and Long Er were both shocked; they couldn't believe it.

Garen did not notice Andrela in the corner of the crowd. It was as if he had an unusual magic: the people around him barely gave him a second look, as if he was utterly invisible.

Garen was breathing slowly according to the breathing rhythm of the Secret Martial Art to recover his energy. Even though he defeated the stout contender from Asura Palm in one blow, he still expended some energy. He still had to prepare himself to face the next opponent in his prime condition.

Unfortunately, after waiting for quite some time, his opponent for the next round didn't turn up. It wasn't just him, even the referee started to get impatient. He sent a disciple from Celestial Circle Gate to inquire, and found out that Garen's opponent for the next round was still in the middle of a tough fight. Apart from ongoing duels, some contestants had sustained severe injuries and required rest and treatment. All contestants for the fourth round had to continue waiting. The rest were martial arts experts who had already progressed to the fifth round. According to the rules, it was impossible to arrange a duel with them in that moment.

"That means I can have a little time to rest for now?" Garen stood up and asked softly.

"Yes. You have about half an hour to rest. In the meantime, you are free to move about," the referee nodded and politely replied. In the Secret Martial Art world, the strong was always revered. Garen's true strength had gained his respect.

"Very well." Garen planned to sit cross-legged again and continue his recovery.

After sitting only for a while, a disciple from Celestial Circle Gate clad in black handed a note to him.

"Senior Brother Garen, someone outside claims to be an acquaintance of yours. He asked me to give this to you."

"An acquaintance?" Garen took the note, opened it, and his eyes widened instantly.

There was only one line written on the note.

'Want to know how Gregor died? Meet me at two o'clock at night. I'll be waiting for you outside.' There was even an illustration of a familiar tattoo design below the words: it was the graphic on the back of the hands of those psychokinetics.

He crumpled the note in shock. Garen's eyes narrowed; there was a trace of coldness in them.

"Where is the person who passed you the note?" he asked the disciple who handed the note over.

"Still waiting outside…" Before he could finish his words, he saw Garen jump straight off the ring and dash out the door. The packed crowd around the ring did not impede him at all. He was like a moving reef; the crowd automatically parted wherever he went.

He was out of the room in an instant. There seemed to be a commotion in the room on the other side; it sounded like a crowd cheering.

"Shura! Shura! Shura!" The cheers were like the tide, coming wave after wave; the atmosphere was bustling.

Garen glanced around the corridor. Suddenly the corner of a black cloak at the far end of the corridor caught his eye.

He arched his body and instantly rushed towards it. He was at the end of the corridor in a few strides. Around the corner was a ten-odd-meters straight black corridor; there were no bends in the middle, but the person earlier had vanished, all in a matter of a few seconds.

"Traveling twenty to thirty meters in a few seconds…" Garen looked at the people walking around in the corridor. He grabbed a female disciple that walked past him and asked, "Did you see someone in a black cloak pass by earlier?"

"Ouch! That hurts! No! No I didn't!" the girl repeatedly answered in shock.

"I'm sorry, I've hurt you." It was only then that Garen noticed he was using too much force, so he released his grip on her. "You really didn't see?"

"I really didn't! Who wears a black cloak in broad daylight anyway?" she rubbed her shoulder as she finished replying, then ran off as fast as a rabbit.

Garen walked on along the corridor. He kept questioning passersby as he walked, but the answer was that no one had even seen a person in a black cloak.

The other disciples from White Cloud Gate rushed over too, and followed behind Garen.

Collin wanted to walk up and greet him, but was halted by Simon, who shook his head at her.

"It must be something important to Eldest Senior Brother. Let's help him search."

Apart from Rimridor who was nowhere to be seen, the four of them kept asking everyone they met, but no one had seen a person in a black cloak at all.

Garen walked into a break room along the corridor. He slowly sat on the bench and wiped the sweat and oil off his face. The note and that corner of a black cloak were haunting him.

Shouts and cheers kept coming intermittently from the rooms around them: those were the tournament venues of other contestants.

The other three from White Cloud Gate were also exhausted, so they sat down with Garen.

"Eldest Senior Brother…" Collin looked at Garen worriedly.

"It's almost time for the next tournament, right?" Garen looked up, and reverted to his usual calm. "Thanks for helping me out in the manhunt. Let's get back to the tournament."

"Okay!" Simon and the rest answered hurriedly.

Garen stood up and sorted through his emotions.

Ever since he enhanced his Mammoth Secret Technique to the level of Achieved Mammoth, even though he didn't feel anything then, eventually he realized that the Achieved level of the Mammoth Secret Technique made his every action more coherent. The Four Major Forms of White Cloud Combat Techniques, Vibration Technique in Strength Utilization under the Mammoth Secret Technique, and Techniques in Fundamental Wrestling Arts had all harmonized into one. It was as if he was a real mammoth: his every move was calm but powerful, and integrated.

He finally understood the purpose of the Mammoth Secret Technique: it was coordination.

Coordinated practitioners of the White Cloud Secret Method, Explosive Fist Arts, White Cloud Combat Arts and the like, would be able to meld all the techniques into one, and form a naturally coherent comprehensive force.

Chapter 85: The Truth 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This coordination was already a hard limit; anything further would just be a slight enhancement. He had understood that—the Explosive Fist Arts, White Cloud Secret Method, and White Cloud Combat Technique—were all fundamental parts, like a mammoths limbs. Training in these martial art techniques was like honing the mammoth's limbs: the stronger they were, the better the foundation, and the stronger the integrated effect of the Secret Mammoth Technique.

The purpose of the Secret Mammoth Technique was to integrate all these together, to form a real large mammoth. Different people formed different Mammoth characteristics: this was dependent on physical quality, and the level of Explosive Fist Arts or White Cloud Secret Method they have trained up till.

Garen's own White Cloud Secret Method had reached an unprecedented level; his Explosive Fist Arts had reached an intermediate level, a minor achievement; his White Cloud Combat Technique was intermediate too. Coupled with the strong physical quality that he was most proud of—a physical quality that was beyond the physical limits of an average person—everything combined, the Secret Martial Art helped Garen attain a terrifyingly phenomenal level.

This was just a third-rate Secret Martial Art technique, but had been practiced by him to an unfathomable level with his mysterious special ability.

Other practitioners from White Cloud Gate would not practice Secret Martial Arts on such solid foundation. Basically they would start practicing it once they had a good foundation of the rest. After all, Explosive Fist Arts and the White Cloud Secret Method were time-consuming martial art techniques. If they only started practicing Secret Martial Arts after attaining a certain achievement in those, it would probably not happen even when the practitioner reached 40 years old. Even the best talents would only be able to attain intermediate levels in Explosive Fist Arts and the White Cloud Secret Method. With their White Cloud Secret Method limited to intermediate level, not even attaining advanced level, there would be too big a difference with Garen's unparalleled achieved level.

No one knew the changes that an achieved White Cloud Secret Method integrated into Secret Mammoth Technique would bring about. The role of White Cloud Secret Method in Secret Martial Arts was like the heart of the mammoth, consolidating the power and explosive force of the entire body.

Garen wasn't even sure what stage he was at. He just knew that he was stronger than before, stronger than when he went to the Golden Hoop meet!

He rushed towards the previous tournament venue along the way he came from.

"Where is Master now?" he asked as he walked.

"After the next round is the final round to determine the top ten, Master should be here to watch," Collin explained simply. "He should be with the masters of other dojos and sects now."

Garen nodded and didn't say more. The incident with the note still weighed heavy on him; he didn't know who passed him the note, but…

A trace of coldness flashed across his face. Garen sped up. All along the corridor, every disciple from the Southern Twelve Gates would give way to him out of respect.

"I heard that Senior Brother Garen has been rated as the first person below the previous top ten! And it was Senior Brother Andrela who had personally evaluated this!"

"Senior Brother Garen, together with Senior Brother Tenstar Ni, have been regarded as the Senior Brothers with the most potential to enter top ten."

"The next round is the finals. Let's go get a place, quick!"

The whispers of trainees would reach their ears from time to time. Garen turned a deaf ear to all of it, but the faces of the other three gradually shone with a trace a pride.

White Cloud Gate had never been bestowed such an honor. As a small, third-rate sect, its martial art methods were limited; even extremely talented disciples have never managed to reach such a level. Every disciple could only participate for three times consecutively, not to mention there was an age limit. Eldest Senior Sister and Second Senior Brother had passed the age limit long ago, and even they were far from attaining this degree of evaluation when they participated.

Now that Garen had achieved it, the three of them walked with their heads held high, no longer the same as before.

After he passed through a few corridors, Garen strode into his initial tournament venue. In the packed room, someone was already waiting for him in the white ring.

A proportionately muscular youth with a tall flattop haircut resembling a broom, he had white hand wraps on both his hands, and a rebellious look on his face. His upper body was bare, and he was wearing white shorts. He had a shoe only on his right foot; it looked very odd.

Garen subconsciously looked at his feet.

When the youth shifted his right foot, Garen realized that the he wasn't actually wearing a shoe, but instead there was a black shoe-like motif painted onto his foot: both his feet were bare.

"Senior Brother Garen, please step into the ring," the referee shouted.

The tournament venue quieted down almost immediately. The crowd gave way to Garen and the other three. Most of them looked expectantly at him, only a few stared rudely.

Garen strode to the side of the ring, somersaulted into it then stood up.

"Order of the Iron Fist, Carlos." The youth had a hand in front of his body, and another clenched, resting at his waist: he adopted the horse stance, and put on a solemn posture.

"Garen of White Cloud Gate." Garen glanced at his opponent, not even bothering to adopt a stance. He looked sideways at the referee and asked, "Can we begin?"

"Begin!" The referee rung the bell definitively, then somersaulted out of the ring. This wasn't child's play: duels at this level were considered to be between experts. A referee like him could be accidentally injured if he didn't take care.

As the referee's voice faded, Carlos threw a fierce punch which arced to hit the right side of Garen's face.

The few-meter gap between the both of them was closed by him in one stride. His fist pierced the right side of Garen's face like a sickle. Due to the extreme speed, only a trace of a shadow could be seen, like the sharp, curved shadow of a sickle blade.

"How fast!" Garen was stunned. He barely managed to lift his elbow; he could feel a gust from the force of the punch ripple the skin of his face.

Bang!

The two were interlocked in a fist fight. Garen blocked with his right arm and threw his left arm out towards his opponent's face. His arm flung out like a spring; he was using a standard Shot Form. The explosive force of the punch made a whoosh sound.

Clap!

Another crisp sound could be heard. All their attacks were blocked by the other.

Within less than half a meter from each other, Carlos' spike-like elbow attacked Garen like a storm. Garen blocked his crucial body parts; the rest of the attacks hit his muscles and caused them to quiver violently but the effect soon passed. His skin merely reddened slightly.

A very frequent 'tap tap tap' sound like raindrops could be heard.

Carlos looked grimmer. Even his Vibration couldn't penetrate the toughness of Garen's Body Hardening Technique. It merely caused a reddening of the skin; this was something he didn't expect.

But to be able to reach this stage in the tournament, his opponent would naturally not be a weakling. He was already mentally prepared.

"Abrupt Kick!" Carlos roared. His right leg shot up and headed straight for Garen's chin. Its swiftness transformed it into a grey shadow.

Wham!

Garen didn't manage to react in time, and got hit squarely by the kick; his head jerked backwards from the impact. But with a sly grin, he threw caution to the wind and took the opportunity to grab his opponent's shoulder with his right arm, and tripped Carlos with a foot.

There was a muffled thud, and Carlos was held down by him in the ring.

Garen didn't hesitate as he followed through with a downward elbow smash.

There was a loud crash; a small dent appeared on the ring.

Carlos rolled over and dodged the attack. He rolled a few meters away from Garen and stood up again. He looked fearfully at the dent on the ground. These rings were made from high strength, special grade cement. Apart from a high base cost, this brought with it an extremely tough rigidity, almost ten times that of average cement. Now it had been easily damaged under Garen's strength.

"If I didn’t dodge that second move…" He let out a low cough. Phlegm surged up his throat, and he felt bursts of piercing pain in his back.

He turned sideways to spit out the phlegm: it was blood sputum. The blood red goop stuck onto the floor of the ring with a flop.

"Good fight!" When he got excited, Carlos' accent immediately turned into a rhotic tone; Garen couldn't make out the origin of the accent.

"You're not too bad either." Garen gave a soft laugh, and temporarily put aside all his worries. "Again!"

He stomped his foot, angled his elbow forward and dashed towards his opponent like a drill.

His left elbow complemented the Dash Form. Coupled with the impact of the Step Form, the integrated use of the Four Major Forms was his true transformation after receiving the Secret Martial Art.

This was the same maneuver he used to defeat the stout youth earlier.

When he rushed to the front of Carlos, the latter gave a cunning smile then suddenly crouched down and kicked Garen's lower body.

Whack!

Carlos caught Garen squarely in the calf, but his expression immediately changed as he attempted to roll over and dodge, but it was too late.

His opponent's calf was anchored like an iron wall. This was the result of a marked difference in strength. Moreover, his straight kick did not actually do his opponent any harm, not even a scratch.

Was this a bad joke? Usually the power of this kick was enough to rupture two sandbags arranged successively!

He saw Garen draw his hands to his chest and do an elbow drop, collapsing on him like a mountain.

It was too late.

Carlos did not hesitate; he made a ruthless decision.

"Abrupt Kick!"

Both his legs suddenly kicked upwards. The tips of his feet were like sharp spikes and stabbed Garen's chest and abdomen one after the other.

Wham!

The two collided hard into each other; the whole ring quaked from the impact.

The entire tournament ground suddenly fell into complete silence.

Garen slowly got up and looked at Carlos who was coughing up blood.

"No matter how fast you are, how fast your rhythm, I just need to hit you once."

It was only then that the referee rushed into the ring to strike the bell.

"The winner is Garen of White Cloud Gate!"

Hurrah!

The audience burst into a loud cheer; the whole tournament venue instantly became rowdy. Most of the disciples from Southern Twelve Gates were over the moon.

Garen shook his head as he watched the medical team carry the injured Carlos away. He looked down at his own chest: two red spots were clearly visible, and his skin was slightly swollen.

"He was indeed an expert who has mastered Vibration, much more lethal than an average person. Any stronger and he would have broken my defense."

"The next venue is the finals tournament ground, that is the open tournament ground outside. It starts tomorrow morning," the referee on the side cautiously announced. "Today's preliminaries have ended. Tomorrow will be the finals to determine the top ten."

"That is to say, I can go back and rest now?" Garen asked.

"Yes."

Garen leaped out of the ring. His white clothing was torn and ragged: Carlos' kicks earlier had shredded his clothes at his chest. He simply pulled off his top and walked out of the room baring his upper body.

"Eldest Senior Brother, you're finally in the finals!" Collin, Carrie and the rest were elated.

"At such a critical moment, where could Rimridor have gone?" Simon moaned softly.

"That guy isn't here yet?" Garen frowned, "It's fine, forget him. You guys head straight back to rest. I'll take a shower first."

"Yes, Senior Brother!" the three of them replied respectfully at once. Their impression of Garen now was higher and more authoritative than ever.

Garen nodded, and walked towards the left side of the corridor alone. Every now and then there would be some disciples from Southern Twelve Gates looking at him in admiration, and give way to him.

He had defeated Carlos from the Order of the Iron Fist. His reputation immediately reached a prominent height. The Order of the Iron Fist ranked ninth, but Carlos was indeed a top ten contender the last time. Now that he had been defeated, this meant that Garen could benefit from his detriment to advance further.

Chapter 86: The Truth 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Under the guidance of an attendant, Garen returned to the accommodation arranged by his sect. He entered his own independent room, took off his clothes and walked into the shower.

He shut the door and gently turned the faucet on.

Whoosh.

Cold water rushed out first, but soon the water warmed and steam slowly filled the bathroom.

Garen stood under the faucet, letting the warm water cascade down from his shoulders. The tense muscles and skin around his body gradually relaxed under the warmth. Hot water drenched his back and flowed to his feet, washing away most of the sweat and stains.

He wiped his face with his hands and started recalling the developments in the tournament so far. Each of his four opponents had their strengths and weaknesses. The strongest opponent was the last one, Carlos from the Order of the Iron Fist; his true strength was comparable to Golden Hoop Number 9.

"Now that I think of it, Carlos and Eldest Senior Sister share a similar fighting style: both aim to kill. But compared to Eldest Senior Sister at her current level, he is slightly weaker. Nevertheless, the difference is marginal," Garen contrasted Carlos with the standard of the Eldest Senior Sister that trained with him from his memory, and carefully evaluated it.

Since receiving the Secret Martial Art, even he himself was unclear what level his true strength had progressed to; he needed a clear comparison.

"Eldest Senior Sister would not have exhibited her full strength when she was training with me. Based on several daily details, I estimate that she is slightly stronger than Carlos. I could spar with Eldest Senior Sister when I am back to find out the current extent of my true strength. But why didn't Eldest Senior Sister and the others participate in the ranking tournaments? If they were here, White Cloud Gate wouldn't be in too low a ranking."

Garen's mind kept recalling the actions, strength and other details of Second Senior Brother and Eldest Senior Sister when they were in training.

Ever since he received the Secret Martial Art, his perspective had completely changed. His strength and martial art techniques have been coherently amalgamated to reach a stage where he could organically combine moves. Naturally, his perspective of former opponents had evolved, and he would notice more than he did before.

"Eldest Senior Sister and Carlos should be on the same level, and Second Senior Brother is slightly weaker. Third Senior Brother is on the same level as the guy from Holy Fist Gate in the first round. He's really too lazy…" As he thought about Third Senior Brother Joshua, he couldn't help but shake his head slightly. Practicing martial arts once every three days could still be considered diligent. No matter how talented he was, he wouldn't be able to accomplish anything if he wasted his talent like that.

He looked down and gently clenched his fists. After a few duels, Garen could clearly feel that he had become more powerful. There were no specific enhancements to his strength and speed, but his martial arts had become more powerful. He could spontaneously apply the Four Major Forms; they had been ingrained as a natural instinct. He could easily integrate the strength of his entire body in the execution of every move.

Even though the Strength points in the Attribute Pane remain unchanged, Garen could feel that his true strength had increased by more than one fold. He could probably achieve 500 pounds of explosive force in situ. If it were coupled with the impact of a run-up, the results would be unimaginable even to him.

"It would probably reach half a tonne…" Garen tilted his head upwards and allowed the hot water to directly drench his hair. "What a shame. This seems to be the maximum extent of the Secret Martial Art of White Cloud Gate. I could still progress further, but the Secret Martial Art has peaked."

Ding dong.

"Garen, are you there?" the voice of Master Fei Baiyun came from outside the door.

"I am, master," Garen hurriedly replied. "I'm in the shower. I'll be out in a minute."

He quickly turned off the tap, dried himself, hastily dressed then pushed the door open to walk out.

The door clicked as it opened. Fei Baiyun stood at the entrance clad in black silk clothing. He was wearing a round black hat and small sunglasses. Coupled with his handlebar moustache, he made an oddly delightful sight.

He let himself into the room and sat down. Fei Baiyun stared fervently at his disciple who closed the door and sat down.

"Garen, I was chatting to some old friends and heard that you won the preliminaries and entered the finals. You've really done me proud this time!" His face shone with glee. "I didn't expect your true strength to develop so fast after you've received the Secret Martial Art! This kind of talent… Looks like I was right in selecting you to be a last disciple!"

"Well done!" Fei Baiyun patted Garen's shoulders hard. "I will meet whatever request you have when we get back!"

"Master, you flatter me." Garen was somewhat embarrassed by his master's praises.

"I am clear about what is and isn't flattery. For you to be able to reach this level in a year, no one would have expected it. Your Secret Mammoth Technique should be at the Mammoth level, correct?" Fei Baiyun lowered his voice and asked.

Garen nodded. This was not something to hide. The Secret Mammoth Technique purely relied on perception and talent. It was different from White Cloud Secret Method and Explosive Fist Arts; those were fundamentals which required hard work.

"Indeed…" The more he looked at him, the more Fei Baiyun liked Garen. The smile that he suppressed to maintain his dignified image as a teacher couldn't be contained any longer. His wrinkly face grinned from ear to ear. "Any injuries from the tournaments?"

"None…" Garen replied truthfully.

Fei Baiyun suddenly stood up and looked at his disciple Garen, shook his head slightly and said, "I can't believe that a last disciple that I, Fei Baiyun, have admitted in my sunset years, would be such a fascinating character like you. There is still hope for White Cloud Gate…"

He hesitated, looked at the confused Garen, then finally made his decision. He reached a hand into his inner pocket and took out a round indigo metal container and gently opened it.

The metal box was merely the size of a palm, but there was another small black box within it. Fei Bayun opened that too.

On a piece of black silk inside the innermost box was a square black piece of paste, even on all sides. It looked insignificant.

Fei Baiyun looked at it and let out a long sigh.

"Here, eat this." He put it in front of Garen.

"What is this?"

Garen stared curiously at the squarish paste: it looked like hardened black toothpaste.

"Why are you asking so many questions? I won't harm you! Eat!" Fei Baiyun urged impatiently.

"Oh…" Garen picked the square paste up and put it straight into his mouth. He chewed a few times; it was sweet and sour, like eating a fruit roll-up. He swallowed it whole. Suddenly, from his mouth to his throat down till his stomach—any esophageal tract that the paste passed through—he experienced a cool refreshing feeling.

"Alright, rest well. Good luck in the finals tomorrow!" Fei Baiyun cleared his throat, patted Garen's shoulder and said as if nothing had happened. "I'll be off. You take care and condition yourself."

"Yes, master." Garen nodded respectfully.

At this, Fei Baiyun gave a contented nod, put his hands behind his back and sauntered out of the room.

When he was a short distance away from the room, he slowly turned back to look at the closed room door.

"Bloodboil Pill… Such miracle drugs are better utilized on youths. Don't disappoint me, Garen."

He turned around and slowly walked to the far end of the corridor, and soon disappeared around the corner. In that instant, even his silhouette seemed to have aged a lot.

At the other end of the corridor outside Garen's room, two other old men appeared. One had a full red beard, and the other had a pale and clean-shaven face, with skin covered in wrinkles and liver spots.

"I can't believe Fei Baiyun gave the Bloodboil Pill to that kid. That was his life's work: in order to collect all the herbs and ingredients, he almost lost his life several times. That is the White Cloud Gate miracle drug, able to cure internal injuries and prolong life, which he specifically intended for self-consumption in preparation for breaking through into the next stage. Now he's actually given it to this young fellow…" the red-bearded old man lamented as he recalled Fei Baiyun's silhouette walking away. He gently shook his head. "Without the Bloodboil Pill, Old Fei won't live for long."

"The accumulation of a lifetime of hard work, all wagered on one disciple. Old Fei is really…" the other old man didn't know how to continue.

"Life's like that. Everything is impermanent. Let's go. The matter regarding Eastern Saintcloth awaits, we have to sort it out soon. This kid doesn't let us have a moment of peace. He's getting into trouble wherever he goes!" the red-bearded old man sighed, and turned around to walk away.

The pale-faced old man took a look at Garen's room door, inexplicably let out a sigh, and turned to leave as well.

In the room, Garen was stunned to see the Attribute Skills Pane in the bottom of his vision undergo a slow but sure change.

Under the Skills column, for Secret Mammoth Technique, the word 'Achieved' after it gradually blurred, and slowly transformed into a new word: Explosive. But the wording was translucent, as if it hadn't fully crystallized.

"What's this?" Garen was shocked. He immediately thought of the thing that tasted like fruit roll-up that his master had given him. "Could it be some kind of secret medicine? What kind of secret medicine has such a powerful effect?"

The word 'Explosive' after 'Secret Mammoth Technique' floated about and looked unstable, as if it wouldn't be completed anytime soon.

Garen didn't know what would happen. He planned to observe first. This change seemed to be incomplete; maybe it would fully stabilize later.

After going out for dinner and giving some instructions to a few disciples, he went straight back to his room. He waited until it was dark outside, changed, and asked an attendant for directions to leave the Celestial Circle Gate grounds.

He went around the perimeter of the grounds and walked to the edge of a deserted forest.

Garen finally saw a figure in black cloak standing under the shadow of the woods. He stood silently with his back to Garen.

"You passed me the note?" Confident about his true strength, Garen approached him and asked loudly.

Whoosh!

The figure dashed straight into the woods without replying.

"Don't think you can escape!" Garen scorned and trailed closely behind.

The bushes and tree leaves rustled as he ran across. They were sprinting one after the other in the dark forest, but Garen didn't manage to catch up with him.

Soon, both of them dashed out of the woods. They had reached the edge of the forest, and suddenly he saw a huge loess stone wall in front of him.

Four skulls were mysteriously engraved onto the stone wall, side by side. The sound of the wind whistling could faintly be heard coming from the black eye sockets and mouths. Each skull was ten odd meters tall; it was extremely spectacular.

A wooden suspension bridge linked the forest area to the open area below the stone wall.

The figure in black rushed onto the bridge without hesitating. Garen followed, and ran past the bridge quickly. An ominous cold current of air constantly poured out from the dark abyss below. The bridge swayed side to side as they ran past, and both stopped at the loess open area below the skull stone wall.

"Who are you?" Garen stared fixedly at the figure in black.

The figure in black slowly turned around, and revealed a handsome, apathetic face of a man. His skin was pale; there was almost no blush on his face. A few strands of long, black hair were vaguely exposed around the edges of his cloak.

"Garen Lombard, the disciple of that foolish brother of mine…"

"Who are you?!" Garen narrowed his eyes as a chill flashed across them. "Do you know how Old Man Gregor died?"

"How he died?" The man calmly gazed at Garen. "I killed him with my bare hands."

"And so you shall go to hell!" Garen's eyes widened. A crater blasted open under his feet as he violently leaped towards the man. An explosive roar like a mammoth trumpet could vaguely be heard coming from behind him.